—
Special Episode
The Hero Public Safety Commission received a request for support
from a small country in Europe named Otheon.
They decided to dispatch
Endeavor's Agency to the scene,
and by extension, us,
who were interning there at the time.
Take-off
People. People. People. People.
We're going abroad!
Man, this is nerve-wracking!
You'll be fine as long as you know English.
They say drawing the symbol for people on your hand relieves anxiety,
but you have to pretend to eat it, too.
Th-Thanks, Todoroki.
People. People. People. People.
What? Even you can get nervous?!
You'll be fine as long as you know English.
Shut the fudge up, dimwits!
We're going on a mission overseas!
It'll be totally different from Japan!
I'm just trying to concentrate
'cause I wanna be at peak performance!
Oh well, I guess everyone's got
their own way of coping with stress.
Some get nervous, some get amped.
I guess Bakugo is the latter.
Hey there, Hawks and Tokoyami!
So where are you guys headed?
We're going to America.
They've got a large area to cover.
Hawks' speed will be a valuable asset.
That's Hawks for you! The fastest man alive!
What? Hawks?
Hawks?!
Hawks!
Hey, hey. Stop, my little chicks.
We're at the airport. Let's not make a ruckus!
There's no stopping the simps.
Why am I getting dragged into this?
I-It's all my fault! I'm so sorry!
Pathetic.
Endeavor!
Nobody approached him at all...
It's time to board. Let's go.
Y-Yeah!
Dad.
What is it, Shoto?
Why do I have to sit next to you?
If it's a joke, I'm not laughing.
I want to sit next to Midoriya and Bakugo.
T-Todoroki!
You bastard...
You still think I'm your friend?
Hey!
Change the seats.
C-Come on, it's not like it'll kill you.
How can he say something so cute
with such a scary face?!
I said I want to sit next to my friends.
Definitely the youngest in the family!
We are not friends!
Wanna enjoy your flight out in the sky
strapped to the tail of the plane?!
Kacchan!
Hand me the tickets!
N-No way!
Don't go ignoring me, dumbass.
Bakugo, can you hold on to this for a bit?
Are you even listening to me, shithead?!
What are you doing to Shoto?!
A-And this is supposed to be
Japan's Number One Hero Agency?!
My stress levels have already shot through the sky and into outer space!
Here, sit in this order.
Come on, you're not grade schoolers.
Right...
It won't be easy for him to
talk to me since I'm behind him.
Oh? Shoto will be looking at my back the whole time?
Not bad.
Endeavor's sitting right next to me?
I'll make him spill all the secrets behind his power by the time we land.
All's well that ends well.
Our flight's about to take-off so we're gonna go on ahead.
You guys can relax and
get ready for World Heroes' Mission.
Right!
Okay.
Yes, sir!
There he is! Don't run away from us, Hawks!
See ya!
Yikes!
Even the fastest man alive got caught twice!
A faraway land.
A world unknown to us.
What will we find there?
It's getting too noisy out here.
Take-off