That's Suichi Iguchi!
So it is the League of Villains.
Dammit!
No luck.
Let's get closer!
Deadbolt!
Sorry, I'm out!
Dabi!
Whoopsie-daisy.
You're too persistent!
Bastards! What are you up to?!
You expect us to answer that?
Why are the heroes here?!
Seems like the information was leaked.
Leaked? But how?
Who knows?
The pursuit team lost them. Now it's up to—
You don't have to spell it out.
Just leave it to me.
Endeavor!
The new number one, huh.
You're out so late.
Working hard, aren't you?
Jetburn!
Hey, hey, hey!
I'll run you over, Endeavor!
Mister, get back.
Prominence Burn!
Damn, is this it?
Endeavor.
Didn't know you were here.
You could've given us a hand, Hawks.
I just got here, Endeavor.
What about the League?
They were all doubles made with Twice's quirk.
What is that thing?
Seems like a life support system.
Maybe for transporting a new type of Nomu?
What'd you mean?
What in the world were Shigaraki and others transporting?
You sure took your time, Nine.
It was worth the wait.
The experiment was a success.
The world has become a superhuman society,
with about 80% of the population
having some kind of special trait.
I, Izuku Midoriya, was quirkless.
But then, I had a fateful meeting with the number one hero, All Might.
And he transferred his quirk, One For All, to me.
And then, I enrolled in the hero course at U.A. High School, the prestigious school that has produced many heroes.
I continue to run toward my dream.
That's right,
this is the story of how I became the world's greatest hero.
Hey, girls!
Come hang out with us!
No, thanks.
Don't say tha—
What the heck?!
It won't c-come off!
Are you hurt?
Ladies.
Thanks!
You saved us!
N-No, that wasn't me just now—
Down! I'm down here!
Asui, 70 meters past the rocks!
There's a child drowning!
Mommy! Help—
Are you okay?
Why're you crying?!
He got scared by your face.
Swimming prohibited!
Swimming past the rocks is prohibited!
NO TRESPASSING
It's dangerous past here, so please don't enter.
That was amazing!
Not bad!
It's not a show.
Hey, Shoto! Can you make me some more ice?
Sure.
Here you go.
That's too much!
There are so many heroes!
Sis?
Iogi Heights
This is U.A. Hero Agency!
Sure, I'll send someone right away.
Kaminari, head to the west district.
Mr. Matsuda's battery is dead again.
Not again!
The old man should get a new one already.
Go get 'em, Chargezuma!
Go, go!
Hi. You've reached U.A. Hero Agency.
Where we strive to solve all your problems with a sparkle.
Did you find the lost dog?
Yeah, just did.
Don't worry, the dog's fine.
Good work. Next up is a missing parrot.
My little brother's lost! I can't find him anywhere!
It's okay, calm down.
First, tell me your names?
There's no need to worry.
Of course!
Iida, Granny Sato threw out her back!
Got it!
I will rush over at once!
Lost child in the shopping arcade!
Any heroes available to come with me?
No way.
That was fast.
C'mon, don't be like that, Bakugo.
Uraraka, I'll come with you.
Just how do you plan on finding a lost kid with your quirk?
Tourist
Guide
If we're looking for a lost kid, then I guess I'm up.
Uraraka, I'll go with you too.
Iogi Heights
U.A. Class
1-A
Hero Agency
One For All: Full Cowling!
8%!
Hero Agency!
Class 1-A!
Heading out!
The twenty of us from Class 1-A
of U.A. High School's hero course,
have come to Nabu Island,
a place far from mainland Japan.
Even though we only have our provisional hero licenses,
why are us students working as heroes on this island?
Last Month at U.A.
Of course, there's a reason behind it.
Principal Nezu
Sending hero course students
to areas where pros aren't available?
A practical hero work recommendation project?
Yes, the current superhuman
society is in the midst of chaos.
Because you, the number one hero and
the Symbol of Peace, are effectively retired.
And because of that, the villains are on the move.
So you're saying that in order to go up against them,
it is imperative that we train the next generation of heroes.
The top brass at the
Heroes Public Safety Commission think so.
Well, I'm sure you have your own thoughts on this,
but I hope you will cooperate with us.
The hero work recommendation project.
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
You'll be stationed on Nabu Island in southern Japan.
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
那
歩
島
Nabu
Island
The pros in residence retired due to old age.
So the people there will have to depend
on you till a permanent successor arrives.
That's so superhero-like!
I mean, we get to be real heroes!
I'm so hyped, yay!
I'm bursting with excitement!
This isn't an internship or a work study.
It's real hero work.
Becoming a hero has been my dream since I was little.
Finally, I will...
Nabu
Island
那
歩
島
I'm not done talking!
All right.
As a rule, you won't get any
backup from the teachers or pros.
It goes without saying that you'll be
responsible if anything happens.
Keep that in mind and behave as heroes should at all times.
Understood?
Yessir!
Nabu Island Fishing Association
Sis, where are you?
Where are you, Sis—
Katsuma?
You're Katsuma Shimano, right?
A Hero...
You've been separated from your sister, right?
Here, come with me.
You're late! That took too long!
Sis!
What's your name?!
I'm D-Deku!
And you are?
I'm Katsuma's older sister, Mahoro!
Eh? Then I guess you found him already.
Thank goodness!
That's not good at all!
You were looking for a lost kid
for over an hour! What took you so long?!
Stopwatch
You're from the famous U.A.
hero course but you're totally useless!
If they're gonna send losers like you,
we'd be better off with the old geezer we had before!
I-I'm sorry.
Well, I guess it can't be helped.
You are just a high schooler.
I'm sorry, I really am!
Deku?
Next time, make sure you do
your job properly. Got it, Deku?
R-Right, I'll be more careful next time.
Let's go, Katsuma!
Ah, okay.
Um.
Thanks.
You don't need to thank him for anything!
Deku, what's going on?
Why were you apologizing?
I got scolded for taking too long to find the lost kid.
Huh? What the heck?
But still, I'm glad.
About what?
That Katsuma got back to his sister safely.
Now that was a very Deku-like thing to say.
Huh? What's that supposed to mean?
That you're a hero through and through!
Nabu Corner Store
Restroom
Those heroes are totally useless, just like I thought.
They can't even handle an island
like this where there's basically no crime.
U.A. must've scraped them from the bottom of barrel.
They came looking for me, though.
That boy was definitely a hero.
Hmph.
Then I guess I'll have to show you
the truth about these so called heroes.
Sis!
Meanwhile
I wonder if the students are
doing alright on their hero work project.
The population of Nabu Island is barely a thousand.
They've only had trivial crimes in the last 30 years.
There's no reason to be concerned.
Besides, being a hero doesn't always mean facing
huge disasters and fighting evil villains like you did.
Interacting with people they protect
will also be an important experience for them.
I'm exhausted!
We've gone Plus Ultra beyond what's allowed by the Labor Standards Act.
Class rep, don't you think
we've done enough small jobs?
There's no such thing as a big or a small job.
We may be working as heroes but we're still students.
We must work hard and prove
ourselves to earn the islanders' trust.
Excuse me! Someone here hasn't done any hero work ever since we got here.
Well, somebody's gotta stay behind and watch the office.
What're you gonna do if a villain shows up while all you geniuses are out doing stupid crap?!
C'mon, there aren't any villains on this island.
Sorry for the interruption.
Mr. Mayor.
Thank you for carrying Granny to the hospital earlier.
And thanks for fixing my bike!
And my battery!
And for keeping the beach safe too!
Here's some fresh fish!
Just a token of our gratitude for all your help!
All right! Let's dig in!
Show some restraint, you guys!
Thank you for everything.
It was nothing. It has been a huge
help ever since you came here.
And I'm sure we can continue to count on you.
Of course!
Absolutely! We'll keep doing our best.
Thanks for the food!
That was so delicious.
You can feel the love they put into their cooking.
Moments like these make me glad I became a hero.
Yeah!
Kacchan of the Bakugos!
We're gonna go take a bath and hit the sack.
Night watch is all yours!
Why me?!
Because you didn't do anything all day.
Let me tell you the truth.
My quirk has the power to transfer power.
One For All.
One person cultivates the power,
and passes it on to another,
who also cultivates it and passes it on.
It's the crystallization of power that spins together
the voices of those who have a courageous heart
and want the power to help.
And next, it's your turn.
Now that you have inherited One For All,
one day you'll have to fight against this great evil.
Now, it's your turn.
Currently, I can only use
One For All at a maximum of 20%.
I have to work even harder to make this quirk my own.
Kacchan!
How's the patrol going—
Looks like you're getting better with One For All.
We can't talk about that here!
I don't like to be kept waiting.
I know that better than anyone.
We've known each other since childhood.
So hurry up and make it your own and fight me with all you've got.
I'll prove it to you that I'm gonna be the number one hero.
Yeah.
I'll work as hard as I can to make this power truly my own.
To become the world's greatest hero!
Then I'm gonna be even greater than the greatest!
Um.
You're the boy from this afternoon.
A...
A villain...
A villain's showed up!
A villain—
Alright, start talking!
Hero Public Safety Commission
There have been continuous acts of
violence against heroes since last week.
The victims were knocked unconscious,
and they all lost their quirks.
Shigaraki's group seems to have acquired
the illegally manufactured quirk erasing needle.
Do we have reports of them
succeeding in its mass production?
No, we don't.
Then we must investigate it.
Continue with your—
Could their quirks have been stolen?
What?
The victims were heroes, so the quirks that were lost were naturally all useful ones.
If the suspect has a quirk that can
steal quirks like All For One...
That's...
Well, either way, Shigaraki's involved.
I'll try investigating both possibilities.
So, where'd the cargo end up?
The heroes didn't collect it, right?
Yeah, that's been confirmed.
What was the cargo anyway?
The Doctor said there's no need for us to know.
What the hell?
He made us do the transporting
but he won't tell us anything?!
Doesn't that make you even more curious?
Just forget about it. Okay?
Roger!
No way!
Shigaraki Tomura.
Do not touch that.
Forget about it.
Doctor.
Kyushu
You said you'll come home in ten days, right?
Daddy, do your best at work!
You don't have to worry about us.
I'll take real good care of Katsuma.
I'm sure you will, Mahoro. Katsuma,
I'll bring you as many souvenirs as—
I've finally found it.
F-Found what?
Don't worry, I won't kill you.
But, I will take your quirk.
We finally got it, huh?
With this, we can make it a reality.
The new world that we desire!
Nine?!
Wh-Why?
Why?
It doesn't work on type B blood.
What?!
Back to square one after coming this far?! Damn it!
No, there's still a way.
Daddy, do your best at work!
You don't have to worry about us.
I see.
Quirks are
inherited.
What are you tagging along for, damn Deku?!
Because if there really is a villain, you might need—
I'll be fine by myself!
Hey, where's the damned villain?
I-Inside those castle ruins!
Should've told me that sooner!
Sis!
Over there!
Go hide.
Katsuma!
Stun Grenade!
This thing...
Kacchan!
Huh?
Ouch!
The villain...
Ow, ow.
Jeez!
At least get a little scared!
Th-That girl.
You're the one who made that villain's illusion?
Yikes!
Huh?! How did you know it was an illusion?
It's obvious!
It didn't have a shadow.
You little brat.
Is taunting heroes a hobby of yours? Huh?!
I'm a little different from your everyday heroes.
I'm the man who'll surpass All Might
and become the number one hero.
The name's Katsuki Bakugo!
You picked the wrong hero to mess with!
P-Please don't yell at my sister.
Huh?!
You were in on it too, weren't you?!
You're going overboard, Kacchan!
Let me go, damn Deku!
We should be glad it was just kids playing pranks!
Be glad?!
Kids these days have no respect!
Hold up, dammit!
Kacchan!
I told you to leave them alone!
Stop telling me what to do!
Wh-What's up with that Bakugo guy anyway?
Become the number one hero? Is he confusing it with the ranking of heroes who look like villains?
He did come to save us, though.
Katsuma, do you want to be a hero that badly?
I'm against it because it's dangerous.
Besides, I know someone
who's even cooler than heroes.
Who?
Daddy.
He is always thinking of us and looking after us.
I want you to be as cool as him.
Among the victims, there's another who lost his quirk.
But he isn't a hero like the rest.
On top of that, everything that can be used to identify him has been stolen.
The suspect doesn't want anyone
to find out what quirk he stole?
Why does he need to hide it?
Hello! You've reached the U.A. Hero Agency!
Your travel bag has gone missing?
Okay, we'll send someone right away!
A tourist lost her luggage at the shopping—
I'll go, I'll go!
You come with me too, Aoyama!
Oui!
Another lost item? People should at least try to—
The client sounded like a real cutie on phone.
I can't forsake someone in need!
Shoji is asking for more backup on the beach!
I'll go over, then.
I'll go on a regular patrol.
I'll go and help Mr. Nijima with his fields.
I'm off!
Is that you, Katsuma?
Is something the matter?
U-Um.
S-Sorry about yesterday.
That's so sweet! You came to apologize?
It's okay. I'm not mad or anything.
Will you tell the other hero that I'm sorry too?
Sure, I'll let him know.
But Katsuma, why did you do that yesterday?
My sister hates heroes.
She told me that even if I said there was a villain,
the heroes would be too scared to do anything.
So that's why, I...
You believed in us.
Huh?
You believed that we'll come and save you, right?
That's why you came to get us.
Yeah.
Oh, that badge!
It's the Ninja Hero, Edgeshot, right?
Yup!
Do you want to be a hero too, Katsuma?
My quirk isn't good for hero stuff.
Besides, Sis says it's dangerous.
You're from the famous U.A.
hero course but you're totally useless!
I see. It's not that Mahoro hates heroes.
She's just worried about Katsuma.
Izuku. I can't take this anymore.
You keep getting hurt.
Your mom's heart can't take it anymore.
Hey, Katsuma.
What kind of hero do you want to be?
A super strong hero who beats up evil villains.
I see.
I want to be a hero who saves people in trouble.
Save people in trouble?
Yeah.
Katsuma, you want to be a hero who wins to save people.
And I want to be a hero who saves people to win.
The order is different but we're aiming for the same thing.
To become the best heroes we can be.
Which means,
we'll both have to give it our all!
Yeah.
Oh, but we should try not to
worry our families too much.
Right!
Little Katsuma really loves heroes, doesn't he?
Here, take this.
Thank you very much, Mrs. Suzumura!
Be kind to him, won't you?
They lost their mother at a very young age.
And their father's away for work so often.
So him and his sister are on their own a lot.
Of course, those of us in the
neighborhood look after them.
But it's lonely not to have
parents around at that age.
Sis!
Where did you go off to, Katsuma?
To see Mister Deku.
I went to apologize for yesterday.
But, why?
Listen, I love daddy.
I do wanna be as cool as him someday.
But...
But still...
Wh-What was that?!
The breakwater.
Why's the ferry coming this way?
Hey, hey, hey!
Run!
Get away!
What? What's going on?!
Chimera, Mummy, make sure I don't get interrupted.
You're in charge of diversions.
Any preferences?
Do as you see fit.
Roger.
Slice.
I know.
V-Villains.
They're real villains!
Sis, let's call the heroes!
But they're just high schoolers—
Mister Deku will come to save us! I know he will!
I finished working the fields!
Welcome back, Midoriya.
Good work!
What? If it's another lame job—
Villains just showed up at the harbor!
I know that voice.
Aren't you that brat from yesterday?
Don't think we'll fall for the same trick—
I'm not lying! It's the truth, Bakugo!
Hello, Deku here!
Bastard.
At the fishing harbor—
What did Mahoro tell you?
Base Transceiver System
Communications have been cut off.
Next up is...
I hope it's still a joke.
Anyway, I'll go to the fishing port!
Thank you so, so much!
Isn't it great, Maa?
Yeah, Mii.
What the heck? She has a boyfriend! Damn that Ashido!
Huh, what was that?
Heroes, it's a v-villain!
It's a villain for real!
That's too sudden!
W-We need to do something!
Aoyama, use your bellybutton beam!
It's called Navel Laser!
Oh? Three heroes in the middle of nowhere.
He just made more!
Hagakure, did you contact the office?!
I can't reach them!
I don't have any signal!
No way!
If I keep shooting, my tummy will...
Damn it!
What should we do?!
Froppy, Tentacole!
Evacuating everyone is our first priority!
On it!
Get away from here, quickly.
Twirling Tail Dance!
What are you after?
Why are you doing this?
You look too young to be a hero.
Tokoyami!
Sorry, I'm late!
Dark Shadow!
Right!
We can't use our phones!
Go back to the office and bring help!
But—
I'll hold things up over here!
Huh? My phone isn't getting any signal.
You're right.
Mine, too.
And mine.
What's going on?
Don't tell me...
This is bad!
V-Villains have appeared!
Villains?!
They're tearing apart the shopping arcade!
Iogi Heights
Heroes are trying to hold them back, but—
Reporting in!
A villain has appeared at the beach!
What?!
Ojiro and the others are holding
them off but they need backup!
Iida!
There's no time to hesitate.
We'll need to split up into two teams
and deal with the villains!
Bakugo, Kirishima and Kaminari.
Intercept the villain at the shopping arcade.
Yaoyorozu, Jiro and Ashido.
Go with them to help with first aid and evacuation.
Todoroki, Sato, Sero and Tokoyami.
Come with me to backup Ojiro to the beach.
Uraraka and Koda.
You'll be our relief evacuation team.
This is a race against time.
We are the only heroes on this island.
And we are the only ones
who can save the islanders!
U.A. High School's hero course, Class 1-A, heading out!
The fishing harbor!
I need to tell everyone!
No signal?!
There are villains on the island.
The others probably know by now
and are dealing with the situation.
In that case, I need to make sure that Mahoro is safe.
Mahoro's house is...
Of course, those of us in the
neighborhood look after them.
Near Mrs. Suzumura's house!
My tummy hurts.
My head is at its limit too.
Mineta! Aoyama!
You extras can't even handle one villain?
You guys are pathetic!
Bakugo!
Red Riot is on the scene!
Chargebolt is here too!
Guys!
Reinforcements?
Everyone!
Yaomomo! Girls!
Let's get people to safety and provide first aid.
Right!
AP Shot: Auto Cannon!
Damn it!
Thanks!
Bakugo!
Damn it!
What the hell's this?!
Objects wrapped in my bandages
move according to my will.
It doesn't work on living things,
but it does with what they're wearing.
Your suit, clothes and weapons are mine to control!
Bakugo!
What will you do if your
friend becomes your enemy?
Ojiro!
Octoblow!
With that body, I bet many would make fun of you.
Don't you ever blame your parents for this?
Shoji!
Leave it to me!
Take care of Ojiro!
Now! Tokoyami, Sato!
Sugar Rush!
This can't stop me!
Sato!
Hey, hey.
Even though you're just kids,
this is going overboard.
Sis, we need to inform the heroes about the villains!
Cell phones aren't working so we can't do anything.
Let's get home first, and tell everyone—
Our house...
Found it.
Type B cell activation.
Kid, I'm going to steal your quirk.
Don't worry, I won't kill you.
Stay away!
I said stay away!
I know it's an illusion.
Sis.
Mister Deku!
Deku!
A power type quirk.
It's okay. Can you run?
Yes.
Quick, get away from here.
Okay!
Stop right there!
Why are you after those children?
Stand aside.
That's not gonna happen!
I'll have to kill you if you're in the way.
Air wall?
So that's his quirk?
Did he just shoot lightning bolts?
It seems like he has two independent quirks.
It's almost like
All For One!
Stop it, Bakugo!
That dude's controlling him.
What should we do, Kirishima?
What can we do?
Shit!
D-Damn it!
I'll let you choose.
You can become one of my puppets
or be killed by your friend.
Stop screwing around!
What?
Don't underestimate me!
Damn mummy bastard!
He sacrificed his own weapon?!
I've got a lot stocked up, you know.
And you get the maximum blast.
Die!
You did it, Bakugo!
And with minimum collateral damage too.
Guys!
Where's the villain?
What? Beating him was too easy.
And the islanders?
We evacuated them all towards the west area.
Where are you going, Bakugo?
Take care of the evacuation!
I'll blast the rest of 'em!
Dammit.
He has us cornered with his power.
Iida, what should we do?
For now I think we should
just keep this monster occupied.
At least until the evacuation is complete.
Black Abyss!
Recipro Burst!
Not putting up much of a fight, are you, heroes?!
At this rate...
Delaware Smash: Air Force!
Air projectiles?
That's an interesting way to use it.
I can't let him get to Katsuma and his sister.
I gotta keep him distracted!
He can launch air projectiles too?
Just how many quirks does he have?
I don't know what he can do.
Better to attack him first and find out!
One For All: Full Cowling!
20%!
His power increased just now.
With all the power I can use right now,
St. Louis Smash!
20% wasn't enough?!
This power.
This quirk.
It's worth stealing.
Stealing?
Is that what he said?
So he really does have the same quirk as All For One.
He's going to steal my One For All!
I couldn't steal it.
No. I don't have enough space for all of them.
This kid.
This quirk has incredible potential.
I need to move.
Move! Move!
Its very existence is a miracle.
Which means, I'll have to eliminate it.
Did he blast me with the wall of air?
Is that Mister Deku?
Mister Deku!
Deku!
Run away!
But—
Hurry up and get away!
That maniac's after the two of you—
Mister Deku!
Hurry! Run!
No.
No!
What is that?
Deku?
Somebody, please!
Come and save Deku!
An explosive quirk.
Found ya, damn villain!
Kacchan.
He's...
Bakugo!
Watch closely, brats!
This is the power of the man who's
going to be the number one hero!
It's over!
Kacchan!
D-Dammit!
Kacchan.
He has multiple quirks at his disposal.
And he can steal quirks too!
Is this All For One all over again?
All the more reason to crush him!
I've already seen these moves!
No way they're gonna stop me again!
Damn it! Where'd that come from?!
Move.
Move!
You just won't stop barking.
You're the one who's barking!
Damn Deku!
Detroit Smash!
Wh-What's happening now?
What's going on?
A blackout?
Well then.
I won't let you!
The fight ain't over yet!
Mister Deku.
Bakugo.
You heroes are so annoying.
Is he in pain?
But why?
Nine!
Hang in there, Nine!
The kid...
Understood.
It'd be wise not to struggle.
Don't worry. We're on your side.
Over here!
Tsu!
Ribbit!
Go after them.
Get that kid, no matter what—
Nine.
They can't leave the island.
You must rest for now.
Is this it?
I guess you'll live for today, brats!
Is he running away?
It'd be more accurate to say that he's letting us go.
Shit!
Don't!
It could be a trap.
We couldn't take him down
even when we had him outnumbered.
Going after him alone is too reckless.
But—
We have to make sure the islanders are safe.
It's part of our job as heroes.
You're using quirks way too much.
We don't know when they might attack us again.
If we don't do it now, there won't be any—
Your brain's already fried.
Here.
Thank you.
It's steaming so be careful.
One per person please!
There is plenty for everyone!
What happened to the villains?
Don't worry.
We'll take care of them and protect you all.
Good thing this island has a lot of vegetables.
What happened to the villain they caught?
Ah.
He's chained up in the basement boiler room.
But he refuses to talk no matter what.
Todoroki, how are Deku and the others doing?
They're still unconscious.
The doctors from the clinic
are doing everything they can.
Thanks for all your hard work.
I apologize.
We closed their wounds with our quirks
but I'm afraid that's all we could do.
We can't do anything for their broken bones.
They need to be taken to a hospital.
Can I try something?
Katsuma?
Katsuma's quirk has the power to reactivate cells.
We don't know if it could help with the wounds, but—
They got hurt trying to save us!
That's why.
We'd appreciate it, little one.
Thanks!
I have to save them.
No.
I will save them!
How is Nine doing?
He will be fine.
He'll be up again in a few hours.
Where's Mummy?
Not here either?
Don't tell me, the heroes...
No way.
Either way, we must stick to the plan.
It has to work, no matter what.
Why did you save me?
Join my cause.
Together, we'll destroy this society
that labeled you a monster and a villain.
We'll create a world ruled by the powerful.
You're joining the League of Villains?
Strictly speaking, I'm just participating in their quirk enhancing experiments.
They're just using you!
It's too dangerous!
It must be done.
We need even greater power than what we have.
We bet everything on you.
Don't you dare die on us.
You're compatible with All For One's quirk!
Now, you can steal eight more.
Along with your own,
you can use nine different powers!
The experiment was a success.
Our plan can finally move forward.
However, the side effects have gotten worse.
Using my quirks too much results in the
destruction of my body's cells and tissues.
That means—
Then what was the point of all this?!
I just need to steal a cell activation quirk.
And then,
we can create the world we want.
Katsuma, you should get some sleep.
I'm not done yet.
But,
I have to do this!
I can't give up.
Heroes never give up!
Mister Deku!
Bakugo!
Here's the current situation.
Electricity and communications are both destroyed.
We can't call for backup.
A while ago, I created a drone with a distress message.
We sent it out requesting for backup.
It'll take at least six hours to get
through and help will take even longer.
I don't think the villains will wait 'till then.
For now our highest priority
is to protect the islanders.
But how?
That villain managed to defeat even Midoriya and Bakugo!
The one we faced was really skilled and powerful too.
Yaomomo and Kaminari can't fight
for now since they overused their quirks.
And as far as we know,
there's still three of them out there.
If they attack us together, we won't stand a chance.
It'd help if we knew what they're after.
Yeah.
Then we could at least make a plan.
I'm going to steal your quirk.
Katsum—
I'm the one they're after.
What do you mean?
He said he wanted to steal my quirk!
Steal your quirk?
Doesn't that sound like All For One?
But now we know what their goal is!
If we just run away with the boy—
It's not gonna be that easy.
They're real villains.
If we run away, they could start
making threats about killing someone.
What should we do then?
Just hand me over to the villains!
Huh?
He said he wouldn't kill me.
It's fine if he takes my quirk.
If that's what it takes to save everyone.
Not gonna happen!
Deku?
Midoriya! Are you okay?
All thanks to Katsuma's quirk.
My quirk isn't good for hero stuff.
Cell activation.
A quirk that increases metabolism and speeds up healing.
I recovered so quickly thanks to that.
It is an incredible quirk, Katsuma. I'm so grateful!
Mister Deku.
We won't let anything scary happen to you.
That's exactly why we are here.
All we gotta do is crush those damn villains, right?
Bakugo!
Save people to win and win to save people.
If you both recognize each other
and focus on making one another stronger,
you will become the greatest heroes.
We'll definitely protect you two!
The villains are good as dead!
We'll save everyone on the island!
Obviously, we'll win!
Bakugo, Midoriya. I'm with you.
Me too! I'll protect the islanders no matter what.
We have to fight!
Guess there's no other way. I can't fix
Mr. Matsuda's battery if he's not around.
I'm in. Granny Sato's got a long life ahead of her.
I'm with you!
Me too.
Same!
Count me in!
Me too!
Yeah!
Let's fight!
Ribbit!
Alright! Let's do it.
Yeah. Let's do it!
I guess it can't be helped.
We're all heroes!
We'll overcome the impossible.
It's just like we always say.
Go beyond!
Plus Ultra!
Midoriya, what's the plan?
We know there are three of them.
If we use the castle ruins as our base,
the villains will have only one route.
When they get here, we'll separate them and use the terrain to our advantage.
Then we blast 'em to hell.
The islanders will be evacuated to the side of the cliff.
We'll personally guard Katsuma and Mahoro.
We should also secure our escape route.
How do we deal with
the one who has multiple quirks?
When Kacchan and I fought him,
he suddenly doubled over in pain.
It's possible that using all those
quirks is too much for his body.
That's why he's after Katsuma's cell activation quirk.
I see.
So we simply exhaust him.
We'll attack him in waves to make him use up his quirks.
Since he can steal quirks,
we'll attack from a distance as far as possible.
It's all good if we manage to defeat him.
And even if we can't, we just have
to hold them up until help arrives!
We just have to protect everyone.
You're wrong.
We're gonna beat 'em for sure.
Nine!
The target's in the mountain castle ruins.
Along with the heroes.
A defensive front?
Let's head straight toward our goal.
The one who'll become King,
doesn't need to rely on cheap tricks.
They're here. All three of them.
They're taking the route we predicted.
We are counting on you. Yaoyorozu, Aoyama.
Twenty seconds until they're on the spot.
Aoyama. Get your naval laser to maximum output!
Charging up.
1!
Can't Stop Twinkling: Super Nova!
Plus Ultra!
This is it!
I made these using the last of my lipids!
It's my final attack!
Terrible aim—
What?!
Phase one... complete.
I can't... anymore.
It worked! They're separated!
Yes!
We've got them right where we want.
All according to plan so far.
We'll protect everyone no matter what!
Tape Shot: Trident!
Release!
Uraraka!
Sero!
We'll make the villain
wear out his quirk!
Take this!
So, they split us up.
Dammit!
That was close!
Ashido, leave the rest to me.
This is my territory.
Cheeky brat!
They actually managed to split us up.
All right!
Just as planned.
Not quite.
Hey now, that was cold.
We meet again.
You better back off. Because today,
I'm fighting for real.
And we're no different!
Now that the islanders are safe, we can go all out!
We will stop you.
Recipro Burst!
Let's finish this in ten minutes!
Got it!
Right!
Bring it on!
Dammit!
We can't even slow him down.
How about this!
It's time for the real thing!
Yeah.
Sero! Uraraka!
Mineta!
Everything's set!
You can do this, Uraraka!
Plus Ultra!
Go, Mineta!
Super Grape Rush!
Take that, and that, and that, and that!
And that, and that, and that, and that, and that!
That was the real thing!
Way to go!
W-We did it—
Are you alright?
Serves you right.
We sealed you up.
He escaped the trap!
He's going after Uraraka and the others!
Is that all?
Aoyama!
Yaomomo!
Now, while he's distracted.
The plan must—
It is no use.
Playtime's over.
You're still alive?
If you're gonna sleep-talk, then sleep and die!
Bakugo has joined the fight!
Midoriya!
Take care of Katsuma and Mahoro!
Mister Deku.
Deku.
We'll defend this place 'till the end!
If I can't even protect those two,
I can't call myself a hero!
St. Louis Smash!
It doesn't have to be at full power.
I just have to make him use his quirk!
X-Catapult!
Not bad.
We're just getting started.
And now we'll kill you.
What'd you mean my territory?
Go on, say it again!
Is that all you've got?
She's faster than I anticipated.
I need an opening, even for an instant.
How pathetic!
Black Abyss: Sabbath!
Now!
Acid Shot!
This is it!
How dare you!
Ashido!
You fiend!
Th-This is...
I won't let you get in Nine's way!
Tokoyami!
Dark Shadow is—
Pay attention to what's in front of you!
I'm trying to!
It's useless!
Red Gauntlet!
That tickles.
Didn't I tell you? You don't stand a chance—
M-My body won't...
There's a reason why we were using
the same attacks over and over.
My legs and Kirishima's hands were
coated in a toxic mucus made by Asui.
Just call me Tsu.
Resign yourself, old man.
Don't act so insolent.
I'll show you
the reason why they call me a monster!
He got bigger!
That form, it's a lot like Amajiki.
Dammit.
Let's go, Tsu!
That's where Iida and the others are!
Are they in trouble? We should help—
You can't!
We must protect Katsuma and Mahoro at all costs.
Mister Deku.
Bakugo.
I won't let you!
Sero!
I'll make him float!
Uraraka!
I-I'm okay.
Bastard.
How dare you?!
He's pushing us back.
At this rate, Katsuma and Mahoro will...
Dammit.
This is...
This is it! He's reached his limit!
That's some crazy power.
We can't even get close to him.
My Recipro will be done soon.
Make an opening for me.
I need to get close to him.
And then what?
I have a plan.
Alright.
This will be our final attack!
Iida, distract him with your Recipro Burst.
Doesn't this remind you of Kamino?
Yeah.
I'll take whatever he throws at us
and make sure you get close to him!
Thanks!
Unbreakable!
Kirishima!
Go!
Increase your body's temperature to its limit!
What he taught me with fire, I'll do it with ice!
Todoroki!
Colder, to its limit!
Freeze!
That's right, hibernate for a while.
D-Did we do what we needed to?
Midoriya. Bakugo.
Kacchan, let's attack in waves!
Don't tell me what to do!
I-If I could only take the cell activation quirk.
I've gotta get a solid hit in!
Then I wouldn't have to hold back!
Mister Deku.
Bakugo.
Mister Deku!
Bakugo!
Cell activation?
That's right.
However, my quirk can only
manipulate the cells in type A blood.
It's not very useful for people with other blood types.
Mr. Shimano, do you have a family?
A daughter and a son who live on Nabu Island.
That's pretty far but Nabu Island
is still within the culprit's range.
Nabu Island
Excuse me.
What is it?
A fishing boat near Kyushu just received a distress message.
Villains have attacked Nabu Island. They're requesting help.
It's the suspect who's been taking people's quirks!
What?!
Send a rescue team to Nabu Island immediately!
Oh, and contact U.A. High School.
U.A.? But why?
Because they have students there. As part of
the project the safety commission sponsored,
Class 1-A from the hero course was sent to Nabu Island.
Shoji, take Katsuma and Mahoro and get out of here.
We're counting on you.
Got it.
We won't let him get through.
Yeah.
Found you.
Heartbeat Distortion!
Tornado Tail Dance!
Ojiro!
We need to evacuate.
Get away.
Run!
Both of you, run!
Hurry!
Go!
Katsuma, run away.
S-Sis!
I'll be fine, just run!
Stay away!
Don't lay a hand on my brother!
I said stay away!
Sis!
If you want her to live, then come over here.
No! Run away!
Run!
Help me make my wish come true.
Run... away.
Katsuma!
Stop it!
I'll protect you!
I will save you, sis!
Smash!
Sorry, I'm late.
Mister Deku.
You really gave it your all, Katsuma.
You're amazing!
Bakugo! You're alive!
I told you, didn't I?
I'm the man who will surpass All Might
and become the number one hero!
Take Mahoro and run.
Right!
C'mon, sis!
How could you possibly have avoided my lightning?
You've stopped us with that before!
That's why,
we used that thunder idiot as a lightning rod.
W-Wasn't that... a bit too much?
Smash!
Die!
Over here!
It can't...
It can't end like this!
This can't be the end!
Like hell I'd let it end like this!
A tornado!
Damn, he can even control the weather!
What should we do?
Katsuma and Mahoro are still here.
On top of that, everyone who was
evacuated could be in danger too.
Is he planning to destroy the entire island?
We've got to stop him!
One For All.
100%!
I'll blast this villain with everything I've got!
Detroit Smash!
Howitzer Impact!
Mister Deku!
Sis!
The entrance!
Sato!
I can hold this! Get everyone back!
E-Even 100% wasn't enough.
D-Dammit.
Even after I lowered myself to fight alongside Deku.
It's no use.
You simply don't have the strength to defeat me.
You won't survive the new world that I'll create.
What new world?
One ruled by power.
The strong will rule over the weak in my utopia.
Same old crap.
It won't matter if you're a villain or a hero.
Everyone will be equal before power.
That's how a true superhuman society should be.
How selfish can you be?!
It's never gonna work!
If you intend to get in my way,
then you'll have to be eliminated.
Think.
What would All Might do?
I won't let it end like this!
Think!
I won't lose!
Mister Deku!
Bakugo!
Please don't give up!
There you are.
Kacchan.
There's still a way.
It's the only way we can stop him.
My quirk was passed on to me like a sacred torch.
The power to transfer power.
K-Kacchan!
Heroes have a lot to protect, you know.
That's why I won't lose!
Deku!
A real hero will always find a way for justice to be served!
A way to protect them.
A way to victory.
There's only one way!
What?
After this, will you still be able to use your power?
I don't know, but...
All Might still protected us with
its embers even after he transferred it to me.
What did you do?!
With double One For All.
We'll save everyone!
We'll beat you and win!
Why won't you weaklings just die already?!
It's the end of your dream, Deku.
It's alright, there's no other way.
I'm sure that All Might would agree if it's you.
You knew our secret and kept it to yourself.
We've always wanted to be the same hero.
So if it's you...
All Might is so awesome!
He's a super cool hero!
No matter how difficult it is, in the end the heroes
always win!
No matter how hard it is to save someone, heroes always
save them with a smile!
Don't make me laugh!
Detroit Smash!
What the...
What is this power?
I won't let you stop me from fulfilling my dream!
Kacchan, let's go!
Stop telling me what to do!
Get out of my way!
This is it.
The last one.
My last.
My final
Smash!
Farewell, One For All.
Thank you.
Are you okay, Tokoyami?
Hawks? But how...
I'm here to help, and I brought someone with me.
All Might.
Young Midoriya.
I'm sorry I was late.
K-Kacchan?
Always putting others before yourself.
He's hurt badly but he'll be fine. His life's not in danger.
Thank goodness.
I might have pushed him too far.
You made him do something?
All Might.
I transferred it...
One For All to Kacchan.
One For All?!
If we both hadn't used One For All,
there's no way we could've saved everyone.
There's no way we could've defeated the villain.
That's why I don't regret it.
But still, I'm sorry.
You chose me as your successor.
You told me I can become a hero.
I just wanted to protect everyone, no matter the cost.
Young Midoriya.
I'm so sorry, All Might.
Please forgive me.
I had to...
I never regretted transferring One For All to you either.
You used it well.
You've cultivated this crystallization of power
with your courage and made it even stronger.
One For All.
Young Bakugo must've passed out
before the transfer was complete.
No, that's not it.
You were risking your life to protect.
You were risking your life to prevail.
One For All did something miraculous.
Master, and all those who came before.
Thank you very much!
What are you planning, Tomura Shigaraki?
So you're alive after all.
Shigaraki.
Did you have a good life?
I'm just getting started. I'll keep fighting.
Don't worry, I will fulfill your dream.
There can only be one true king.
That's right, just one.
Goodnight, Nine.
You did well.
Iogi Heights
It hurts!
What the hell happened to me?!
Undergoing
Treatment
Kacchan doesn't remember anything
about me transferring One For All to him.
Undergoing
Treatment
Somehow, One For All still resides inside of me.
Nabu Port Terminal
Daddy!
Mahoro, Katsuma!
Later, Katsuma and Mahoro reunited with their father.
We were able to protect everyone on the island with very few wounded.
The public security commission's project was suspended.
But we stayed on the island a while longer,
to help with the reconstruction as best we could.
And then, finally, it was time for us to go home.
Are we gonna leave without saying anything?
I know, right?
We wouldn't want to interfere with the reconstruction.
Well, I guess this is cooler.
Yeah, very hero-like.
Yep!
I can't believe it's time for us to leave already.
Yeah, whatever.
Are you really gonna leave
without saying goodbye to those brats?
There are things I wanted to say.
But it's okay. I'm sure they already know how I feel.
Hey!
Mister Deku!
Bakugo!
Everyone!
Thank you for protecting us all!
Mister Deku!
I'll get stronger!
I'll get strong enough to protect daddy and sis!
Just you wait!
And then, I'll become a hero as cool as you and Bakugo!
Make sure you don't forget those words, brat.
Katsuma!
You can do it!
You can become a hero!
I'll see you at U.A. one day!
Let's go! The time for beginnings is at hand
It's goodbye to all those tear-filled nights
Let's raise a banner for the world's glory, up in the sky
If you start walking, the winds will blow your way for sure
Banners aflutter, let's advance
Let's go! Begin this story of awakening
No more hesitation
Advance this story of dawning
Even further beyond
Walking down, blind and dazzled
By the countless banners at the end of a headlong plunge
Not a single one like the other, yet each one raised with pride
We're neither flattering nor are we playful
We're just travelers headed the same way
Hey! Let's start building up this glory we fell in love with
Let's go together, walking side by side along with this parade
Even further beyond
Mornings may birth shadows and hope may grow ill
But don't stop believing in the here and now
March on with the resolve that shines in each of us
Hey! Let's start building this story of freedom
No more hesitation
Even if we're not alike, let's march on together with this parade of dawn
'Till the day the world ends, let's keep raising the banner
Light up one another, transcending even destiny
Even further beyond
We will go beyond