Go ahead, they said.
So I opened my eyes.
I was inside the ocean.
I reached my hand out together with my mom.
They followed me
no matter where I went.
It's a memory from my childhood.
Is it the song?
No, these whales are answering the song.
The dolphins started migrating in response.
It's a new type of song that
has never been recorded before.
It's distant, but it's getting closer little by little.
The story of the origin of the stars,
of the children of the stars,
and the birth of the stars.
From the star, from the stars.
The sea is the mother.
It's about time!
CHILDREN OF THE SEA
I can fly through the sky!
Nice shot!
Let's keep running!
You're movin' good, Ruka!
Of course I'm movin' good.
It's the beginning of summer vacations.
In summer, my whole body feels light!
Nice shoot!
Nice shot, Ruka!
Nice, Ruka!
Yes!
Ruka, you're in awesome shape today!
Amazing!
I don't trust her and her explosive energy.
What?
Whoops, I'm sorry.
You're trying too hard, kiddo.
What happened? Is it your nose?
Ruka's elbow hit her in the face during that last shot.
That was on purpose, wasn't it?
Her nose might be broken.
Bring her to the infirmary.
Ruka, you went too far this time.
Yeah, I know she tripped you and all, but still.
But...
Ruka.
Ruka!
Come to the staff room.
What a scene.
And it's only the first day of vacations.
You're a real trouble maker, ya know?
How many times has it been?
Against your teammates? Your opponents?
Why did you hurt her like that?
C'mon, answer me!
She is the one... who started...
So it's not your fault, then?
That's not... what I meant.
So you're sayin' it's her fault?
All right, I've heard enough.
Anyway, I might have to get her to the hospital.
You can go home.
Okay.
I need to go to the infirmary too...
Ah, one more thing, Ruka.
If you don't intend to apologize,
don't bother comin' back!
It's just the first day
but I guess my summer vacation
is already over.
I can't fly anymore.
What are you doing this vacation?
Celebrating Bon Festival.
That's so cool.
I want to go on a trip!
I know, right?
I'll take care of the team stuff before I go.
Your holidays sure are packed!
They sure are.
Lucky you! We're not going anywhere.
We're just visiting the family grave.
Wanna go watch a movie?
Yeah, totally!
I'm coming too!
Let's go together.
I wonder if she's doing all right.
But...
It's been so long...
I miss the aquarium.
Last station, Enoshima.
Wasn't that amazing?
Mom, I wanna go there!
It's the Wonder Aquarium!
WONDER           AQUARIUM
Enokura Aquarium presents
Come visit the Wonder Aquarium!
Tonight's the first night event, do come and visit!
Dad, let me see!
Let's go!
Bye-bye.
Thank you.
Here you go.
Oh, thanks.
Wait, excuse me.
Aren't you Mr. Azumi's daughter?
What? Ruka's here?
You recognized her?
She's got your eyes, and you often
brought her around when she was little.
Why is she here?
I'm a bit tied up right now.
Tell her to meet me behind the big aquarium.
Yeah, thank you.
Chief, the sardines are here.
Ah, okay.
This way.
I'll take you to where your dad works.
Sure.
Thank you.
Go through here and you will find him easily.
This way.
Be sure to check out the Wonder Aquarium later.
Excuse me...
Dad?
Anyone here?
Ouch!
What?
Who's there?
Summer vacation...
Is it a break in the summer?
He jumped in!
Really?
Ruka?
He's flying.
My name is Umi. What's yours?
My name is...
Your name is?
Ruka.
So you're Ruka!
Ruka!
Fascinating, isn't he?
Dad!
He was raised in the ocean by a pod of dugongs.
Dugongs?
My long, long, long summer vacation is about to begin.
"Dugongs, the inspiration for mermaids."
Smells like dad.
Ten years ago, he was discovered swimming
with a pod of dugongs off the coast of Philippines.
Actually, there was another boy with him.
His skin is extremely sensitive to dryness.
Probably 'cause he's been living in the ocean.
They were left with us at the aquarium for research.
By the way, why'd you come all this way?
No reason.
Entertainment News!
A gigantic humpback whale was spotted off the coast of Manhattan.
The reason is still unknown but marine specialists are looking into it.
So Masaaki left without telling me again.
Why'd you go there anyway?
Hey, Ruka!
I'm heading out!
A will-o'-the-wisp is coming.
Circle round!
I thought I just saw...
I'm sorry.
I apologize.
But it wasn't even my fault.
Ow.
What am I doing...
playing hide-and-seek at school?
Ruka! I found you!
Umi?
All right, shall we go now?
Go where?
A will-o'-the-wisp is coming. Let's go see it.
A will-o'-the-wisp?
Yeah.
I wanted to see it with Sora but he can't come along.
Sora?
My elder brother. He's in the hospital right now.
Oh.
Then I remembered you, so I came to get you.
What's a will-o'-the-wisp?
They shine and fly across the sky.
Let's go see them together.
Tell me, what is this place?
It's the Shrine of Harvest.
And this?
That's a Jizo Buddhist statue.
Ah, I know this one!
That's an ice cream store.
Yummy!
Why'd I have to...
Why me?
Why'd he come for me?
I wonder if he asked himself why.
The sound of the waves is getting louder.
It'll be dark soon.
Is a will-o'-the-wisp really coming?
I wonder if he's just pulling my leg.
Maybe he is.
I'm sure he is.
It's getting dark so I'm—
Here it is!
And another one!
What on earth?
They were so bright and huge...
Spectacular!
What were those? Comets?
Asteroids? Shooting stars? Meteorites?
Will-o'-the-wisps.
They're will-o'-the-wisps.
Whatever it was, it was amazing!
How'd you know they were coming?
I knew because they wanted me to find them.
They were shining so bright
because they wanted us to see them.
Insects and animals that shine,
do it because they want to be found.
Oh, I see.
I was so happy that Umi found me at school today.
Hey, do you think they'll show up again?
I wanted someone to find me!
That was breathtaking.
Thanks for bringing me here, Umi.
No Visitors
Sora
Sora! Jim is here to pick you up.
Okay.
Meteorite Crash
How are they doing?
They seem distracted.
The seals were loud last night.
Do you think it might be due to that?
The meteorite?
There have been sightings of humpback whales
near the estimated impact site of the meteorite.
Jim, it's just as you predicted.
That's good to hear.
I am sending you a recording of their song.
Please do.
Excuse me.
Aren't you Azumi's daughter?
What was that music you just played?
Ah, you're referring to the song.
The song?
It was a whale's song.
They sing songs as they travel.
Sound travels much farther in water than in the air.
By singing, whales can communicate across vast distances.
A whale's song is an extremely complex wave of information.
Us humans have never been able to
communicate even half of what we're thinking.
Perhaps whales are able to put their sights and
emotions into a form that can be shared by everyone.
A form shared by everyone.
They don't need words to communicate.
I wonder if another will show up tonight.
What's that sound?
Wait, is someone there?
Umi?
No.
Is that Sora?
There's that sound again.
It's the sound of sand and rocks hitting under the waves.
It usually gets covered up by the sound of the waves.
The edge of the water is quite eloquent.
You can hear all the information carried by the ocean.
If you can tell them apart, there's a lot you can know.
You're Ruka, right?
You know who I am, right?
You should know.
Sora?
You're boring.
Such a simple girl, so predictable.
You came here to see Umi, right?
He happens to be offshore right now.
Too bad for you.
But you're not well...
You shouldn't...
I'm fine, it was just an examination.
You're free to be interested in Umi,
but is he interested in you?
I don't think Umi is—
I don't care! It's not like I came here for Umi!
I just wanted to see the will—
I mean, the shooting stars again tonight.
Umi has me already, so you can go home now.
I was just about to!
I don't know what you're up to here but—
The song.
I can hear a song I've never heard before.
Song? You mean the whale song?
Earlier today, when I heard the recording,
I saw whales and those shooting stars inside my mind.
Also, some kind of celebration. Something like birth.
Yeah? What about it?
N-Nothing!
So you're lonely,
and want me to play with you, young lady?
What a jerk!
I can't believe a guy like that is related to Umi.
He's so annoying!
He seemed as if he'd disappear like a ghost.
Wait. It's just you, Sora?
It felt like Ruka was here too.
She was until a little while ago.
You were right, she does have the same smell.
Let's look into her a little bit more.
How are things underwater?
Looks like a bunch of them are gathering.
Can you hear it?
Sure can.
From the star, from the stars.
The sea is the mother.
Let's start with our deductions.
Sora is definitively human.
His eyeballs, cardiopulmonary functions, muscles, and bone density,
are all the results of adapting to life underwater.
But, we didn't find any luminescent elements in his skin tissues.
So there's no physical reason he would emit light—
False killer whales?
Ruka, sorry to keep you waiting.
You sure you want to do this?
Yep!
The water sure is cold in here.
Don't put your fingers in there!
That's the shark tank.
Yep, I know!
Masaaki?
I'm sorry, but who are you?
Ah, Ms. Kanako! It's been a while.
Who is that?
Mr. Azumi's wife.
Oh, Ruka's mother?
Hey.
Mr. Azumi is out for a workshop today.
Really?
Yeah.
Okay then, where's Ruka?
She's probably somewhere in the building.
I see, thanks.
Don't mind me, I'll look for her myself.
Ms. Kanako used to work here,
but she's been away for a while.
Oh, she's legendary around here, right?
Ms. Kanako is coming this way?
Hey, kids!
What's up?
My mom! She's a pain!
If you wanna hide, I know the perfect place.
This way!
There it is.
Ah.
Let's hide in here!
This boat belongs to the aquarium.
They'll never think to look for us here.
Sorry.
Hey, this moves.
Eh?
Ready to set sail!
Let's go!
The ship is setting sail!
It's unbelievable that you know how to drive it.
I don't.
What?
I'm just messing around a bit.
Are we gonna be okay?
Watch out! Incoming!
You almost crashed!
I was sure he'd dodge us.
The port! It's so far away.
But this feels so nice.
Hey, let's go and see the whales!
Yeah, let's do that.
The whales?
It stopped.
Eh?
Not a peep out of it.
It won't move?
Guess not.
What are we gonna do all the way out here?!
There's not much we can do.
No idea.
W-What are we gonna do now?
How are we gonna get back?!
I don't recall you ever trying to stop me.
Did you ever tell me to stop or go back?
No you didn't. You were enjoying it yourself.
So don't go blaming it on others.
Since we grew up in the ocean,
our skin starts to burn without water.
And we have trouble breathing.
My body is more used to it.
But our life expectancy is still pretty short.
It's short?
Yep.
They're doing researching to see if they can extend it.
Hey, something's heading this way!
You should come too, Ruka!
But the water here is really deep, right?
There's no way I can do this!
Absolutely no way!
It's so deep.
I can't do this!
What's that?
Whale sharks?
I can't hang on!
Geez.
Don't jump in if you can't swim.
I can swim!
You were drowning.
No, that's 'cause—
Because you couldn't swim.
I can!
The whale sharks are gone
but there's something behind them.
Ah, you're right.
Something's moving.
Oh, a school of fish?
Wonderful.
They're chasing after that group of whale sharks.
The whale sharks' patterns,
they were glowing in the ocean.
Just like before.
Like the ghost at the aquarium.
It was glowing?
Yeah.
When I was little, I saw it turn into light and disappear.
We saw it too.
The ghost?
Yeah. We called it "the Ghost of the Sea."
We saw the same thing?
And the song?
Didn't you hear the whale song back then?
No, I only heard it in the recording the other day.
What does it mean?
There's gonna be a huge celebration,
a birth festival, somewhere out in the ocean.
We've been traveling all over the world with Jim,
trying to understand what links it to us.
Whales are said to sing of the coming of this event.
They're looking for a guest for the festival.
A guest?
Sora's examination reports don't show anything unusual.
Yet his condition seems to be deteriorating faster than ever.
Umi however, has adapted well to life on land.
They might seem similar but they're quite different.
And about the meteors,
seems like they didn't make it to the Earth's surface after all.
I guess they burned up.
Professor Anglade is out to
collect them, but I'm sure it's a lost cause.
However, the fish all seem to be
gathering around that part of the ocean.
And then there is that unfamiliar whale song.
All these events are probably omens of the coming festival.
Then we need to hurry, or else Sora—
What is it, Sora?
Is it here?
It's the false killer whales!
Sora!
Umi!
Something's glowing.
Umi? Sora!
Sora!?
The ocean just happened to be calm and a boat passed by!
What were you thinking?!
Are you even listening, Ruka?
What were you doing out there by yourself?
You even lied to me about going to practice.
Ruka! Where have you been going everyday?
To see Masaaki?
That's none of your business!
None of your business.
The poor thing was thrown back by the sea.
How did this happen?
Is it already dead?
Excuse me!
I'm sorry!
What...
Is that...
Oh, Ruka?
Dad!
Strange, isn't it?
It's a relative of the Megamouth.
Megamouth?
Yeah, it's a type of shark that lives in the abyss.
As do these other fish.
How'd they end up here?
All these fish washed up here, and Sora is still missing.
What a mess!
Wait, Sora hasn't come back?
Nope, Jim is out looking for him.
What about Umi? How is he doing?
Not good. He's probably worried about Sora.
Hey, wait.
A typhoon's approaching! Stay home!
A ribbonfish too?
It's Umi!
Hey, Umi!
Umi? Get up.
Umi.
Talk to me!
His heartbeat!
No! He's not breathing.
What should I do? I don't know how to do CPR!
Ruka, what were you doing?
You idiot!
What were you doing out here?
I know where Sora is!
The waves told me.
The waves did?
This typhoon carries the smell of the sea
where I was born, and the smell of Sora!
The typhoon?
Umi's hand...
is so warm.
I must protect him.
The typhoon just changed course and is heading this way.
First the deep-sea fish and now a typhoon?
Hey, isn't that Mr. Azumi's daughter?
Oh, it's Ruka!
Don't go up to the beach, you guys!
It's not safe!
They don't even have an umbrella.
We're closed due
to the typhoon.
I'm telling you, she isn't here.
Washed away?
Nah, someone spotted them in town so that's unlikely.
I'll let you know as soon as—
Yeah, all right, all right.
Why'd they have to go out right in the middle of a typhoon?
Memories, time, and spirits cross paths in a typhoon.
Time is running out faster than I'd imagined.
Much faster.
Running out?
Bye-bye!
Are we getting closer?
Yep.
This way!
The sea!
Hey now, you found us already?
Sora is out for a swim at the moment.
I found him out in the middle of the ocean.
The one who brought him here was me.
And then,
you brought Umi here.
Or rather,
Umi brought you here, following the typhoon.
Yeah.
In that case, you better be careful of Umi.
Consider this your warning.
Hey! Catch us something for dinner, okay?
Well, make yourself at home.
I'll call Jim and let him know you're here.
Wait, you know each other?
Of course.
I'm an oceanographer who happens to be Jim's assistant.
Well, I was.
Since we have an unexpected guest,
I guess I'll take my summer vacation.
Summer vacation?
Ruka!
Sora.
A dugong.
Wonderful!
So you're saying that the day of the festival is drawing near?
Yes.
What's the location?
I believe the boys from the sea will guide us to it.
Studying the proceedings of this festival in person
will greatly advance our knowledge of the oceans.
According to our intel, your assistant Anglade
has abducted these boys that you believe are the key.
He's just coordinating with them,
and I can contact him at any point.
But then we won't know when the festival will happen!
In that case,
Anglade can be the one to guide us when the time comes.
Do you expect us to trust him?!
There's no need to worry.
We can track the location of his ship.
What slackness! Mobilize the fleet!
Please wait.
How much time do we have left?
Umi.
Sora.
Awesome!
The sky and the sea are all red.
Your eyes are red too, you know.
Here, look.
Hey, guys!
Did you catch any food?
It's about time we started cooking!
Ah, I almost forgot!
The sea isn't red due to the sunset alone.
See that?
What is it?
You will find out once night falls.
Caught something!
Look!
Let's dig in.
Sora, how are you feeling?
Not too bad, actually.
Although I feel worse after each examination.
To understand our origin and fate,
I went through numerous experiments and examinations.
But neither the X-Rays nor the MRIs showed anything unusual.
I can feel that my body is changing,
but the scientific eye can't see
what's really going on inside our bodies.
All we humans can see
is just a tiny fraction of everything that exists in the world.
As our ability to observe the universe improved,
we discovered something called dark matter,
which can't be observed by any means.
The sum of its substance is at least
ten times more than that of normal matter.
In other words, more than 90% of the universe's
mass is made up of this matter we can't identify.
So, almost all of it?
Yeah.
It's like we're not seeing anything at all.
The world is full of things we can't see.
The universe is far more complex
than what our eyes can perceive.
I think the universe is a lot like people.
Inside each person, tiny fragments of memories are scattered around.
Until by some chance, several fragments get connected to each other.
They form a larger memory, which draws in more fragments.
And they merge together, and grow.
That's what it means to think and feel, right?
And that's just like—
Yes, that's right.
That's just like how a star or a galaxy is born.
The universe and people...
Where'd Sora and Anglade go?
Umi?
You're burning up!
Please be okay.
When I was little,
my mom used to do this to comfort me.
Hush, hush, go to sleep.
Rest, my little one.
I just adore you more than anything.
I forget the rest.
Anglade's yacht is gone.
Huh?
The water is glowing?
The sea sparkle—
Huh?!
Sora!
They're known as sea sparkle.
Sea sparkle?
That's what caused the red color of the ocean.
It's a type of plankton which glows when it's agitated.
Impressive.
They can make a red sea glow blue.
Hey, Sora?
Now, pay attention.
The ocean is separated into different masses of water.
You can ride those masses and glide.
Beautiful.
Can I do that too?
Amazing.
If I keep going...
If I keep going on like this,
I might just swim all the way to the stars.
The Milky Way surrounds us
from both the sky and the waves.
And tomorrow is the new moon.
It's like a cradle for life.
The entire ocean is bustling around this
meteorite that is believed to have burned up.
Why do you think that is?
Perhaps this world we live in is merely a dream.
Maybe it was breathed into life by the
countless shellfish that live in the abyss.
Where did Umi and Sora really come from?
Who are they, really?
Where are they headed now?
And where are we headed?
I'm sure those two view the world very differently than we do.
As if from a different place and time.
They live in a world beyond our imagination.
And yet, they've appeared right before us.
The only thing we can do for them,
is not to impede the natural course of their journey.
If you really want to help them,
protect them from those who think they know better.
It's almost time for the festival to begin.
And the guest has undoubtedly been chosen.
There's no need to worry.
Umi's body is going through a transformation.
It happened to me too.
And it'll happen again, when the time finally comes.
It's so beautiful.
They shine because they want to be found.
Umi told me that, but...
their beautiful light somehow makes them seem lonely.
Maybe sad is the right word?
Maybe because they'll eventually fade away.
They shine even as they're fading away.
Oh, I was just thinking out loud.
Don't mind me.
Wait, what did I just swallow?
The meteorite. I entrust it to you.
Remember this.
If Umi ever needs the meteorite,
cut it out of your stomach and give it to him.
What the—
Sora?
I'm afraid... that time really has run out.
Sora!
I thought it'd happen on the night of the full moon.
Both Jim and Anglade will be caught off guard.
Watch carefully now.
So you'll have some data when Umi's time comes.
Sora, wait!
The dugongs this afternoon must have come to get me.
It happened earlier than I expected.
Too early.
What's this sound?
What's happening?
I'm starting to wonder if Umi lost his voice.
Yeah, he hasn't spoken since he got back.
All right, the show is about to start, time to get out.
Well, at least she's back home safe and sound.
That's all you've gotta say?
I didn't mean it like that.
It's fine. Just what I expected.
Ruka doesn't wanna stay at home 'cause I'm a drunk.
You two are similar in that way.
It's the two of you who're similar.
You both want people to know how you're feeling,
but you don't know how to express it.
So you get frustrated and lash out at everyone, right?
You're both just making things awkward and complicated.
I finally get it.
I had no idea how I could help you, until now.
We're all awkward and complicated.
Even you.
Maybe I haven't done my best, but I wanna make things right.
If you'll give me the chance.
I think we belong together,
living under the same roof as a family.
You finally made it, Jim.
Yeah.
We didn't make it in time.
Sora is already gone.
At that moment, I heard the sound transmitted across the waters.
698.45 hertz.
The sound of a dying star.
When I got back to the shore, I found Umi with
a fever and Ruka lying on the beach in a trance.
Do you think Sora is dead?
I don't know.
It must be the festival that Dede spoke of.
In the end,
there was nothing we could've done for him.
But it's strange that I can still sense Sora's presence.
I need to look deeper into the sky.
Ruka.
Somewhere deep inside me, a whirlpool is swirling.
What's going on?
What's happened to them?
Is there something out in the ocean?
At the ocean?
Look! It's a whale!
What is it? A whale?
Mom, what is that?
Chief! A huge whale's been spotted!
A whale?
It's huge!
It's a humpback.
Your eyes are focused on a world far beyond this place.
I need to get there, no matter what.
Lucky for you, I'm a shepherd of the seas.
Hop aboard.
Ah, the wind is great.
The currents too.
We have a good chance of catching up to that whale.
This whale song, I've heard it before.
It's searching for its guest.
It's the song of the stars.
The song of the stars?
"From the star, from the stars."
"The sea is the mother."
"Gather every star you can and drop them in the sea."
"Cradled by the waves, they'll be put back to sleep."
I finally remember the lullaby that mom used to sing to me.
The wind sings along with you.
The whales sing the song of the stars and
the wind carries the memories of the sea.
We've taken the messages from those memories,
and passed them down as songs and poems.
But there's only so much wind you can capture with words.
Just like these sails.
This instrument is just a way to communicate with the wind, the memories of the sea, and the emotions we can't express.
I can hear a soft voice carried by the wind.
These memories come to us when we least expect it.
Memories of someone's life, of their past and future.
A pod of false killer whales!
They are all headed in the same direction as us.
In that case—
Crap!
Huh?
Why did I dive in?
I lost track of Umi.
What is it?
Are you trying to tell me something?
I know everything that Sora is feeling
because I can feel it too.
Ruka.
The song is coming!
Umi?
It's coming straight at you!
Unbelievable!
I've never heard the song this loud before!
It's as if the entire ocean...
The entire ocean has started gathering together.
Isn't this a bit of an overkill?
It's just the usual protocol.
It's a lot farther from the location we predicted.
I understand.
I assure you it's the center of the festival,
where all the answers will be revealed.
Well done, Jim.
Looks like we'll have the best seats in the house.
Well then, best of luck to you all.
I'll be going my own way.
Is there nothing else I can do for them?
All I wanted was to buy them more time.
That's why we started this research.
However, things got out of hand with the experiments and they ended up becoming its victims.
You know what Dede told me?
To protect them from those who thought they knew better.
Those who believe that humans are superior to everything.
Would this be enough to protect them?
Jim!
Umi and Ruka have gone missing.
You know where they are, don't you?
You have to take us to them, please.
Take us to Ruka.
Little fish.
Go on.
Your home's that way.
Of course.
Creatures from the sea can't survive on this side.
Umi! Are you all right?
Umi!
We have to get you back in the water.
Wait.
Which side does Umi belong to?
Umi! Where are you?
Umi?
What's that?
This creature.
It has been here all alone for a very long time.
Were you watching it all?
Incredible.
Even in a place so deep and devoid of light, there is life.
All the memories from every creature in the sea are here.
Sora?
Ruka.
This is where your role ends.
You did well.
My role?
Yes, the meteorite has awakened.
What'll happen now that it's awakened?
It'll become the eye of a tremendous whirlpool.
Stick around if you want to see it.
Maybe one day it'll all come together.
If you can keep your eyes open till the end.
Sora.
You're not really Sora, are you?
Didn't I tell you?
The meteorite converges all memories together.
This memory is taken from someone you've known.
It's a part of the meteorite and it's a part of you.
Now, go ahead and close your eyes.
Slowly and gently.
Just like that.
The sky and the sea are becoming one.
And the festival of life is about to begin.
Sing now. Sing of the joy of being born.
It's your lullaby, can you hear it?
The song has already begun.
The universe and all its creatures are singing in unison.
You're annoying as always.
The universe is a lifeform.
The ocean is its womb.
The meteorites fertilize it.
It's a festival of conception!
Those who have witnessed this
celebration have composed a song for it.
From the star, from the stars.
The sea is the mother.
And now the song continues.
The people are her bosom.
Heaven is the playground.
The real festival is finally beginning!
I wanna see!
I see it.
Am I the universe?
Hush, hush, go to sleep.
This lullaby...
Rest, my little one.
Mom used to sing it to me.
I just adore you more than anything.
My mom,
she lives within me.
Is that Umi?
Umi!
Umi.
Wait, Umi!
No, don't!
You can't!
Umi, no!
It shines because it wants to be found.
That's Umi's light!
Umi!
Hey, Umi?
Where are you?
Good and evil.
The universe is held together by balancing opposing forces.
All things can indeed be observed from two different perspectives.
Just like the differences between aquatic and terrestrial beings.
But are we truly different?
I mean, all lifeforms are made up of the same matter.
Matter that came from outer space.
Every one of us is comprised of it.
The universe is a lot like people.
If we're all made up of the same substance,
we're not just similar, we are exactly alike.
The sun, the sea and man.
Sora, Umi, and me.
And every single thing here on Earth.
If I were to go into outer space,
I'm sure it would look just like the ocean.
Umi!
Did you just...
say goodbye?
Umi!
Where are you going?
Wait...
Umi!
Umi, no!
Wait for me!
Take me with you.
I just...
I just want to be...
with you forever!
Ruka?
Ruka!
Hang in there, Ruka!
We've got you.
Ruka.
C'mon, let's go!
Move it!
I think I was just about your age,
back when I met a beautiful boy from the sea.
The children of the sea appear to us
in secret and whisper the stories of their truth.
They tell us where we came from,
where we're headed and our reason for being.
They give us hints to unlock
the secrets of the world in many forms.
Like the goddess of the whale, or boys who slip through time.
They communicate with us
through the messages carried by the wind.
The universe conceals itself in many forms.
Even in a little story that fits in the palm of your hand.
My own...
My own story.
I...
I don't understand anything.
I just wanna see them one more time.
I wanted to ask...
Why me?
I'm not—
You're perfect just as you are.
Believe in Umi and Sora.
And most importantly, believe in yourself.
The sky and the sea,
they're both right here.
And that's everything that happened this summer.
Original Creator
Daisuke IGARASHI
Children of the Sea
The door is open wide, but no one's inside
Character Design
Animation Director
Kenichiro KONISHI
Art Director
Shinji KIMURA
Music
Joe HISAISHI
Just a chair that smells of the ocean breeze
Screenplay
Saku KONOHANA
Graphics Direction
Kenichiro AKIMOTO
Color Design
Miyuki ITO
Its scent will guide you, so I'll keep it safe
Montage
Kiyoshi HIROSE
So push open the haunting doors
Sound Direction
Koji KASAMATSU
Theme Song
Spirits of the Sea
Kenshi YONEZU
I just hope we don't forget where our story starts
We met the night the stars fell
Into my memory forever more
The most important things need no words
Like a gift from those summer days
Shimmering bright in front of me, I saw the spirits of the sea
In the scorching evening sun, treetops see the boats off
Whispering songs and scattering petals
Somewhere out there, I can hear your laugh
And I can feel the warmth of your cheeks
Once you get past that winding road, you will realize
No matter how far, our hearts beat for each other
Let's make it known that this is happiness
And the most important things need no words
Just let these feelings melt into the light
We met the night the stars fell
Into my memory forever more
The most important things need no words
Like a gift from those summer days
Shimmering bright in front of me, I saw the spirits of the sea
Perhaps we will meet again, at the shore with the ocean breeze
Director
Ayumu WATANABE
Okay, could you cut the umbilical cord?
I asked them. I want you to cut it.
Here.
It felt as if I was cutting off a life.
Hey, mom?
Yeah, what is it?
When I was little, you used to sing me a lullaby.
Was it your mom who taught it to you?
Ah, yeah your grandma used to sing it to me,
back when I was little.
Why do you ask?
Oh, no reason.
Hush, hush, go to sleep.
Rest, my little one.
Little fish at the sea, this is your bedtime song too.
Drink your milk and grow up tall, standing where you are.
One day, you'll reach the skies and soar among the stars.
Gather every star you can and drop them in the sea.
Deep within me, I can feel we're all connected.
The most cherished kind of promises don't need any words.