Why were these supernatural meta powers, called Quirks, introduced into the human race?
Why was the first metahuman,
the Shining Baby, born into this world?
It is all a tragedy.
Quirks are not a blessing for humanity but the beginning of the end.
As it is described in the Quirk Doomsday Theory,
as generations pass, Quirks will mix and evolve
until eventually, no one can control them anymore.
In these times where 80% of humanity is sick with Quirks, it won't be long
before the remaining 20% of the pure humans
have relations with Quirk holders, decreasing their numbers.
Extinction is right around the corner.
We, Humarise, must take action now.
Even if it means we dye the earth with blood.
For the salvation of humanity!
For humanity's salvation!
Now, let us begin.
It seems you don't have a Quirk.
Congratulations.
You have been saved.
The group claiming responsibility
for the recent attack is known as Humarise.
This radical sect was founded by Flect Turn, who advocates for the salvation of humanity.
The attack used a device to spread a Quirk-activating substance known as Ideotrigger through the streets.
These devices will hereafter be called Trigger Bombs.
The mission of our All-Star Hero Team
is to search all twenty-five Humarise complexes around the world at once.
Arrest any Humarise members present
and secure the Trigger Bomb as soon as possible.
Be advised, you should expect heavy resistance.
There's even a chance they might set off the bombs.
As such, we're not asking local law enforcement to assist.
I would like you to carry out
this mission with utmost urgency.
All Might.
Heroes, the success or failure
of this task rests on your shoulders.
Let's give smiles back to the citizens who are frightened by terror.
This is it, heroes.
Start your missions!
Team A, no matter what happens collect the Trigger Bomb before it can be set off.
Roger that!
There it is. Humarise's Otheon headquarters.
Those of us in Team B are tasked with taking over the facility and capturing their leader, Flect.
Don't let your guard down.
You think we don't know that?!
Stay back!
We won't let you get past!
This is what resistance gets you!
Clair, track down the Trigger Bomb!
I'm on it.
Voyance!
They're violating our sanctuary!
Bakugo! Most of these members are Quirkless.
Don't be too rough—
I know!
Stun Grenade!
Endeavor, there's something wrong.
I can't find it anywhere.
Say what?!
Team B, what about Flect?
We're about to close in on him.
Once he's captured,
make him tell you where the bomb is!
Roger!
Flect Turn is in that room.
Damn it!
The leader's gone! Search the premises!
In the end, even after searching
every Humarise building around the world,
we couldn't find a single Trigger Bomb.
Yeah, we interrogated the members we rounded up,
but they've got no clue
where the Trigger Bomb is being kept.
Doesn't seem like they even knew it existed.
It's the same for the members of other branches, too.
There's a good chance this recent attack was carried out by an internal group,
directly under the control of Flect Turn.
Director,
there might be another
facility that we don't know about.
They must have anticipated us
and moved the devices.
All teams stand by in your respective locations.
We're going to send in more heroes to find Humarise's secret base.
I have to deliver this.
If I don't, the world will be destroyed!
Ruru, Lala, it's time for me to head off to work.
Make sure you guys—
We'll study bunches!
And if I'm not home till late?
We'll make dinner for ourselves!
Okay, but what if some weirdo shows up and tries to call you out?!
We'll totes ignore 'em!
All right!
Don't worry, though.
Today's gig shouldn't take too long.
Yay!
Pino!
All right, I'll catch you kiddos later.
Have a good day!
Old codger, you got work for me?
Pickup's on East Third Street.
It needs to be delivered to the Chinese restaurant in South Grove.
How much cash are we talking?
Like you're in a position to negotiate fees.
You'll take the regular rate and do it with a smile.
Yeah, yeah.
Heard you loud and clear.
Oi! That's my bike!
It's stolen, anyway, right?
I'll give it back to its owner later.
You can't just take whatever you want, damn punk!
Now, time for work!
Whoa, the streets here are so busy.
Yeah, well, it is the biggest city in Otheon.
Being told to wait on standby is one thing,
but why do I get treated like an errand boy?!
It's because we're the lowest ranks on the team.
Huh?!
The only reason we're on the World Heroes' Team
is because we were doing our
work studies at Endeavor's Agency.
We're basically freebies.
But since we are on the team,
it's our job to protect everyone from terrorism.
The ideological organization, Humarise.
The stupid organization is full of obsessed idiots.
Quirk Doomsday Theory, my ass.
It's just a cock-and-bull story
and they're actually taking it seriously.
He's running away with the jewelry! Catch him!
Aw, hell! Heroes!
Let's meet at the usual place!
I'll leave the case to you!
Y'all chase the other one!
Got it!
Move! Move! Get out of my way!
Blackwhip!
Todoroki, stop him!
Leave it to me.
That'll teach ya.
You call that an explosion?
I'll show you what a real one looks like!
This is taking too long.
The pickup better not be a no-show.
Catch!
Wait, what?
Doesn't work on me!
That took longer than expected.
Todoroki!
Midoriya, he doesn't have the case!
Did he throw it somewhere?
They've got an accomplice!
Got him!
Stinks to be you!
He's already up on the roof?
Oh, sod off, will ya?
Blackwhip!
Alright then...
Knock, knock!
Thanks much!
He couldn't have gone too far!
Think you can catch someone with these moves?
It's a million years too early for you!
Whoa!
H-Hey!
Wait!
An accident?!
Midoriya!
I'll take care of the crash.
Thanks!
Oh hey, we're alive...
We're gonna be late.
Yikes!
Hold up!
Hold the door, will ya?
Been a wild day, innit?
Geez, this is my best set of clothes and now they're all scuffed up.
That hero bloke, it's all his fault.
Wait, has he always
been around in this neighborhood?
Oh, well, it's not like we'll ever see him again!
Why exactly did you chase me down?
Why were you running away?
I've got work to do so I was in a hurry!
What kind of work?
Business discussions, y'know what I mean?
I may not look like it,
but I'm actually a very talented salesman.
So will you please let me get along with my business?
Then, can you show me what's inside that case?
How much are you offering?
If you ask for something,
it's only natural you should pay for it.
I just want to see what's inside.
You're not a hero from this country, are you?
Is it really okay to do hero work
in a foreign land without permission?
Well, the thing is—
You've got no authority here,
so maybe rethink your tone, mate.
Or should I tell the police that I was chased down and harassed for no reason?
Y'know what? Maybe I will.
I'm glad we could come to an understanding.
If you really wanna do pro work,
I'd suggest you do it in your own country.
Cheerio.
Wait!
What's your problem?
I told you I just want to see what's in the case.
If you wanna see, then flash some cash.
Show me and maybe I will.
Show me a hundred thousand eurus.
That's a bit overpriced.
Then let go of me!
Just a peek!
Hands off!
Uh...
Where's... the jewelry?
Good work.
Hey, come over here for a sec!
Take a look at these.
Where'd these holes come from?
They look like...
Unfortunate, but so be it.
We'll take the necessary precautions.
You shall continue tracking it down.
Thank you, Sir.
Do not forget, Beros—
The only atonement for those possessed by the demon of sickness
is to give oneself to the cause of
salvation of the innocents.
I understand.
I'm so deeply sorry!
Bloody hell—the Japanese culture is strong with this one!
W-Well, I'm just glad you
don't think I'm a criminal anymore.
We're good here.
I guess even heroes make mistakes sometimes!
Oh crap, what's going on?
This isn't what I signed up for!
Wasn't this supposed to be full of jewelry?!
No, don't tell me...
I mixed up the cases?!
A-Anyway, I'm super b-busy, so I'll be on my way.
You're really sweating. Do you feel okay?
Shoot, I need to hurry up and backtrack!
Will it still be there?
If someone picked it up and looked inside,
there's no way I'm getting it back!
I'm dealing with villains here.
"Oopsie, I lost it" isnt's gonna cut it!
What am I gonna do? I'm fucked!
Excuse me?
Are you positive you're all right?
Yeah, I'm peachy.
But—
The police? But how?!
It's a bit of an overkill!
Put your hands up and kneel on the ground!
I-I didn't...
Please just hold on! He's not—
I didn't steal anything!
We have permission to shoot! Fire!
Hang on tight and grit your teeth!
Why'd they suddenly open fire like that?
That scared me half to death!
Someone's after us?
We can't put civilians in danger.
They're coming after us!
Shoot—
We have to get somewhere safe.
You idiots!
We're in the middle of an important mission!
You should leave petty criminals to the local authorities.
I thought heroes were supposed to assist those in trouble.
Maybe you should've taught us
how to prioritize jobs during our work study.
You're not even sorry?!
I assume there's a reason Deku's not here?
He's following someone who was working with the jewel thieves,
but he's not picking up his phone right now.
You slackers!
I never should've brought you here
even if you were doing your work studies!
It's from Midoriya.
Midoriya, do you have
the suspect and the case?
The police just attacked us out of nowhere!
What did you do?
I don't know!
They barely said anything
before they started firing at us,
and when we tried to run,
we were attacked by some villain!
Calm down. Tell me everything that happened from the beginning.
Okay, so I chased the guy who ran away with the case and eventually caught him,
but there wasn't any jewelry inside when I opened—
Endeavor, emergency!
It's about Deku.
Once again, according to recent police reports,
the suspect who is thought to have killed twelve people is at large and considered highly dangerous.
He's a Japanese hero called Deku.
His real name is Izuku Midoriya.
He's been put on the nationwide wanted list.
There are also reports that he has accomplices
Anyone there?
Hello, Todoroki?
but we're unable to identify them at the moment.
Midoriya, what did you really do out there?
What do you mean? Nothing!
According to the news,
you're wanted as a suspect for mass murder.
T-That makes no sense. What's going on?
We'll look into that on our end.
You stay off the grid for now.
They can track you with GPS.
Turn off your phone and don't forget to take out the battery.
Don't do that!
So you were able to
get in touch with your friends?
Wait, what are you taking out the battery?
When are they gonna pick us up?
Yeah, about that...
We're getting an emergency call from the Otheon team.
Apparently, Deku has been put on the wanted list!
Young Midoriya?
But how? What did he do?
According to this, he killed twelve civilians in Otheon.
What kind of ridiculous lie is that?
But this intel comes from HQ.
Whoa, hold it!
You don't actually believe
Midoriya would do something like that, right?
Not a chance.
This has to be some kind of mistake.
Fake news!
There's no way...
Deku would never...
He would never do something like that!
Ribbit!
I'm sure there's an explanation behind all this.
Yeah, yeah!
Don't worry.
Endeavor and the others are on it.
What the fuck?
You're a stone-cold murderer and I'm your accomplice?!
When did we end up on the same side? Explain yourself!
I don't know how we ended up like this.
I still can't wrap my head around it.
Bye-bye, life.
Here I thought I was already living at rock bottom.
What happens if I fall even lower?
Is that even possible?
This is all your fault!
You dragged me into this mess!
Fix this. That's what heroes do, right?
The police fired at us without hesitation, and then we were attacked by a villain.
Whoever is behind this
doesn't care if we're dead or alive.
I would suspect they're not really after us.
Ah, they must want this!
I don't get it.
Nothing in here looks incriminating.
Wait, what are you doing?!
They're after this dumb case, right?
If we just hand it over, this will all be put to bed.
It's simple as that! We'll be done in a jiffy!
It's actually not.
They'd probably want to silence us
since we know about the case.
Hey, hey, hey!
Why you gotta be so negative about it?
All right, new plan: let's destroy the case.
Then we can just say, "Whoops, it burned up!"
That's not gonna fix our problems.
What if we contact the police?
Huh? And say what?
If you want the case, then give us a million eurus!
That would make us real criminals!
We need to calm down!
Come on, let's just hand it over!
They won't go so far as to kill us.
You're overthinking things!
If this case is related to some sort of crime,
we can't just let the bad guys have it.
Don't drag me into your superhero bullshit!
I'm afraid we're already in this together.
They were out to kill us.
If we don't know the reason why,
then it's too dangerous to act rashly.
Otherwise, we'll end up full of arrows.
Okay, then what do you suggest?
We run away.
What?
We can't fight against the police
no matter what the situation may be.
The ones chasing us are the Otheon police.
If we cross the border into
the neighboring country of Klayd,
they shouldn't be able to follow us.
Let's hurry and get out of here before we end up trapped.
What about villains? What if they chase after us?
If it comes to that, I promise I'll protect you.
Running away is our best course of action.
Okay, fine, I guess that makes sense.
I'll go to the border or wherever you think is best.
That bus will get us to the border.
And it'll be free if we hang onto the back.
Absolutely not! We have to pay if we ride.
We're wanted criminals, remember?
It'll be over if somebody recognizes us.
Oh, man.
Look who decided to hitch a lift!
We're partners in crime now, hero.
Delaware Smash: Air Force!
I just paid for two seats.
And we're still riding on the roof?
Well, yeah...
I demand evidence, Commissioner General!
What makes you suspect Izuku Midoriya is the culprit?!
The case against Izuku Midoriya is still pending.
I'm afraid I can't discuss any of the finer details.
Especially not to a fellow Japanese hero.
Japan's number one hero, Endeavor.
He's gravely afflicted with Stage 5.
For the salvation of humanity.
Shoto!
I just got this report back
from a detective friend of mine.
What does it say?
Apparently, the driver of the car that was attacked was a member of Humarise.
Wait, Humarise is involved?
Where is he now?
He's comatose and in critical condition.
Police are standing watch outside his room in the ICU.
Guess we can't interrogate him, then.
And there's one other thing.
It looks like the stolen jewelry
was left scattered near the scene.
That's odd.
It's a message from Midoriya.
What does it say?
Keep eating lunch with strawberries and make sure you eat the dinner in the fridge, too.
Is he telling us to eat strawberries?
Could it be a code?
Right!
Klayd.
Klayd? Does he mean the neighboring country?
He must be heading there right now.
Which means I'm going, too.
All right, then I'll update Endeavor.
Bakugo, you're with me.
What the—where?!
It's about the damn nerd, huh?
Yeah, I'll explain later.
First, let's lose the guards.
Who put you in charge?
I hope Todoroki and the others figured out my code.
Now if only we could figure out
the mystery of this case...
Looks deserted.
No police around.
Hey, do you mind if
I go and make a call real quick?
Oh, sure.
They didn't have anything about you
on TV, so you should be okay.
Try to make it short, though.
Gotcha.
Yes, this is Stanleyk.
Yo, old codger.
Hm? Is that you, Rody?!
Y-Yeah, sorry to call you out of the blue,
but can you swing by my place and
tell my siblings I won't be home for a while?
I'll pay you later, promise.
You bastard!
I have no obligation to do you any favors!
And besides, I got a complaint
saying that last delivery was never made!
Well, things went south—
No excuses!
It's not my fault!
If you value your life then
hurry up and get it delivered! Got it?
I don't have the goods.
Dang it!
Hey, is everything okay?
Oh yeah, all hunky-dory.
Huh?
You think the cases got switched?
Yeah.
Midoriya thinks the case with the stolen jewelry got mixed up with another during the chase.
Which means the one he has now
used to belong to a Humarise member.
That doesn't explain why the police are chasing him.
You're right, it doesn't.
I'm guessing whatever he's carrying around is important.
Question is, why are the police mobilizing on such a large scale?
Humarise members must've infiltrated the police force.
Yeah, and there's no telling
when they'll make their next move.
We have to be careful.
I'll do what I want.
As expected, there's no
transit system going to the border.
We'll have to borrow
some sort of vehicle tomorrow.
Otherwise we'll be stuck walking.
Walking? Are you mental?!
Did you forget how heavy this thing is?
If you get tired, I can just carry you on my back.
Helping people out whenever they're in trouble,
that's what strength is for, right?
I already am in trouble,
so hurry up and help me out already!
Oh, I will, I promise.
Time for take-off!
Rody, gimme too!
Here you go.
You're so lucky!
Pick me up next!
Me, too!
Wow, Rody!
Dad, welcome back!
Hey there, kiddos!
Come on, the puzzle this time is too hard to crack!
How am I supposed to solve this?
All right, but I'm only giving you one hint.
You should be able to figure it out from here.
Dad, this is your...
It's for you.
Thank you for always taking care of Roro and Lala.
I heard the father abandoned them.
What's worse is he became a member of Humarise.
That cult who thinks Quirks are a sickness?
Ugh, they're whackjobs!
They were behind that incident the other day.
Wasn't the dad a famous engineer, though?
Guess you can't judge a book by its cover.
Kids, I don't want you to play with them anymore.
Who knows what they might do.
Okay!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Rody!
I will always be here to support you, okay?
By any means necessary.
If this case is related to some sort of crime,
we can't just let the bad guys have it.
Hello?
What's wrong?
No, he wouldn't...
Are you with the police?
Hand over the package.
So, this means I'm free to bounce, yeah?
Where's your friend?
You both know, don't you?
About the secret of this case!
No, we—
We haven't got a clue!
Please, my brother and sister need me!
They're only kids!
You have to let me go!
Air Force!
And then,
Smash!
I'm so—
But...
Just hold on tight.
Damn it.
Hang on!
I'll go find some medicine!
I-It's not that deep. I'll be fine.
Can't say the same for my phone, though.
You mind?
There should be a first aid kit in my backpack.
Oh, sure.
That villain is a tough one for sure.
We're getting away from here as soon as I'm healed up.
Why did you take the arrow back then?
What do you mean why?
I betrayed you, you know that.
I stole the case while you slept.
Instead of worrying about me,
you could've grabbed it and bogged off.
Why would I do something like that?
I was carrying the jewelry the villains stole this afternoon.
I'm one of those "bad guys" you heroes hate so much.
I can't ignore someone who's in trouble.
I would still want to help them.
Is it really worth getting hurt over?
It's always worth it if I'm able to help someone.
I do not get you.
It's kind of my life's dream.
I want to be someone who can save people.
With a smile on my face the whole time.
I want to be like All Might.
You mean that world-famous hero chap?
Yup, he's my teacher.
Seriously?
You wanted to be like All Might,
so you chased that dream and became a hero.
You and I couldn't be any more different.
My future is pretty much set in stone already.
I don't have the luxury of saying nonsense like "I wanna be a pilot."
It's all I can do to provide for my younger siblings.
Well, maybe—
Don't say a word!
I don't want your pity.
I've always thought heroes
were just people looking for attention
and wanted to make money under the guise of helping others.
You see, heroes never come to the place where I live.
They wouldn't make any cash there, I bet.
But I guess there are heroes like you around, too.
The more you help me and I get to know you,
the more I wonder about what I'm doing with my own life.
Truth is, I'm pretty lame.
I would say the same about myself.
I've wanted to be a pro hero ever since I was just a little kid.
But people kept telling me that
I couldn't do it—that I was too weak.
I couldn't use my Quirk properly,
and I was at the bottom of my class.
Even now I'm always being propped up by my classmates.
I'm pretty lame as well.
That's why I wanted to improve so badly!
To become a hero who saves people
and always with a smile.
That's Pino.
Pino?
And by the way, the name's Rody. Rody Soul.
What's your name?
My name is Izuku Midoriya,
but call me by my hero name, Deku.
Deku. Rolls right off the tongue.
Yeah, it's grown on me.
Let's get some sleep, Rody.
Yeah, let's, Deku.
I deeply apologize.
They escaped before we could neutralize them.
The entirety of the police force
has been mobilized to seek out their location.
Can't you get the army involved?
I'm sorry, Sir.
I'm afraid that's beyond my jurisdiction.
Then continue with the search.
Of course.
For the salvation of humanity.
A villain?!
Rody?
Sorry, did I wake ya?
Where'd you get that car?
I kind of borrowed it.
Just figured we were done walking.
I even wrote an IOU saying I'd pay later.
In the name of the Heroes Association, of course.
Wish they had a Cessna. We could've flown straight into Klayd, no problem.
Cessna? Like the airplane?
You can really fly something like that?
I-I'm obviously kidding.
Hop in.
Hey, Deku.
What's up?
Once we figure out the case's secret,
I can go home, right?
Of course!
You've got a younger brother, right?
Yeah, and a sister, too.
What about your parents?
My mom died right after she had my sister,
so it was up to my dad to take care of us.
He did a pretty good job there for a while.
Then he suddenly up and disappeared one day.
Disappeared?
Ever heard of the group called Humarise?
The terrorist organization?
Yeah, after the townsfolk found out that dad left to become a member,
things got bad for my family.
Friends started ignoring us.
We got kicked out of school
and out of our house.
And I couldn't even get an honest job.
I see. That's awful.
I obviously resented my dad at first,
but after all this time,
I don't give a rat's arse about him anymore.
My little brother and sister are all I care about now.
I just wanna give them a shot at an honest life.
Aw, they're so cute.
My little brother's stupid smart!
And my sister is totally adorbs!
I bet she'll be a fine bird one day!
Whoa! Keep your eyes up, Rody!
Dang, I can't get over how useful your Quirk is.
What about you, Rody?
Yeah?
You've got a Quirk too, right? Show me!
Dun wanna!
Oh, sorry.
You won't laugh, will ya?
I promise!
Really?
I won't! I swear it!
Well, it's kinda weird...
The path is heavily guarded.
No way we're getting in
without fighting our way through.
Our only choice is to scale these ridges.
On my back. Let's move.
Deku, take this.
But why?
It'll be difficult for you to carry me with that injury.
This is where I say goodbye.
Hold on. The truck's out of gas.
I can't leave you alone in a place like this.
C'mon, you know how fast I can run.
I'll scrounge up some berries and wait for you here.
Hurry up and figure out what's up with this case and come back for me.
But Rody...
I'm counting on you, hero!
It's them!
I will not fail again.
Hit 'em with these!
Damn it! What is wrong with those guys?!
Delaware Smash: Air Force!
Rody! Are you okay?
Yeah, somehow...
Where's the case?
Watch out!
Rody!
Catch it, Deku!
I'm coming!
For the salvation of humanity!
Is that... Todoroki?
You learned nothing from Hosu.
Your codes are as lame as ever.
Eyes on me!
Wait, free me! I'll do whatever you want!
Tell me what I want to know and maybe I'll consider.
Fine, you got it!
Die, you traitor!
Damn it.
Bakugo, take her down!
I don't take orders from you!
It's out of control!
Stand down and come quietly.
For humanity's salvation.
Hurry! Get over there!
Rody, are you okay?
Yeah, not sure how.
Where's the case?
Midoriya, this is it, right?
Thanks a bunch, Todoroki.
But how did you find us?
I spotted you from the train thanks to their flashy attacks.
Is he the one you were talking about on the phone?
Yeah, he's been pegged as a criminal like me.
His name is Rody.
Hey, thanks for the assist.
Cut the crap!
The damn case! It's somehow connected to Humarise.
Wait, are you sure?
Yeah, that's why we decided to get involved.
It's possible we might get some useful intelligence.
What's the matter, Midoriya?
This looks like...
What is this?
How does it work?
Try pressing it here?
That'll just make it go back to how it was.
This is hard.
Nope, no dice.
Ugh, hand it over. I'll just blow it up.
No way! You can't do that, Kacchan!
Deku, can I see that for a sec?
Do you know how to solve it?
I did a puzzle like this back when I was a kid.
Let's see...
This goes... here.
Aw yeah, I think I got it!
I wonder what this is.
This one's a memory card for sure.
Okay, there's a town at the foot of the mountain.
Let's go there and investigate.
The target has fled to the country of Klayd.
I'm afraid I don't have the authority to search inside their borders.
No matter.
If he has fled to Klayd,
then he won't be able to interfere
with the plan while it's being carried out.
The time of revelation and the time of reckoning is nigh!
For humanity's salvation!
For the salvation of humanity.
Emergency alert!
Humarise has started a broadcast
and they're streaming it across the planet!
Put it on the screen.
We, Humarise, shall now fulfill our purpose.
To protect the humans who are called powerless,
against those infected by
the wicked disease called Quirks.
The devices we have developed for humanity's salvation
will soon be activated in
twenty-five countries across the world.
Seriously?!
The deliverance from evil
shall be witnessed by all in two hours.
Just two hours?!
However, we are not without mercy.
If you wish to prevent this plan from going into effect,
we will tell you the locations
where our devices have been installed.
What is he playing at?
Even if you do not believe in our righteous cause,
you should still have a fair chance at survival.
Director, these are the twenty-five zones the bombs are placed in.
They all match up with the locations of Humarise branches!
It's possible that this is another trap.
Be that as it may...
Give marching orders to the hero teams on standby.
On it!
There's widespread panic
in each of the affected zones!
Surrounding areas are in chaos as well!
Streets are gridlocked. Transportation is a mess!
Oh no!
Sun Eater, search for anybody who's injured.
Red Riot and Real Steel,
secure a solid evacuation route.
Roger that!
Chimera Kraken!
Let's do this!
Red Gauntlet!
This is your way out!
Hurry up, please!
Do it, Cementoss!
Here it is, Mic!
Listen up, everybody!
We've got a rocking path for you over here so get slidin'!
Remain calm. Don't panic.
Y'all saved our asses!
Thanks a bunch!
We're counting on you, search team.
Find me the Trigger Bomb ASAP. Got it?
Understood!
Ribbit!
Leave the evacuation to us!
We'll focus on finding the Trigger Bomb!
Right!
Tsukuyomi, leave the evacuations to the American team.
We'll search for the Trigger Bomb from up here!
Roger!
Go, Fierce Wings!
Leave no stone unturned!
Tokage, take these sensors
and look for the Trigger Bomb!
Got it!
We'll find it in no time!
Momo, let's head to the next spot.
Right!
How are we supposed to find
such a tiny bomb in this huge city?
You guys!
Hello there!
Nice to see y'all!
Salaam?!
You must find what you seek, not seek what you find!
Follow me!
He's so fast!
He's not paper-thin for nothing!
Clair, where's the device?
No sign of it in this area.
Moving to the next location.
Shoto, what are you doing?
Hurry up and get back here!
Whoa, so many folders!
Where do we even start?
Move it!
Let's sort it by timestamp.
This is the latest file.
Hello, my name is Alan Kay.
I'm one of the scientists Humarise kidnapped.
Kidnapped?
In order to enact their plans,
Humarise took the families of many scientists hostage
and forced us to manufacture Quirk Factor triggering bombs.
That first terrorist attack using one of
these devices was merely a ploy
to gather the world's top heroes in places where Humarise branches are located.
And now that they've succeeded,
the next part of their plan
is to use those horrible bombs to eradicate the pros.
After losing its top members,
the hero society would collapse.
Using the vacuum of chaos afterward, Humarise will wipe out anyone with powers
and build a world where
only the Quirkless are allowed.
That is the true goal of
Flect Turn—the leader of Humarise.
I hope my voice will reach the heroes in time.
The key I've included was made by a fellow scientist, Eddie Soul, who lost his life helping me.
You can use it to disarm the bombs at their base.
Please, save the world.
I repeat.
Humarise, the organization advocating for the salvation of humanity,
has placed bombs around the world which are set
to explode one hour and fifty-two minutes from now.
As you might expect, panic has gripped the areas where the devices are said to be located.
Heroes have been working to evacuate people to safety and subvert this attack.
These are the areas that are in danger of being affected.
No, it can't be!
That circle's in Otheon!
My house is inside of it!
Oh no.
Where are you, Rody?
We should send this to HQ and have them order the hero teams to retreat before it's too late.
It won't work.
The heroes are out there looking for Trigger Bombs.
Even if they are the actual targets of the attack...
Even if they know it's a trap...
As long as there are people who need help,
they will never leave them and run away.
That's what makes them heroes.
They must've counted on it
when they came up with this plan.
Then it's up to us to use that disarming key and stop those bombs.
But how do we do that?
Move it!
The answer has to be in here somewhere.
What kinda idiot makes a key
without telling people where the lock is?
Let's look for a place that
wasn't part of their announcement.
This is where the bastards are hiding.
Kacchan, can you find where the bomb controls are?
Already on it, you damn nerd.
The lowest level underground.
So we know where it is,
but it's more than four hundred kilometers from here.
We can make it.
I think I've got an idea.
It's all right, I know the basics.
This is no time to be chirping.
We'll stop the Trigger Bombs no matter what.
We'll crush those crazy cultist bastards!
We'll protect them all—
the heroes
and the world!
We just received a transmission from Shoto,
a hero who was sent to Otheon.
He said he obtained a master key for disarming the bombs!
Where is he now?
He's heading to a hidden Humarise facility
where their main system is located.
Young Todoroki.
Young Bakugo.
Young Midoriya.
Shoto is heading over to
disarm all the Trigger Bombs?
Then let's go support him.
We can't. Our priority is
evacuation and bomb removal.
Endeavor!
What is it?
I've finally found it!
Where?
It's in front of the north gate of
Otheon Tower inside a large semi-truck!
All heroes near the tower, head over to remove it!
Roger!
Clair, come in!
What the—
Shoji!
Midoriya and the others
are headed to disarm the bombs!
Don't lose focus, Jiro!
What we need to do right now
is complete the mission we were charged with.
R-Right!
There, I found it.
It's hidden inside the third container of that freight train!
We're on it!
Villains?! But how?
Tch, of course there are guards.
Uravity, Froppy!
Take the bomb to someplace safe!
Ribbit!
Yes, ma'am!
I believe Deku and the others will stop the bombs for us!
But we'll do what we can to back them up until then!
Out of my way!
Our teams have located the devices but
they're meeting heavy resistance from Humarise!
Less than thirty minutes on the clock.
The pros fighting desperately across the world
are all counting on you, future heroes!
Almost there.
The afflicted must be purged.
That's their base!
Going in for a landing. Brace yourselves!
Rody, you turn back.
What?
Normies like you should stay out of the way.
From here on out,
it's a job for the heroes!
I don't have time for you small fries!
Some of their members have Quirks, too.
It's not just the mercenaries?
A sound wave?!
Kacchan!
Yeah, yeah!
Midoriya!
Bakugo, we'll leave this to you.
Not so fast!
Don't tell me what to do!
Stop them!
We're taking a right at the end here.
Hold on.
These weaklings are all they've got?
You've got Quirks! Why are you morons helping Humarise, huh?
We have been chosen by Humarise as the worthy!
We will work alongside them
and live in their new, rebuilt world.
So you're just trying to save your own asses?
Selfish much?
Not like I expected any better.
Die!
They're fast!
They think they can do whatever they want?!
You're Rody Soul, aren't you?
Todoroki!
We're on the clock. You go on ahead!
I'll settle this with one blow!
Flashfreeze Heatwave!
My flames had no effect?
He's raging out of control. Is he on Trigger?
He's controlling the flow of water
with his Quirk's rotation?!
Smash!
What the crap?
How'd they cut through my explosion?!
Drop the tough guy act already!
Point-Blank—
Stings, doesn't it?
All that jumping around is getting annoying!
Quit laughing!
It's making my ears bleed!
You chumps never saw it coming, did ya?
I planted grenades all over while we were fighting.
Hell, if you wanna get crazy,
I'm right there with you!
Hurry! Faster!
Get out my way!
This is the deepest room in the base.
So the controls should be right behind that door!
Go away.
This is not a place where someone so diseased should set foot.
He must be their leader, Flect Turn.
This is the holy stronghold that will bring about the salvation of humanity.
This is what you call salvation?
The Quirk Doomsday Theory
hasn't even been scientifically verified!
It's nothing but a rumor!
How can you accept something so uncertain and use it to justify doing such terrible things?!
Pure humans are being threatened by the sickness of Quirks.
Of that, there is no doubt.
As time passes, these powers will mix, evolve,
and run rampant—driving humanity to destruction.
You don't know that!
Whether you have a Quirk or not doesn't matter.
We're all alive! We're all human beings!
The gravely afflicted are beyond our help.
I suppose I shall have to force you to atone.
I will stop your Trigger Bombing!
Smash!
Did he counter my attack?
No...
This shock and force...
It felt like I was hit with a Smash.
That's right.
I was born with this cursed plague myself.
A disease that can't be cured.
I automatically reflect all I come in contact with.
I knew it.
His Quirk reflects any attack against him.
It's the type that's always activated.
You have a Quirk of your own,
and you still don't believe in them?
Long-distance attacks don't work either.
Believe in them?
Ah, such inanity.
Because of this ailment,
I was never once held by my parents.
Even my closest friends
and those I gave my heart to left me.
I could do nothing but watch
as even their feelings got reflected.
Since I reflect everything,
I couldn't even choose death for myself.
A Quirk that cannot be controlled only leads to a life of suffering.
But I can save others from this misery.
These meta powers will trample no more hearts!
I won't use One For All until the moment of impact!
It still didn't work?!
F-Focus all your strength one more time...
Use your speed to get to the controls!
I reject myself.
I will eradicate this global contamination before it's too late!
It is my duty to protect the worthy—to save the pure humans from destruction!
You wretched soul.
In mere five minutes,
the baptism shall begin—the first step towards cleansing this tainted world—
with the blood of the heroes.
I won't let you!
I'll stop the Trigger Bombs if it's the last thing I do!
Try me.
You will be sacrificed just like your friends.
Uraraka.
Asui.
Kaminari.
Sero.
Mineta.
Kirishima.
Shoji.
Jiro.
Yaoyorozu.
You're all fighting so desperately.
To stop these weapons from going off.
To protect everyone's smiles!
Think.
How can I beat this guy?
R-Rody... Why?
It's all right now, Deku.
It's dangerous...
Get away... from here...
I will.
Once I hand this over to those fellers.
The disarming key...
Rody...
They cut me a deal.
They said they'd stop the
Otheon explosion if I helped them out.
Rody, don't do this!
We'll stop him and save everybody!
How are you gonna stop anything when you're all messed up like that?
We're out of time. The bombs are gonna explode.
It's game over.
Rody...
If I can, I will at least protect my family.
Look, I'm a worthless delinquent, Deku.
I can't take on the world, much less save it.
I'm not a hero like you.
Between the world and my family—if it's only one or the other—it's a tough choice to make.
It was the same for my dad, am I right?
Indeed.
Your father, Eddie Soul, was a great help
in the development of the human salvation bomb.
Eddie...
The key I've included was made by a fellow scientist, Eddie Soul, who lost his life helping me.
Please, save the world.
My dad didn't help you.
You threatened to murder our whole family.
He only worked for you because you made him.
Fortunately, he had the clarity to
make the correct decision.
And it appears you're a wise man,
just like your father.
You're making an honorable choice by protecting your loved ones.
You're the same as me.
I developed this plan because I love humanity and wish to save it.
Rody, you can't!
Please!
Rody!
It's time to give up, hero.
People betray. People get betrayed. That's just life.
It happened to me too. Happens all the time.
Nothing to cry about.
Rody...
What about you?
You've got a Quirk too, right? Show me!
You won't laugh, will ya?
I promise!
Really?
I won't! I swear it!
Well, it's kinda weird...
All right! Just as planned!
Deku!
You imbecile!
Rody!
How impertinent!
Deku!
Don't you dare lose. You kick his arse!
Leave the bombs to me. I'll stop them!
You can do it, hero!
Let's go!
I'm the end of the line!
I will not let you get past me!
Hey, Rody.
You've got a Quirk too, right? Show me!
She's my Quirk.
You see, her actions show my true intentions.
Really?
No matter how good I am at lying,
Pino always gives away how I truly feel.
Honestly, it's not much of a Quirk.
Oh, I wouldn't say that.
Not being able to lie?
I think that's a wonderful Quirk!
Damn it! They're hammering my right side!
It's about time you two shut it for good!
This time
I'm really gonna drive it in!
Howitzer Impact!
Happy now? You idiots.
I'm losing consciousness...
Is that...
One last shot.
I won't let you get in Midoriya's way!
Flashfreeze Heatwave!
You can manipulate flames, too?
Fine!
This is the most powerful move I've got!
Flashfire Fist: Jet Kindling!
Midoriya,
make sure
you stop them.
I'll be... like my dad...
I won't give up...
Just like... Deku...
Rody?
For both father and son to die in vain.
There's no hope for such fetid scum.
Shut up!
He's not scum. He's my friend!
It's futile.
Why won't you understand?
Do I need to spell it out?
Because I believe in Rody.
Because I believe in heroes!
We need to cover Endeavor!
Fight, Shoto.
Leave this place to me!
Push it faster, Fierce Wings!
Let's get that thing out of here!
Hawks! We've just discovered a new Trigger bomb.
Wha—
Another one?
This one should be taken care of.
Any remaining devices?
We currently know of two.
Wait!
I just found a new one! So there's a total of three!
Never give up. Right, Bakugo?
Get this up in the air and—
Ribbit!
Ochaco, the Trigger Bomb—
I won't give up!
Because Deku would never give up!
Midoriya and the others are fighting till the end!
So we won't stop either!
It's my duty as a hero!
That's right, heroes always see things through.
Like we'd ever give up!
Has he gotten stronger?
Perhaps, but there's more to it.
His resistance is decreasing? That's it!
There must be a cap on
what his reflecting Quirk can take.
Good.
I'll just go beyond that limit!
Impossible!
Have I reached my boundaries?
I-Is that even possible?!
Because you gave up.
If you didn't lose hope—
If you kept trying—
You might've been able to get along with people!
But instead, you decided that power is a disease.
You gave up and chose to wallow in self-pity.
You're a failure because you stopped trying!
Be silent.
A hero knows what it means to keep fighting until the end.
Shut it!
That's why we're always reminding ourselves...
Quiet.
Go beyond.
Plus Ultra!
Shut up!
Detroit Smash!
A real hero will always find a
way for justice to be served.
I know, All Might.
Young Midoriya!
Heroes have so much to protect in this world.
Which is why...
we won't lose!
United States of World Smash!
You're... too late.
The countdown is over...
...but there's no explosion.
It stopped functioning.
Did they disarm the bombs?
Yeah.
They did it.
Good job, everyone.
Thank you, Rody.
You hang in there, okay?
I'll get you to a hospital soon.
Deku...
I did it, right? I protected my family.
Just like... my dad did.
Yeah.
And I stopped the bombs too, right?
I saw it to the end... just like you would, right?
Yeah, you did great!
You're amazing, Rody.
That's true.
I am pretty cool.
The terrorist attacks that shook the world
were successfully prevented
through the efforts of the hero team.
The members of Humarise, the group behind the threat,
are being arrested as the incident is being resolved.
The case was resolved
without a single new Trigger Bomb exploding.
In the end, the heroes protected the world.
But it wasn't just the pros and students.
The one who really saved everybody—
the one who never gave up—
Rody!
Didn't think you'd be out so soon.
They said I was good to go already.
Glad to hear it.
If I had died stopping those bombs,
I would've become a total legend, though!
Well, that's a morbid thing to say!
So, did you come up with any big plans for the future?
Just going back to the everyday life for now.
Though, I won't pick and choose anymore.
I'm gonna reach out and grab it all.
Great!
We will now begin boarding for flight NNY-224.
I guess I gotta run.
Do me a solid and never come back, okay?
Nothing good happens when you're around.
Probably best if you kept your hero stuff to Japan.
I'll come back and visit for sure.
Yeah, like I care.
Got a job for me, old codger?
Like a real gig! Something more respectable.
One of my employees did quit on me.
Guess you could help.
Whatever shall I do?