Otheon
Japan
Egypt
France
America
Humarise France Branch
Humarise America Branch
Humarise Singapore Branch
All-Star World Heroes' Team General HQ
Otheon Airport
Otheon Team Standby Hotel
Midoriya
Japan Team Standby Hotel
Egypt Team Standby Hotel
France Team Standby Hotel
Otheon Police HQ
Otheon Police
Commissioner General's Office
-
Izuku Midoriya
Keep eating
lunch with strawberries
and make sure
you eat the
dinner in the fridge, too.
-
Izuku Midoriya
Keep eating
lunch with strawberries
and make sure
you eat the
dinner in the fridge, too.
|
-
eroes
Neighboring Country of Klayd
Klayd Airport
Day of Departure