As still as a city
As still as a city with no one in it
As insecure as hands
As insecure as hands grasping at thin air
And yet my body
And yet my body refuses to give up
Within these eyes,
Within these eyes, I hold
Within these eyes, I hold the sparks of my dream
As awkward as a room
As awkward as a room filled with silence
My days without you
My days without you are dry as dust
And yet once again,
And yet once again, I rise up all alone
To this reality that
To this reality that spreads out before me
There may be times when
There may be times when the rains hold us back
There may be nights when
There may be nights when the words won't let us sleep
But I believe our compassion—
But I believe our understanding—
But I believe our sympathy—
But I believe our compassion—
But I believe our empathy—
might be the place where our souls reside
Already awake;
Already awake; kicked the door open
And dashed through the sky
And dashed through the sky under the blazing aurora
As the dew starts to cover up the city streets
The sound of your breathing gets even heavier
Yet you keep moving forward every single day
Until you cross the sea of asphalt
At the edge, you can already feel the freedom
Beyond it, the whole world is shouting all the time
Remember the vistas of home we saw
Reject the destiny that chains us down
Dream of a future where we accept each other
Just dream
Just dream of it
There may be times when
There may be times when the winds hold us back
There may be nights when
There may be nights when the tears just won't stop
But I believe our compassion—
But I believe our understanding—
But I believe our sympathy—
But I believe our compassion—
But I believe our empathy—
might be the place where our souls reside
Already awake;
Already awake; kicked the door open
And dashed through the sky
And dashed through the sky under the blazing aurora
As the dew starts to cover up the city streets
The sound of your breathing gets even heavier
Yet you keep moving forward every single day
Until you cross the sea of asphalt
At the edge, you can already feel the freedom
Beyond it, the whole world is shouting all the time
Cheering for you!