In exchange for wings that can fly in the sky
We chose to have hands which can hold each other
Even then, we were fascinated with the sky
I wonder if its a sin to let dreams overlap
When summer looks at the fall that arrives
I imagine what kind of face it makes
Is it admiration, or is it love
All while knowing that the dream won't come true
From passing rain to passing rain, sun shines past tree after tree
Forever and ever before you had introduced yourself
Were you able to remain as yourself?
Today is the one day in the millennia when gravity sleeps
We stand in the blind spot of the sun, ready to depart from this planet
When he had awoken from his sleep, we head to a place of no return
on the sound of "go" we slam our feet on the ground, to a planet far away
Let's go
My heart becomes rushed because of the summer cold
It makes the summer go by even faster
Amidst the dizzying scenery
You were the only one that I could see clearly
Ever since that day I had met you
I had suddenly stopped dreaming at night
It had been waiting for long within the ground
The time is now for that dream to be fulfilled
Today is the one day in the millennia when gravity sleeps
We ride on the sound of the fireworks, ready to depart from this planet
When he had awoken from his sleep, we head to a place of no return
on the sound of "go" we slam our feet on the ground, to a planet far away
Let's go
Just a bit more, we'll reach past our destiny
Just a bit more, we'll reach past civilization
Let's go
Just a bit more, we'll reach past our destiny
Just a bit more
Let's go
Just a bit more, we'll reach past our destiny
Just a bit more, we'll reach past civilization
Let's go
Just a bit more, we'll reach past our destiny
Just a bit more
We are the sails for our dreams
We get past the nights to approach the coming day
Now, we are filled with expectations
Together we say "We'll do something about the rest"
While we are not fearless, we won't stop
Even if we try to avoid danger, we cannot help it when it arrives
But our love tells us, its voice tells us
It tells us to "go!"