It's something only she and I can tell you about.
A story of one of the secrets of this world.
It looked like a pool of light.
She ran out of the hospital.
Praying with all her heart,
she crossed the shrine gate.
Fish?
Now I wonder if what I saw that day was just a dream.
But it wasn't a dream.
That summer day, up in the sky,
we fundamentally altered the nature of this world.
I'm a 16 year old high school student
We're expecting heavy rain shortly.
It's gonna rain again?
I thought it'd finally cleared up.
We ran into a typhoon on the island, too.
Excuse me.
Sorry.
For your own safety, please head back inside.
Here it is!
Wow!
Thanks a lot.
That was one hell of a storm.
I'm looking for a well paid part-time job
This is delicious.
Sure you don't want any, kid?
Yeah, I don't have much of an appetite.
Really? Thanks for the treat then.
Don't mention it! You saved my life after all.
Yeah, that was a close one.
Come to think of it,
it's the first time I saved someone's life.
Okay...
By the way, I wonder if they have beer here.
Should I get you one?
So expensive!
A grown-up man scrounging on me...
Tokyo is scary.
Where can I get one without a Student ID?
Question posted.
It's raining again.
Why did you come to Tokyo, kid?
Ehm... I'm visiting a relative.
Summer vacation starts early at my school, you know.
Well, feel free to contact me if you ever need help.
See ya, kid.
K&A Planning
I won't.
Shower's 280 yen for 20 minutes.
Here...
It started pouring again all of a sudden.
Don't you ever learn? It's a pain to clean up.
Sorry...
Last year's instances of sudden torrential
rain were largely exceeded this year.
Part-time jobs
0 results
Ah, finally!
4 answers
No such jobs
Wait, that's illegal
Sex club boys don't need IDs
For real!?
Huh, are you really a university student?
Your ID?
No way.
Forget it.
It's not a job for kids!
Sudden downpours are expected—
Tokyo is scary.
Living in Tokyo
Expenses, Job Interviews
I've got to start saving.
Shinjuku Station
Please, don't sit down here.
Sorry.
All you can drink for 1800!
Hey master!
Hey, wait a minute!
Everything the solicitors say is a lie.
Illegal weapons possession
18 guns and 1600 bullets found
Don't hand them any money.
You'll never get it back.
Hey, you.
What are you doing here at this hour?
Aren't you a minor?
Hey! Wait!
Quit messing around!
Tokyo is scary, right?
But...
I don't want to go home.
Never again.
Well, who's this kid?
Is he asleep?
On the floor?
Hey you, are you a customer?
Sorry!
Hey... is he gonna be okay?
I'm sure he'll be fine.
Get out of the way.
Sorry.
Must be a toy gun.
Route Planner
K&A Planning
Yamabukicho
Uhm, This...
It's for you. Don't tell anyone.
Huh? But, why?
Isn't that's your only dinner in like, three days?
In all the sixteen years of my life,
I think that one
was the most delicious dinner I've ever had.
Hey, when can we meet again?
How about the day after tomorrow?
Great! I found a nice café.
I'll book us a table.
See you, Nagi.
Bye, Ayane.
A grade schooler?
Lucky me! I was hoping to see you.
Hi, Kana.
Hey, Nagi.
He's a ladies' man.
Did you curl your hair?
You could tell? How does it look?
You look great! Super cute.
Tokyo is amazing.
K&A Planning: Downstairs
This is the place.
Does this even work?
Excuse me.
I'm Morishima from the call earlier.
Is Mr. Suga around?
Ah, Mr. Suga?
Mr. Suga?
Wait, this isn't appropriate!
Hello.
I-I'm sorry!
Ah, the new assistant Kei told me about.
Huh? No, I haven't—
I'm Natsumi. Nice to meet you.
Finally, someone else to do the grunt work!
Hey, kid.
Yes?
You looked at my boobs, didn't you?
I did not!
What's your name, kid?
I'm Hodaka Morishima.
Hodaka. That's a beautiful name.
Do you work here, Natsumi?
Huh? Wanna know about me and Kei?
Yeah.
Amusing.
It's exactly like you think.
Seriously?
I've never seen a mistress before.
Long time no see, kid.
Did you lose some weight?
Hey, don't tell me you went gambling again.
So, kid, you're looking for a job, aren't you?
This is what we do here.
We write for time-honored and prestigious magazines.
The man who came from 2062
Downpours and weather weapons
Human sacrifices protecting Tokyo
Our next feature is on Urban Legends.
Go and interview people who have
experienced something like that.
Huh, but I—
Any topic will do.
Like prophecies or getting spirited away.
You kids like that kinda stuff, right?
How about this?
It's an internet rumor.
The one hundred percent sunshine girl.
Sunshine girl?
I'm a sunshine girl!
It's raining so much this year.
He ignored me?
No wonder there's such a demand for that.
Right.
Come on, you've got zero initiative.
She's got an interview. Go along and listen.
Huh? Me? Right now!?
You're on probation!
He's an intern.
No, really, I can't.
Of course, sunshine girls do exist.
I knew it!
And rain girls exist, too.
Psychic
sunshine girls are possessed by the fox god,
and rain girls are possessed by the dragon god.
Excuse me?
Dragon god individuals drink a lot.
They yearn for water.
They're strong-willed and competitive,
but a bit careless and unreliable.
Huh, maybe that's me.
Fox god individuals are hardworking,
but too weak-hearted to be leaders.
Many are beautiful.
That's definitely me.
The weather is off-balance right now,
so more sunshine and rain girls are born.
It's the Gaia homeostasis hypothesis.
I see.
But, we must be careful.
Messing with nature always has a cost.
Whoever uses too much weather power, gets spirited away.
That's...
I'll be careful.
So, how did it go?
A so-called psychic talked at length
about fantasy novel like stuff.
"If you use too much power, you'll get spirited away."
I see, that kinda stuff.
I mean, weather isn't some kind of power.
It's a natural phenomenon.
Look, we're aware of that but
we're providing entertainment here.
That's all you've written so far?
You're slow.
Sorry.
Aah, but it's not bad.
Alright kid, you're hired!
Wait a minute! I never said I was—
It's a live-in job.
Meals included.
Really?
I'll do it! Hire me, please!
Good good.
What was your name again?
You're kidding, right?
It's Hodaka.
Ah, Right.
Here we go.
There you go.
I'm underage, remember?
Let's celebrate Hodaka's hiring.
Cheers!
That was the first meal I shared
with someone since I came to Tokyo.
This is where my new life began.
The afternoon when the wind had turned our helm right before our eyes
I felt that I could do anything reckless, anything world-breaking
Be it my dominant or off-hand, I really felt I could
It was a small editing company
run only by Mr. Suga and Natsumi.
We'd go between "We'll manage somehow," "How much longer?" and "Are we alright?"
My job was to manage all the office chores.
Starting from Mr. Suga's personal care.
Answering calls, filling receipts, transcribing interviews.
Like a pendulum, making sure to hang on tight
Is that all you've written so far?
This isn't mine.
Mr. Suga is not at the office right now.
Let's see if we can use up that dream from the inside out
Sometimes we rode around town on Natsumi's bike.
If we could change the world with love that won't be laughed at
Nothing's decided from the start, I don't need that
A middle schooler?
So please, God, quickly show me the next step
They're looking for a sunshine girl.
With an unbelievable amount of heart, with my terrible voice
Really? That's hilarious.
My sis's friend's a real sunshine girl.
She always calls her before a date.
I want to be able to shout and not rot away
We're not interested.
And then, the weather balloon picked up something strange.
Let me use up all the courage I have
A swarm of moving objects among the cumulonimbi!
If we could change the world with love that won't be laughed at
That's all you've written so far!?
Don't buy these unless they're on sale.
He's not at the office.
This paragraph's crap.
Nothing's decided from the start, I don't need that
Yes.
But this one ain't so bad.
Gambling
Let me use up all the righteousness I have
Mr. Suga, come on, wake up. Please wake up.
A greeting without goodbyes and future without helplessness
Is like a heart with lots of doors with no key in sight
My days were hectic.
But for the first time, someone was relying on me.
I don't care how proud our future feels as it looks over us
We still have something we need to do
And then, those rainy days in Tokyo, passed by in a flash!
We want to use it all up, all the miracles we have
Rain.
There you are.
How's it going, Rain?
Yeah? Good boy.
It's an easy job.
Don't worry, you'll see.
But—
Just give it a try.
You'll get paid right away.
Our club's right over there.
That girl...
Give it a shot and earn yourself some bucks.
It's right there.
Let's go!
But...
Hey, hey, wait just a minute!
Hey, wait—
Just keep running!
Listen to me!
You damn brat!
Hey hey hey, you
what do you think you're doing?
You were forcing her.
Huh?
Are you retarded or what?
We had a deal.
Hey, wait a minute.
Aren't you the brat who was
squatting in front of our club?
What's this, payback?
Please, stop it!
Dammit!
Get off me!
What's that? A toy gun?
He's totally lost it.
Get up!
You.
What the hell was that for?
To thank me for that burger?
And what's with the gun? Who are you?
That's...
I found it. I thought it was a toy.
It was like a lucky charm for me.
What?
You pointed it at that guy!
You could have killed him!
I can't believe this!
You make me sick!
You're the worst!
I got fired, from my part-time job.
Because of me?
Nah, nothing to do with that burger.
But still, I need a well-paid job.
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have—
Tell me, does it hurt?
N-Not really.
You're a runaway, aren't you? I can tell.
But, you can't enjoy Tokyo if its raining all the time.
Huh? Yeah...
Come here for a sec.
Look, it will clear up now.
Huh?
What'd you mean—
A sunshine girl!?
I'm Hina. And you?
Hodaka.
How old are you?
Sixteen.
Younger than me?
I'll be,
let's see,
eighteen, next month.
Huh? No way!
You better treat me with respect.
Nice to meet you, Hodaka.
Yeah.
Mom, there's a fish.
Really? That's nice.
Don't talk bullshit.
I'm serious. It's this way.
Look, over there.
I don't see it.
It's right there!
Take a closer look.
The hell is that?
Kanto region is experiencing
record-breaking rainfall this summer.
It's been raining continuously for two months now.
Forecast predicts heavy rainfall for another month.
Sunshine For You
The Meteorological Agency said
it's an extremely exceptional—
5000 yen
Maybe that's too expensive.
Hey, hey!
Check this, it's pretty incredible!
Huh?
This... came down with the rain.
At the Cosmo Hall parking lot.
The fafrotskies!!
It's a mysterious object from the sky.
Like a see-through jellyfish.
They kinda look like fish.
They came down from the sky?
But, they leave no trace...
Look, they disappear instantly.
Remember what that guy we interviewed earlier said?
The sky is a deeper unknown world than the sea.
A cumulonimbus can hold as much water as an entire lake.
So, it might as well harbor an uncharted ecosystem.
Like, these fish?
I guess. Fascinating, isn't it?
That means,
we can make some money off of it!
Huh? What the heck?
You are starting to sound exactly like Kei.
You'll be boring when you grow up.
Don't put off your sunshine girl.
Aren't you going out on a date?
It's not a date! I'm just—
I'm gonna go look for a job.
Job? Don't you work here?
Nah, I'm just hanging out.
As I said, it's not a date.
I understand how you feel, Keisuke.
But, she finally stopped talking about you.
Wouldn't it be inconsiderate to meet her right now?
But, I have the right to see her.
Besides, you have a smoking addiction, don't you?
Huh?
She's got asthma.
You're too inconsiderate.
I quit smoking a little while ago.
But still,
you give off a bad impression.
It keeps raining all the time these days.
She can't even play outside, and it's bad for her asthma.
I feel sorry for children nowadays.
We used to have beautiful springs and summers.
They can't live together, just the two of them.
I know, right?
Wait a second.
Wouldn't this be
the first time
that I'm visiting a girl?
Welcome, Hodaka.
You got lost, didn't you?
No, uhm... It's not much, but...
Wow, thank you.
Come on in.
Thank you.
Sure thing.
Potato chips
Ramen
Hodaka, have you had your lunch?
Not yet... But, you don't have to—
It's fine, don't worry about it.
How about I use these?
Yeah, sure.
Thanks.
Do you live all by yourself, Hina?
With my younger brother, actually.
We ran into some problems.
Huh, problems?
And what about you, Hodaka?
Why did you run away?
I found it suffocating, that town and my parents.
I see.
Thought about going back?
I don't want to.
I see.
I apologize for the delay!
Woha!
Ah, I forgot the chives!
Chives.
So, how's life in Tokyo?
Eh? Oh...
Come to think of it, I don't feel so suffocated anymore.
Really? Happy to hear that!
Let's dig in!
Huh? What? An earthquake?
No, no.
It's just the train.
Hodaka, is this for real?
Sunshine For You
Well, you're a real sunshine girl, aren't you?
Yep.
You can clear up the sky just by praying, right?
Well, yeah.
Don't you need a job?
I do, but I can't just charge people for that.
I don't think the nightlife business is for you, Hina.
Hodaka...
What are you looking at!?
I'm not looking at anything!
Yikes.
Isn't 5000 yen a bit too expensive?
Then how about 3000 yen?
Considering living expenses, though...
Maybe we need some graphics.
Ah, I'll draw them!
What's that? A hippo?
It's a frog...
For real?
It's done!
Sunshine For You
Then I'll post it, okay?
Yeah.
I'm home.
Sis, I'd like some sardines—
Who're you?
You're that boy from the bus!
Eh?
You two know each other?
Hodaka, this is my brother, Nagi.
Nagi, this is Hodaka, my business partner.
New request
Whoa, we've got a request!
You posted it already!?
They want good weather for the flea market.
It's tomorrow!
Wait a minute! Am I really going to do this!?
Widespread rain tomorrow—
It's gonna rain tomorrow!
That's the whole point!
Who the hell is this guy?
Don't worry, Hina! I'll help out too!
How!?
Hina, please use this!
Sorry, don't need it.
Huh? Then, I've got another secret weapon for you!
Quit messing around, Hodaka!
Who called those weirdos?
We thought they might bring good luck.
Don't push yourselves too hard, you guys!
We're almost there!
Hina, do you need water?
Sis, want some candy?
Just tell them to go home.
Okay
Hey, the sky's clearing up!
No way!
The sun's out!
It's been ages!
Take a look! It's been so long!
So beautiful!
Amazing!
How was it?
You guys are awesome.
You're a real sunshine girl.
I still can't believe it.
That was great,
even if it was a coincidence.
It wasn't—
Is 20,000 yen good enough?
It's too much!
You get a bonus because you are cute, missy.
Thank you so much! We'll sell a lot more now.
Hell yeah!
That was amazing, sis!
I feel I can do this!
Cool! Let's make money with the weather!
Yay!
I can't find the song I want to listen to
At the start of this sullen day
New request
Just by hearing your exaggerated "good morning"
Make it sunny for our wedding, please
Its strange how everything had changed
On the sports day!
I wonder why your words feel like the lines that you would see
The human mind works in mysterious ways.
Like, you just need to see the sun
shining in the morning to feel energized.
Being recited at the climax of a movie and I like it
A blue sky makes you feel glad to be alive.
It makes you feel more in love
with that someone by your side.
It's a once-in-a-lifetime chance, you know!
If being coward is a sickness then I feel mine won't heal soon
I wanna wear a white dress under the blue sky.
To watch the meteor shower!
It never wins on rainy days.
But you had appeared before me with the face of the savior
I worked so, so, so hard
at the sweatshop just for this day!
I wanna play outside!
It was you who had the key to my inner light
Everyone had their own reasons
to wish for sunshine in a rainy Tokyo.
Hina was only able to clear a small spot for a brief time.
It's not too bad to be living just to find out why that is
But the sky would always answer her prayers.
She really is the one hundred percent sunshine girl!
It can only be you and there's no reason that it's not you
So please don't go asking me "why is that so?"
Even though it feels endless, you finally offer a good answer
It felt as if the whole town was dressing up.
After I had 2019 other bad ones
And I thought, what a wonderful world I was born into.
Even though it feels endless, you finally offer a good answer
C'mon! Say cheese!
Go! Go! Keep goin'!
Look, there's more!
Whoa!
A good answer from the get-go
Thank you!
Thank you very much!
Thanks!
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
We could really influence people with the weather.
I realized how much the human heart
is connected with the sky.
There's miso soup in the pot — H.
I'm off.
To where?
Terror alert
Is it canceled due to the rain?
It's already past noon.
When will it start?
I even changed into these clothes for this.
It's canceled for sure.
Shall we go home?
I'm tired.
I read online about the amazing
one hundred percent sunshine girl.
But are you sure about that?
Relying on a sunshine girl for such a huge event?
It's gonna rain all week.
We won't be able to postpone it.
In this situation, we're even willing to rely on a charm.
The fireworks festival
will start at 7 pm as scheduled.
I'm in love.
With this job, as the sunshine girl.
I feel like I finally found my role in life.
Maybe.
Or maybe not. Or maybe not not.
Maybe not, not not...?
Which is it?
You're unbelievable.
I mean, thank you, Hodaka.
Weather is a mystery.
The way the sky looks can move you so much.
Hina really moves my heart.
Yesterday's fireworks festival
were blessed with a miraculous sunshine.
But heavy rainfall is back again today like a backlash.
Type of company
The temperature in the capital is now 21ºC,
much lower than average.
Your strengths
It's unusually chilly for August.
Make sure you wear a jacket—
You're my first choice.
You're my first choice!
I admire skilled and charming people
I'm looking forward to joining the company
Be careful to not catch a cold.
Rainfall and low temperatures
are driving up the food prices.
Lettuce is three times more expensive than last year
Sky Fish report
Oh, that project? Right, we've put it on hold.
Sorry, we're not going ahead with it.
I see. Yeah, I'll do my best.
It was nice working with you.
What is it?
Hello, Mamiya speaking.
Mamiya, It's Keisuke.
Sorry to rush you. Regarding our meeting—
You're late, Kei! It's an important interview.
In a bad mewd, are we? No luck with work?
Where's Hodaka?
Busy with his other job?
He's been neglecting work lately.
Not really. Just let him be.
We're not that busy anyway.
He took in that cat.
You did the same with him, Kei.
Huh?
You helped him because he reminded you of yourself.
So, how much are you paying him?
Just 30,000 yen? That's so low.
Nope. It's 3000.
What?
Are you for real? 3000 yen a month? That's exploitation!
Eyes on the road.
You're gonna get sued! Actually, I'll report you myself!
I mean, he gets food and accommodation,
and the company pays his phone bills. It's only fair.
Ugh!
It's no surprise he's got an extra job.
I'm surprised it actually cleared up.
You kids sure are something.
It's a shame you're quitting.
She was caught on camera and we got flooded with requests.
The web famous sunshine girl!
We really can't do this anymore.
We'll stop for a while after this one last request.
She looks tired, too.
We've got guests, Granny?
Oh, there you are.
Thought I could help.
Well aren't you young. So you're friends with Granny?
Hello!
I requested for good weather on
my husband's first anniversary.
Oh, it actually stopped raining.
It'd be hard for him to return if it was raining.
Return?
They say the dead come back
from the sky around mid-August.
So that means, he passed away last year?
Yes.
Around the same time as my mom...
You lost your mother last year?
Yes.
Then, you should light a welcoming fire for her.
I'm sure she will protect you.
Okay.
Riding the smoke, he'll come back from the other side.
From where?
From heaven.
There's always been another world up in the sky.
Apparently, this is what the Weather Maiden saw.
It's a mysterious painting.
Flying fish in the sky. And a dragon, too.
It's beautiful.
I know, right?
And this Weather Maiden was like a shaman, right?
Huh? What?
Was she like a shaman?
Yeah.
Fixing the weather is the Maiden's job.
Fixing it?
Sounds fishy to me.
Like this year's abnormal weather?
Huh? What do you mean abnormal?
They all keep saying the same thing.
"First time in recorded history."
But since when did records begin?
Maybe a hundred years at best.
How old do you think this is?
Eight hundred years old!
Eight hundred!?
Don't get too excited, Grandpa.
Weather changes on a whim in the first place.
Regardless of human needs.
We can't even tell what's the norm and what isn't.
We're only allowed to stay temporarily
in the space between the sky and the earth,
clinging hard not to be shaken off.
We used to be aware of this in the past, you know.
However, there's a thin thread linking us humans to the sky.
That is the Weather Maiden.
I pray for good weather
I pray for the rain to stop
A special girl who can take in people's
wishes and deliver them to the sky.
I pray for good weather for Mom's birthday
I pray for a blue sky for my Grandpa
In ancient times, there used to be
one in every village and every country.
Kei, doesn't that sound like the sunshine girl?
Hey you guys,
do you even want to listen to my Grandpa?
It all sounds pretty far-fetched.
Ouch.
It doesn't seem far-fetched at all!
Thank you for such an interesting story.
But, everything comes at a price.
After all, a tragic fate awaits the Weather Maiden.
Tachibana
One, two, three.
Your turn sis!
Thanks for keeping Granny company.
We're actually here because of work.
Play with us, Granny.
They seem to be having fun.
How old are you guys?
I'm sixteen and she is...
She said it's her birthday next week.
Really? You've gotta get her a present.
Come have some watermelons, everyone!
Yay!
Thank you.
Hey, wait a second!
Dammit.
Shit, but why?
Wait a minute.
I had no idea she was a minor, I swear—
That's not what this is about?
I told you it wasn't!
You made us run for no reason.
That's you, right?
Can you tell us anything about this boy?
A high schooler?
Maybe he picked up the gun, that Shibata threw away.
In that case, he might've written about it.
On social media?
Kids write all sorts of stuff on social media these days.
I'm a 16 year old high school boy
What's the best birthday present
for an 18 year old girl?
Posted
4 answers
Bang her
Cash
Don't ask online!
Go, Nagi!
You're amazing, Nagi! You're the best.
A ring would be perfect.
Really? Isn't that a bit too serious?
It's for sis' birthday, right?
Yeah, I did ask someone else for reference, but—
What present I'd like?
Hugs and kisses. Cash.
A decent boyfriend. And a job.
She wasn't helpful at all.
Bye bye, Nagi!
See you later, Nagi!
Hodaka, you're in love with sis, aren't you?
Huh? It's not like that—
Or maybe it is...
You know, being insecure
is the worst condition for a man.
R-really?
Be clear before you start dating,
and be ambiguous later. It's the basics.
Can I call you Master Nagi?
Sis has been working hard ever since Mom passed away.
I'm sure she's been doing it for me,
because I'm still a kid.
That's why I want her to do more teenage stuff.
I don't know if you're the right guy, though.
Thank you very much.
Um, do you think she'll like it?
Huh?
You spent three hours choosing it for her.
If it were me, I'd be very happy to receive it.
I wish you the best of luck.
Shinjuku Station
Longest rain spell record broken
Tomorrow's sunshine girl job will be our last.
A man requested good weather
at the park for his daughter.
After that,
I'll give her the ring.
Daddy, do it again! Once more!
Alright, you'd better be ready!
Ouch!
This isn't good for my back.
How did it turn out to be you, Mr. Suga?
Did you know about my job?
You knew and you said nothing!?
And you have a daughter!?
I'm quite surprised.
Today's forecast said it's gonna rain for sure.
My daughter has asthma.
She lives with her granny,
who won't let me see her on rainy days.
Nothing beats a gorgeous blue sky.
So Mr. Suga, you're Hodaka's boss, right?
Right, I also saved his life.
Why does she treat you like a little kid?
Hina is two years older than me.
Huh? Sixteen? Seventeen? Eighteen?
It's all the same.
—Isn't it?
—No it's not!
There you are!
Hey, everyone!
Aren't you gonna be in trouble?
Does Natsumi know that you're married?
Hey, hey, what's up with you guys?
Hodaka thought you were my—
Mistress!?
I mean, you never told me
that you were uncle and niece.
Hodaka, that's a disgusting fantasy.
Hodaka, you're a perv.
Hodaka...
You looked at my boobs just now!
I did not!
Ah, Nat!
Moka! Hello!
Hey, Daddy! I made a crown of flowers for you!
Ah, really?
Hodaka, you come here too!
Ah, my master is calling.
Hodaka's hilarious, isn't he?
He's such a kid.
Don't you think they're alike?
Hodaka and Mr. Suga?
Yeah.
Kei ran away from home
and came to Tokyo when he was a teen.
He met his future wife and fell in love big time.
But she met with an accident a few years ago.
He's still in love with her.
You know, I've been dying meet you, Hina!
You're the one hundred percent sunshine girl!
That's incredible!
How I wish I had a skill like that on my resume!
I hate looking for a job.
I wish I was in high school again.
I just wanna be a grown-up quickly.
Right, good to see you're doing fine.
I was actually a bit concerned.
Moka, are you tired?
Here, take a breath.
One, two, three.
I'm fine! Let's play!
I don't think so.
I guess we'll leave now.
I want to spend more time with Nagi!
How about we all go and get some dinner?
But—
Then, I'll go eat with Moka.
Sounds good?
Sure!
Yay!
Hodaka, take sis home.
Hina! Thanks for bringing sunshine today!
Likewise!
I'm glad I could make you happy.
Oh my god.
Oh my god!
Wouldn't this be
the first time
I propose to someone?
Hina!
Hodaka.
Ah, sorry.
It's okay.
What were you saying?
Ah, nothing in particular.
What were you gonna say?
Hodaka, you know...
I...
Hina?
Hodaka!
I think I became a sunshine girl
on that day, last year.
I prayed for good weather all day long.
I wanted to have one last walk
with my mom under the sun.
It looked like a pool of light.
Praying with all my heart,
I crossed the shrine gate.
When I came around, I was lying on the roof
and the sky was clear.
Since then, I think I got connected with the sky.
Connected
with the sky?
Hodaka, hide!
Sorry for the late visit, it's the police.
The police?
Are you sure you've never seen him?
He's been spotted around this area quite a few times.
I don't know him. What has he done?
We just want to ask him some questions.
He's a runaway and his parents
filed a missing person's report.
Also, Miss Amano, you're living
alone with your little brother, right?
That's right
That's a bit of a problem too.
Without a guardian, you—
But!
We don't cause trouble for anyone.
Hina.
They'll come back tomorrow with the social service.
What should I do? They'll separate us!
Mr. Suga
Hodaka! The police were—
I know. Master, go home for now.
Temperatures have fallen sharply after the sunset—
Mr. Suga?
Surprised by the new look?
It's my disguise.
The police came to my office earlier.
They're treating this like a kidnapping.
I denied any involvement but they still suspect me.
Take it, it's your severance pay.
Don't come to the office anymore.
They'll arrest me at this rate.
I filed for custody of my daughter.
It's a delicate time, sorry.
You should go back home tomorrow.
Then everything will go back to normal.
It'll be best for everyone.
Time to grow up, kid.
We can't stay here anymore.
But, where will you—
I don't know, but—
Anywhere will do as long as I'm with you, sis
Hodaka, you'd better go home before you get caught.
You've got a place to go back to.
Don't say that.
We're gonna be fine.
I'm not going back.
Let's run away together!
A heavy rainfall warning has
just been issued in the Tokyo area.
It could be the heaviest rainfall in decades.
Watch out for floods in lowland areas.
A sudden low pressure system is developing into a typhoon—
Rivers are flooding.
The danger is rising.
Hey, it's overflowing!
Keep calm and walk slowly towards the exit.
Namboku Line Akabane - Iwasbuchi Station,
Shibuya Metro Station.
Heavy rain and flood warning
Several flights canceled at Haneda Airport.
Over 6 inches of rainfall in an hour.
Heavy floods in many areas of Tokyo.
Are you okay?
Kita Ward, Arakawa Ward, Taito Ward,
EVACUATION ORDER
Sumida Ward, Shibuya Ward.
You may get stranded.
Isn't it a bit too cold?
It's unusually cold for August.
Rainfall range and intensity
The temperature in Tokyo has fallen below 10°C.
Cumulonimbi keep gathering above Tokyo.
In just an hour, it feels like an entirely different season.
I repeat, a heavy rainfall warning
has been issued in the Tokyo area.
The low-pressure system over the Kanto region—
because of a stream of cold air at Kanto, the weather—
Heavy rainfall in central Japan even after dawn—
These erratic conditions will continue for a few weeks.
This abnormal weather is
unprecedented and extremely dangerous.
Due to transportation delays,
Yamanote Line trains are suspended.
What's going on?
Let's get off.
I'll ask Mom to pick us up.
It's freezing!
What should we do?
Let's look for a place to spend the night.
I'm sorry, we're completely booked.
Do you have a reservation?
We're full.
Just the three of you?
Do you have your IDs?
We can't accept unaccompanied minors.
Love hotel
It's not about the money.
This isn't a place for kids.
You guys.
Are you runaways?
Sis, Hodaka. Look!
Snowfall?
Is Hina really
connected with the sky?
I'm freezing!
Hey Kei, how is it snowing in August?
Ah, the world has finally gone crazy.
Oh?
It's unbelievable, but it's snowing here in Tokyo.
Kei, wake up. You'll catch a cold.
Asuka—
Asuka! And you too, Kei! Smile!
You look like an old man, Kei.
Once you grow up,
you can't switch between your priorities anymore.
What're you saying? Where's Hodaka?
You kicked him out?!
You're kidding me, right?
I told you, the police showed up.
I've gotta protect myself.
Then you smoked a pack of cigarettes
and got drunk because you felt guilty?
That's so pawthetic.
See, even Rain is saying it.
That's so lame. So last century.
Can you stay away? You smell old.
Huh? You're just as lame.
Hina, was it?
If the story about the Weather Maiden is true,
if she's really a sacrifice, then one day she will—
But that's—
Then, what should've I done?
No need to get so worked up.
It's just a myth.
But, if it really was true...
If you could fix this crazy weather
with just a single human sacrifice,
I'd be fine with it.
Actually, everyone would be fine with it.
A heavy rain and snowfall warning has been issued.
Do not go outside unless it's strictly necessary.
Heavy rain emergency warning
Please follow the evacuation instructions.
Hey, you guys.
It's dangerous to walk around unsupervised.
Are you all siblings?
Uh...
We're going home.
I'm a college student.
They're my younger brothers.
So you're their older sister.
Can you show me your Student ID?
I don't have it on me.
Maybe it's him.
He may be carrying a gun.
Please exercise caution.
And you? Are you in high school?
That's quite a huge backpack.
Could you take your hood off?
Hina.
Run away!
Hey wait!
Stop running away!
Gotcha!
Let me go!
Resisting arrest!
Quit struggling!
Hodaka!
Please, stop running!
Hina?!
Please!
It's dangerous!
Let's go, Hina!
Holy shit.
Let's go take a look.
Master!
It's 28,000 yen a night.
28,000 yen, can you pay it?
Y-yeah, I'll pay.
If you wish to leave early call the reception.
Seems like I'm a wanted man now.
That's kinda cool!
I was really worried, though.
Hodaka, you almost got arrested!
I totally panicked.
That's hilarious.
There's nothing hilarious about it.
The room's spacious!
The bed's huge!
The bath's massive!
Sis, Hodaka!
Let's take a bath together!
Do it alone!
Well then, Hodaka,
let's take a boys-only bath together.
So warm.
What's this?
Wow!
Amazing!
Switch!
There's a lot of stuff here.
What do you want?
Let's try them all, Master.
Are you sure?
I've got my severance pay.
Sis, we're having an excellent dinner tonight!
Looking forward to it!
Sorry for the delay.
Welcome back.
Let's dig in!
Lemme try some of that Hodaka.
The curry's yummy.
Yakisoba's delicious.
I want some too, sis!
Isn't it too early, Hodaka?
Tastes better if you wait only two minutes.
Fortune cookie
Maybe the future ain't that bad
The thing that's in your heart
The thing that will soon disappear
If god really does exist, I have only one wish.
This is more than enough.
This is all we need.
We'll manage somehow.
So please, don't give us anything more.
And don't take anything more from us.
Dear God, it's my only wish.
Please just,
let us be together like this forever.
Hina.
Happy 18th birthday!
It's not too costly, but I picked
something that'd look good on you.
Thank you!
Tell me,
Hodaka, would you like for this rain to stop?
Um,
Yeah.
I was chosen to be a human sacrifice.
What?
Natsumi told me about the sunshine girl's fate.
She gets sacrificed and disappears,
and the weather goes back to normal.
Come on.
They're always telling weird stories.
People don't just disappear.
What are you looking at?
I'm not looking—
I'm looking at you, Hina.
Why are you crying?
The more I pray for sunshine,
the more transparent my body becomes.
I'm sure that if I die this way,
the usual summer will come back.
Take care of Nagi for me.
No!
No way!
You're not going anywhere!
We will live together, the three of us.
Hodaka...
Hina, let's make a promise
to always be together.
I'll get a job.
I'll earn enough for all of us.
If you quit the sunshine girl job,
your body will go back to normal.
So—
I had a dream.
I was still on the island.
I wanted to leave.
I was rushing desperately,
trying to catch up to that light.
Just when I thought I did,
I found myself at a dead end instead.
At that time, I decided
I wanted to reach that light.
And at the edge of it, I found you.
I had a dream.
The day I first met you.
You looked like a lost kitten.
But,
you found a meaning for my existence.
I was happy to make people smile,
so I kept working as the sunshine girl.
I'm glad to have met you.
So don't cry, Hodaka.
What is this place?
Hodaka.
Hina?
Hina, where are you?
Hina!
Hina?
Hodaka, what's wrong?
I can't find Hina anywhere!
Huh, I just had a dream.
Sis was disappearing in the sky.
It can't be...
Open the door!
Open up!
What the—
Morishima Hodaka, correct?
You've been reported missing,
and suspected of unlawful possession of a weapon.
Come to the police station.
Lemme go!
It's okay—
I said let me go!
Hodaka!
Master!
Quit struggling.
Keep going.
After months of rain,
Kanto is finally seeing some sunshine.
It seems unreal, as if it was an illusion.
In the last few hours, the sudden changes—
By 8 am, the temperature was already over 25°C.
Many areas around the Arakawa river are flooded.
It's a miracle!! sunshine!!
The town is flooded.
A dream? Thank you sunshine girl!!
The transportation is still suspended.
I think I saw that dream too.
#MaybeJustMyImagination
The total damage is yet unknown.
It will take at least a few days to recover—
Everyone looks happy under the clear blue sky.
Look at the sky!
Is this for real?
It's sunny!
It cleared up!
The sky is so clear!
I'm so happy I could cry!
The real summer has arrived, at long last.
What're you doing?
Hina
sacrificed herself?
Hina! It can't be real!
Hey!
Hina..
Hina!!
Calm down!
There's one more thing I would like to ask.
The girl with you who disappeared,
was the fifteen year old Amano Hina, right?
Any idea where she might be?
Hina is fifteen year old? And not eighteen?
She faked her resume for her job.
I guess she had to make a living.
But she's still in middle school.
It's compulsory education age.
You weren't aware?
What the heck?
I'm the oldest one.
What a pain.
By any chance, do you know we could find her?
The sky has cleared because
she sacrificed herself in exchange!
And nobody knows about it.
I can't take this.
Such a pain.
Do we need a medical witness?
The sun is out.
Daddy! Did you look outside?
Yeah, I did.
I had a dream about Hina.
I'm sure it was Hina who brought the sunshine back.
Yeah.
Maybe she did.
Ikebukuro Police Station
Excuse me,
Detective, I've got a favor to ask of you.
What is it?
Let me go look for Hina! It's my turn to help her now.
I'll come back as soon as I find her.
I'll listen to you in here, come on.
Let Mr. Yasui know we're about to start interrogating.
Yes, sir.
Hey! Wait!
Stop right there!
Someone stop him!
Come back here!
That brat!
Don't let him escape.
Stop!
Hold it!
Bastard!
Watch where you're goin'!
Cheeky bastard.
Across the street!
Yessir!
Dammit!
Hodaka!
Natsumi?!
What the hell are you doing?
I'm going to find Hina.
Hop on!
That little brat!
Nagi called.
He said Hina has disappeared and you got arrested.
Where is he?
At the Child Consultation Center.
It's kinda fun! We're outlaws now.
So, where to now?
What? Another visitor?
Ayane Hanazawa
Oh, it's girl again.
He must be quite popular.
Nagi!
Ayane! You're here too.
Kana, this is Ayane.
Please to meet you!
Ayane, this is Kana!
Nice to meet you!
And she's Officer Sasaki.
She'll be here with me all day.
Wow, that's so cool!
You're like a VIP, Nagi!
Pleased to meet you.
Today's meeting record
Thank you so much for coming.
Sorry for the sudden news.
When I heard they took you in custody,
my heart almost stopped!
Same for me! My heart's still pounding.
You can feel it, Nagi.
Oh, you're right.
Excuse me.
Yes?
It's my first visit here and I'm kinda nervous.
Huh?
I mean, I need to use the restroom.
Ah, okay, okay.
Thanks, I owe you one.
Jeez, you even call your ex when you need something.
There.
Now look the other way, I need to change.
Mr. Keisuke Suga.
Thanks for yesterday.
Ah, you guys again?
Summer's finally back the way it should be, huh?
I told you I don't know anything about that runaway kid.
Can we check your office for a minute?
H-hey, wait a minute!
What's that for?
Oh, it's flooded.
There's no one in there.
Well, it's a bit embarrassing, so—
Huh? He ran away?
From the police station?
A run down building in Yoyogi?
Yeah, that's where she became a sunshine—
Down!
Hina said she got connected
to the sky on the roof of that building.
So, if I go there, I'm sure...
Oh, crap!
You, on that bike! Stop now!
Hold tight!
Whoa!
Natsumi!
Am I awesome or what?
I feel like I was born for this.
Maybe,
I should become a speed cop!
I doubt they'd hire you now!
As for the reason for his escape,
I think he may be searching for the girl who was with him.
Dear daddy,
I'm out for shopping - Asuka
Well, the story is quite strange.
The boy said she disappeared in
exchange for this good weather.
Don't tell me you actually believe—
Nah, I find it hard to believe.
But, he's throwing his life away,
all because there's a girl he wants to meet so badly.
Makes me a bit envious.
There's no point in telling me that.
Mr. Suga, you...
Huh?
Are you okay?
Why?
I mean, you are
crying.
Oh, crap!
We're jumping in!
It won't go any further.
Go on, Hodaka!
Thank you, Natsumi!
Hodaka!
Run!!
Hina.
Hina!
Hina, you're there, aren't you? Hina!
Hey, Hodaka.
It will clear up now.
It's for you. Don't tell anyone.
Isn't that's your only dinner in like, three days?
Does it hurt?
You're a runaway, aren't you?
But, you can't enjoy Tokyo if its raining all the time.
Younger than me?
I'll be, let's see, eighteen, next month.
Hina's 15th Birthday
You should treat me with respect.
Hodaka, have you had your lunch?
It's fine, don't worry about it.
How's life in Tokyo?
Come to think of it,
I don't feel so suffocated anymore.
Really? Happy to hear that.
I'm in love with this job as a sunshine girl.
Thank you, Hodaka.
Hey, hold up!
Someone's on the tracks.
What's wrong with him?
Hey, you!
It's not safe!
Hey! What're you doing?
It's dangerous!
Stop right there!
What's that?
Hey, look!
What is he doing?
Someone running.
He'll get arrested.
I guess he's an idiot.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Hina!
I made you do that sunshine girl job.
You shouldered every responsibility all alone.
Tell me, Hodaka.
Would you like for this rain to stop?
Mr. Suga?
I was looking for you, Hodaka.
Why?
Do you realize what you're doing?
Hina has disappeared.
It was my fault.
The sunshine girl job was my idea.
Hodaka, you—
It's my turn to help her now!
I need to hurry.
Hey, wait a sec!
Where are you—
I can go to heaven through there!
What?!
What are you saying?
She's in the sky!
I'll use the emergency stairs—
Hodaka!
She can't be up there.
I have to help her!
Get a grip!
Calm down, Hodaka.
Just go back to the police station.
They'll understand.
You've done nothing wrong.
If you keep running away, it'll be too late.
You know that.
We've located the suspect's car.
Moving in to apprehend him.
Don't worry, I'll come with you.
Let's explain everything to them, okay?
Let me go! Please!
Calm down!
Get off me!
Hodaka, you idiot!
Get out of my way!
Hodaka. That's—
Just let me go see Hina.
Born into this world with nothing in my hands
I keep on going around in circles in this gap of eternity
Morishima Hodaka!
In the era where only the wise and resigned are the winners
Drop the gun!
Hey, hey, hey, wait a minute!
It's a misunderstanding, I'll explain.
Where can we find a moment to breath
Right, Hodaka?
You...
Put the gun down, Morishima.
Don't make me shoot.
Even the kings and gods turn a blind eye
Hodaka.
C'mon Hodaka, drop that stuff.
But we all know deep in our heart
What's wrong with you guys?
He's just a kid!
Just leave me alone!
Why're you getting in my way!?
Destiny is very much like the number on a die
You don't know anything.
You pretend you don't!
I just
want to see her
Much like the usual whim of the gods
one more time!
About the magic of courage, hope and bonds
Got him!
Let me go!
Adults don't find use for them, so they look away
Take your hands off Hodaka, you assholes!
Even then, your will from that day is still here with me
You bastard—
Go! Hodaka!!
As the central pillar of all my justice
Stop!
Hodaka!
Nagi!
Even if the world turns its back on us
Hey—
It's all your fault, isn't it?
Bring my sis back!
You are here right now, standing your ground
I need to know if there's still anything that love can do
I need to know if there's still anything that I can do
Because you had given me the courage
I want to use it all for you
I need to know if there's still anything that love can do
Oh God.
Please.
Please!
Fish
in the sky?
Hina!!
Hina!
In exchange for wings that can fly in the sky
Hodaka!
We chose to have hands which can hold each other
Even then, we were fascinated with the sky
Hodaka!
Hina! Jump!
I wonder if its a sin to let dreams overlap
When summer looks at the fall that arrives
Hina, I found you!
Hodaka!
Don't let go of my hands.
I imagine what kind of face it makes
Okay!
Is it admiration, or is it love
All while knowing that the dream won't come true
Hina!
Hodaka!
Today is the one day in the millennia when gravity sleeps
Let's go back together, Hina!
We stand in the blind spot of the sun, ready to depart from this planet
But, if I do, the weather will—
It's okay!
You've done enough!
When he had awoken from his sleep, we head to a place of no return
You don't have to be the sunshine girl anymore!
On the sound of "go" we slam our feet on the ground, to a planet far away
Let's go
Just a bit more, we'll reach past our destiny
I don't care if we never see sunshine again.
Just a bit more, we'll reach past civilization
I want you more than any blue sky.
Let's go
Just a bit more, we'll reach past our destiny
The weather
Just a bit more
can stay crazy!
We are the sails for our dreams
We get past the nights to approach the coming day
Now, we are filled with expectations
Together we say "We'll do something about the rest"
While we are not fearless, we won't stop
Even if we try to avoid danger, we cannot help it when it arrives
But our love tells us, its voice tells us
It tells us to "go!"
Make a wish for yourself,
Hina.
Okay!
Hodaka.
All the love songs have been sung to death
In countless movies they've been told to death
Though you and I were born into such a barren land
But still, I need to know
It started raining again that day, and never stopped.
Slowly sinking Tokyo into the water.
And it's still raining even now,
three years later.
What can I say?
Congratulations on your graduation!
Graduation Ceremony
Morishima!
Um, you're moving to Tokyo, aren't you?
Huh? Yeah.
Come on, ask him! It's now or never.
Could this be
the first time
You know, Morishima!
There's something I've always wanted to ask you.
someone proposes to me?
Um, Is it true that...
Ahh!
Is it true that you're wanted by the police in Tokyo?
Eh?
That summer three years ago,
I was arrested and put on trial.
They put me on probation until graduation.
The island, my parent's house and the school
were the same old places where I was supposed to live.
But each day, I was silently waiting for graduation.
Since that day,
I haven't seen Hina.
I have no idea how I'll feel
after seeing how much Tokyo has changed,
nor what I'll say to her.
Tomorrow's weather for the Kanto region.
University Entrance Guide
It will rain again all day.
Now I just need to find a part-time job.
Job Search
Bread Wrapping and Sale
Hair Dye
The high will be 15°C, slightly hotter than most areas.
Education for the
"New Geology Generation"
Oh, right.
Speaking of part time jobs...
It's still there!
1 request
It was a sunshine girl request from 2 years ago.
Next stop: Takashimadaira.
Look who's here. Are you alone?
What about the sunshine girl?
She's not a sunshine girl anymore.
I came here just to tell you about that.
Oh, please don't trouble yourself.
You moved here.
You used to live in an older house downtown.
That entire area is underwater now.
I'm sorry.
What do you have to apologize for?
Um...
Did you know, that whole area used to be under the sea.
Until about 200 years ago.
Tokyo was just a bay back when it was called Edo.
Humans and the weather changed it little by little.
So you know, I think it has just
gone back to how it was before.
What the heck?
You've been thinking that crap for three years?
It's not like that—
You're about to be a university student
but you're still acting like a kid.
But that day, we—
You two caused all of this?
You altered the nature of this world?
Don't gimme that crap, dummy.
Get off your high horse.
Check this, I went on a date with my daughter.
Natsumi and Nagi were in the way, though.
Quit sweating the small stuff.
And why haven't you seen her yet?
What were you doing this whole time?
I mean, I was on probation and didn't want to trouble her.
She doesn't even have a cellphone.
And I'm so nervous I don't even know what to say to her.
Ah, Rain?
You've sure grown up.
Come on now, get going!
I've got work to do.
Just go to her place already.
Thanks for your time.
Come back again.
Hey.
Don't sweat it, young man.
The world's always been crazy anyway.
Next stop: Hamamatsucho.
Aren't you positive.
You think?
Looking forward to the picnic.
Yeah!
It used to be under the sea.
The world has always been crazy.
So, nobody's to be blamed that the world is like this.
Is that what I should tell her?
The whole world rests upon your tiny shoulders
I'm the only one who sees it and I'm on the verge of tears
You notice that and ask "Are you alright?"
No! That's not right.
And I reply in haste, "I'm alright," but...
On that day, I— no, we,
we did change the world!
I made a choice.
Why is it that you're asking me such a thing
I've chosen her.
I chose this world!
I've chosen to live here!
When it's you who's about to fall apart
Hina!
Hodaka!
What's the matter, Hodaka?
Are you alright?
Yeah.
Hina, I'm sure
we'll be alright!
The whole world rests upon your tiny shoulders
I'm the only one who sees it, and I'm on the verge of tears
You notice that and ask "Are you alright?"
And I reply in haste, "I'm alright," but...
Why is it that you're asking me such a thing
When it's you who's about to fall apart
Even though I'm small and incapable of obtaining
this big dream I have now that's overflowing
That dream is for you to be alright, I want you to be alright.
I don't just want you to be alright
I want you to be the alright that's alright to you
Born into this world with nothing in my hands
I keep on going around in circles in this gap of eternity
In the era where only the wise and resigned are the winners
Where can we find a moment to breath
Even the kings and gods turn a blind eye
But we all know deep in our heart
About the magic of courage, hope and bonds
Adults don't find use for them, so they look away
Even then, your will from that day is still here with me
As the central pillar of all my justice
Even if the world turns its back on us
You are here right now, standing your ground
I need to know if there's still anything that love can do
I need to know if there's still anything that I can do
Because you had given me the courage
I want to use it all for you
Because you had shared with me this love
It would be meaningless without you here
I need to know if there's still anything that love can do
I need to know if there's still anything that I can do
Why were we shown dreams, even though we own nothing
Why were we given hope when our lives have an end
Why were we handed only things that would slip through our grasps
Even then, as we cling onto it, would you call us unsightly
Or are we beautiful, please tell us
All the love songs have been sung to death
In countless movies they've been told to death
Though you and I were born into such a barren land
But still, I need to know
There is still something that love can do
There is still something that I can do