To Icy Tail's first solo performance!
Cheers!
All right!
Tomo here is paying for everything, so let's go nuts!
Excuse me!
Could we get ten orders each of
beef tongue, grilled beef, sirloin steak, beef tripe and...
Please, no more!
Man, solo gigs are the best, aren't they?
Right? Everyone is there just for us.
And that many people, too.
The dressing room was so spacious.
Usually there's barely any room for us.
Eh? That's supposed to be the best part?
We did it, Tomoya-senpai!
Our new game's promotion is going great!
Sure is, and it's all thanks to your hard work.
I did finish that key visual at ten this morning, though.
Thanks to that, we barely got the merch done in time...
Don't worry about it.
You've been working yourself to death for this.
It's our job as fellow circle members to back you up.
Megumi-san...
The problem is that even though everyone's giving it their all,
there is still one member who hasn't contributed anything.
Katou...
Let me guess, you're talking about me?
I wasn't exactly trying to be subtle.
Me-Megumi-san?
I'm not a fan of taking on work
that anyone else could do, you know?
I think that as a member of the circle,
trying to help out where you can is a given.
I wish you'd consider how much
careful effort I put in to prepare for this.
You do understand how much it's worth, right?
Hey, Michiru.
Why do these two hate each other so much?
What? Why would I know?
If you're asking Micchi, you must truly be lost.
She's the most clueless person in the room.
That's why she could never join in on the Holy Girlfriend War.
Excuse me, what is this war I'm just getting to hear about?
Listen, Katou-san.
The advertisement I put out on Twitter has hit over five thousand retweets.
Which means, I've already spread the news of our work
to over ten times the size of this concert's audience.
I'm pretty sure that's just advertising,
which doesn't help in making the game at all.
Selling merch at a concert isn't getting the game done any faster either, is it?
Ahh! It's on fire!
I told you not to put it all there!
Katou-san has changed, hasn't she?
Heh? What was that?
Just thinking how we were always in the spotlight in the TV series,
so now it's hard to adjust to being side characters in the movie.
It's only fair. We're not part of the circle anymore, after all.
The probably cast us as bottom-of-the-barrel actresses.
Thanks for coming here tonight.
Eriri, Kasumigaoka-senpai.
No, we should be thanking you.
I'm glad you invited us, Megumi.
So how are you doing?
Good.
Well, work has been hell, though.
Fields Chronicle is a huge project, right?
With the scenario written by Kasumigaoka Utaha,
I'll have a hard time believing that.
I see we are getting along as well as ever.
You two really are close, as usual.
What gave you that idea? All we ever do is argue.
You guys are getting closer too, aren't you?
Really, since when were you able
to argue with Hashima like that?
Oh, that...
Well, you know, you have to sterilize any
foreign objects that make it into your circle.
Aren't you in luck, then? That the all-important
Sawamura-san here was so kind and easy to tame.
Huh? What are you implying?
Rinri-kun,
come over here for a second.
Utaha-senpai...
We haven't seen each other in so long.
Let's have a good, long talk.
S-Sure...
But...
You don't need to worry about what happened back then.
Sure, it was my first time, but I don't regret doing it.
Ah, please! That's enough!
Ah! I remember!
What happened, Eriri?
Get this, Megumi.
Please! Stop!
This woman... This wench!
Katou... uh... that was just...
You really shouldn't tease Eriri so much.
Aren't you two supposed to be
getting along and working together?
Oh? So you think this is between just me and Eriri?
Well, if that's what you're talking about,
then we still have plenty to discuss.
How about you go sit at another table, Aki-kun?
How have you been, Rinri-kun?
Great. Until just now.
What the matter?
No matter how much you regret it,
the fact that you've hurt me so much,
and that you were my first man won't ever change.
I didn't regret anything until you started talking!
You're so clingy!
A college student still drooling
over a high schooler? Disgusting.
What about you? Still stuck on that
childhood friend you've betrayed twice?
How's that for sad?
I'm perfectly fine.
After all, he forgave me both times.
That just means your relationship
was reset back to nothing, right?
Will you two ever grow up?
So how is it going?
Blessing Software's new game?
Leave it to me. Just watch, you two.
This time, I'll make it with my own two hands.
A gal-game that everyone will be thrilled to play!
This is only your second game, and you went and
wrote the scenarios for all five heroines all by yourself.
Aren't you determined?
You were just a moe-loving pig until last year.
Well, I don't think that's changed.
Uh, well, you know...
Tomoya-senpai might be a disgusting moe-lover,
but his scenario here is really good.
I get so excited every time he finishes a new scene!
I'm like, what poses should I use here?
What expressions should I use in this scene?
Of course, there are still a few issues.
Like the blonde, twin-tailed heroine,
or the similarly-clichéd heroine with long, black hair.
Are they really even necessary?
Though to make up for that, there's the cute and courageous underclassmen heroine.
So overall, the scenario is still legendary.
You sure you're talking about just the scenario here?
Besides the scenario, with Michiru-senpai's BGM, Megumi-san's direction, and my art,
I'm sure it will turn out to be perfect!
So, even if you two are working
on a big project with a huge budget,
if it gets delayed and turns out to be trash,
it will just end up in the garbage bin.
Don't come crying to us if that happens.
I'm the one crying here.
Right back at you, Hashima Izumi.
I admire that reckless confidence of yours.
Then, can you promise me?
That you'll make a legendary game that can compete with ours?
That's a given.
When it comes down to it, our teamwork is second to none.
Don't underestimate us.
Let's get started.
What are you doing, Kousaka-san?
Worming your way into a get-together like this?
You're insane. Being rude has its limits, you know?
Object all you want. I'm just here
to give feedback as soon as possible.
I told you to sent it over at night.
This is what happens when you send it during the day.
We forced ourselves to finish things early because we had plans later!
Unfortunately for you, those plans are canceled.
It's a private discussion, Tomoya-kun.
I know that...
No!
This has to look like this!
What are you doing?
That won't look any good on screen!
Are you retarded, kid?
How is this armor supposed to work?
If we do things your way,
the design would be way too plain!
Think about the overall balance!
This one piece is floating!
Designing this is my job, isn't it?
So just shut up and let me draw it!
Not if you're going to give me this bullshit!
Rethink this whole thing from the top and try again!
Fine!
Hey, Iori... uh...
Well, we are in Akihabara after all.
I've told Akane-san many times not to discuss work in public like this.
It's hardly a private meeting anymore.
U-Uh, please don't take pictures or share this anywhere...
Ugh, this has no impact at all.
What the hell is this scene?
You just can't appreciate the subtlety!
Please just stop arguing and eat!
What aren't you understanding?
This scene where Philene dies
is supposed to be the climax of the first half!
And the spoilers were out
before the climax even existed...
You're the one who doesn't get it!
Describing this scene slowly and quietly
can have an even greater impact!
You want me to throw in some boring, run-of-the-mill crying scene?
Players have seen enough of that!
Then give it more of an edge!
Make it run through the players' hearts like a blade!
If you can't handle that, all that's left is this pretentious hot air!
Excuse me...
What?!
You're bothering the other customers...
Ah, sorry, we've caused you so much trouble.
I'll take care of all their bills.
You get what I'm saying, right?
Eat all you want, and forget everything you heard here.
Beef tongue, grilled beef, sirloin steak, beef tripe,
I'll take everything you've got!
Out of meat for the day
How to Raise a Boring Girlfriend. Fine
Sorry, I don't have the appetite.
When did you go to sleep?
Well, I was planning to stay awake until everyone got here.
How are things progressing?
Who was it that, back in July,
said he could take it easy over summer break
because only the main heroine's route was left?
Well, that was only a little while ago.
And how much time is left before summer break ends?
Just a little while...
Izumi-chan might be stuck without
work waiting on the scenario soon.
Ah, I'm sorry.
I'm in a slump. What am I supposed to do?
Which part are you on now?
Meguri 15.
After the player makes the final choice to select Meguri as heroine
(start of Meguri route)
Ah, I'm not too familiar with this stuff,
but even I can tell that this is important.
That's right.
The event that kicks off Meguri's route.
The big climax at the turning point of the story!
This part has to be perfect!
That's right!
I need to write the greatest scene in the game!
So, what's the plan?
Hey, Katou.
How am I supposed to get around my writer's block?
You're asking me?
What else can I do? I'm stuck! Help me out!
And this feeling that you're not really
relying on me, is just in my head, right?
Well, in that case...
How about trying to learn from other people's work?
I see. We shouldn't underestimate
the work of our predecessors, after all.
Or maybe you could just keep writing
one attempt after the other for now.
Good idea.
Hundred kilobytes of trash
is still better than a zero kilobyte masterpiece.
Or maybe you could just
stop thinking about it and get some rest.
Absolutely! It's very much possible that a group
of little elves will finish my work while I'm asleep!
You don't really have the time
to try out that option right now, though.
Hey, Katou. What should I do?
I mean, instead of asking me,
why don't you try asking an expert?
You mean...
Hasn't she been though the same thing
that you're going through right now?
Maybe Kasumigaoka-senpai could help—
But... if I asked Utaha-senpai for advice...
Would it be okay with you?
Why wouldn't it be okay?
Well, that time at the barbecue place...
Kasumigaoka-senpai may not be in our circle anymore, but if it's for our game, I think I could tolerate her.
Wait a minute!
Wait one minute, Katou!
Your words and expression don't line up at all!
Well, anyway.
Hyoudou-san and Izumi-chan should be here soon.
Why don't you at least wash your face?
Y-Yeah...
Event Number: Meguri 15
I was running some errands and ended up near your place. You home?
'Sup.
It's too bad Kasumi-sensei was out.
What were you there for today?
She sent over a revised scenario this morning,
but it's still no good.
You should have asked her before driving over.
I don't want to hear that from the guy who was
standing outside her apartment like a stalker.
You'll have to be bolder than that
if you want to get her back, you know?
Your position as head of your circle aside, as a man—
That is not why I was there.
I just wanted to ask for some help with my scenario.
Besides, I don't want to hear that from you.
I was the one who discovered Kashiwagi Eri and Kasumi Utako.
They were well known in the doujin and novel worlds
long before you even noticed them.
But still, making a game with their talents
combined was my idea which you stole.
Do you have to be so mean? And to your savior, at that?
What? Since when did you—
Enaka-san?
Even after I drove you all the way to Nasu Kougen.
In the middle of the night, too!
I, uh...
I missed four deadlines thanks to that, you know?
You have no idea how much bullshit I got from my editor.
I-I'm sorry!
Wait a minute, Kousaka-san...
Did seeing Eriri's art back then
made you want to work with her?
Now that you mention it, yeah.
Guess that makes me your unlucky charm.
Let me out! Stop the car!
Good idea. I'm tired of all this driving. Let's grab a bite.
That's not what I meant!
Uh... Kousaka-san...
Shut up, I'm trying to focus.
Uh, are you actually reading it?
Don't worry, I haven't missed a word.
That's inhuman.
Hey! You're definitely not laughing
out of appreciation for my writing, are you?
What the heck? It's so creepy.
Especially this blonde haired heroine who cries after a kiss.
What am I reading? What kinda crazy pure maiden is she?
Even in 2D, a girl this extreme is rare.
You don't have to explain every detail!
M-My sides!
Just stop...
Please, no more...
This long, black haired heroine's
mood swings are pretty insane too.
Normally she's so sadistic.
Why the heck does she become a shy little girl in bed?
Just so you know, they're just
sleeping in the same bed, nothing more!
Then what's with this
"E-Even though I'm usually like that, this is actually my first time..."
What the hell is that supposed to mean?
Please don't act it out!
So this is the main heroine's scenario...
It's only partially finished, though.
H-How is it? I...
I want to hear your honest opinion.
You progressed a lot while writing this.
It's a far cry from what you wrote for the sub-heroines.
Earlier it was a disgusting mess of a script,
but it becomes a lot more refined in the main heroine's route.
I never would have expected for you to change so much.
Amateurs who stumble onto the right path are scary.
I'm glad to hear it!
Truth is, I wasn't sure if I was headed in the right direction.
I could tell things were different and thought
I was in a slump, but I had actually improved!
I was actually making progress!
Thank you so much.
I feel like I've regained my confidence thanks to—
You...
Moron!
The one thing you got right was doubting yourself!
It's a good thing you slumped! It's good that you stopped!
You were this close to turning everything into a pile of trash!
What?
Your script is getting so polished it's bland.
What is this inoffensive garbage?
Are you getting shy? That's not like you.
But just now, weren't you saying that this was a far cry from all the previous routes?
How the hell is this heap of dense shit
supposed to compete with a polished turd?
In Cherry Blessing, weren't you the one
who wrote that painfully positive route?
There's no way Kasumi-sensei could write something so corny.
The first half of your scenario here is basically the same thing.
That's... well...
Even I couldn't have ever written something like that.
That's your weapon.
Kousaka-san...
Your strength is in writing these dumb otaku fantasies!
It's exciting. It's embarrassing.
It makes you want to look away!
It's hot garbage that you end up craving for!
If you're complimenting me,
could you not call my work garbage?
The disgusting otaku of the world will gladly eat it up.
If you want to get better, focus on those fantasies!
Let your inane desires flow!
Flirt with your overly-cunning heroine like crazy!
That's just...
That's right, it's like masturbation!
Just like masturbation, young man!
Masturbation that makes you feel amazing!
Masturbation that everyone wants to see!
Take something as incredibly embarrassing
as masturbation, and show it off!
Excuse me!
So, what are you gonna do now?
Wanna stop by Kasumi-sensei's place with me?
I'm gonna head home.
Alright, then. I'll see you later, I guess.
Kousaka-san...
For today... uh...
When you've finished the game, save me a copy.
I'll pick it up at Winter Comiket.
Sure!
Hold up! Don't drive! Get a taxi!
So that's how it is, Katou!
Megumi
Uh... I'm not really sure what you mean...
The reason behind my slump.
In the end, I need to focus on my disgusting fantasies!
I need to masturbate more!
Megumi
Sorry, that came out wrong.
What I wanted to say was that I need to
focus on writing self-satisfying fantasies.
And so you have to write something even more disgusting?
I don't know if I could stand that.
Maybe girls wouldn't be able to stand it!
But guys like me will lap it up! It makes our heart flutter!
So basically, isn't this the worst possible situation for me?
So anyway, before starting Meguri 15,
I rewrote Meguri 01 through Meguri 14.
Hey, Aki-kun, what's today's date again?
Um... August 31st.
And when does our summer break end?
August 31st.
Mind if I say something else?
Don't! I don't care about any homework or tests!
This year, I decided to put everything I can into this game!
We're third years, we'll have college entrance exams soon.
Anyway, I'll send over the updated Meguri scenario.
Give me a video call once you've read it
so we can talk it over while going through.
Well, look, Aki-kun...
Do you know what time it is?
I don't care what time it is!
Later!
I've finished reading.
You actually called me back today itself...
Okay, bye.
N-No! Thank you so much! Katou-sama! Megumi-sama!
Let's just start going over everything!
Event Number: Meguri 04
Ah, this scene is just no good.
The protagonist's actions, dialogue, attitude,
and basically everything about him.
Everything?
You know, if a guy is this self-absorbed,
no girl would be able to stand him.
It's a man's fantasy!
In a story like this, that attitude
awakens the girl's womanly instincts!
She'll think, "Well, I guess I'll play along," and it'll be fine!
In reality, she'd think, "Well, I guess we're breaking up,"
and just end things right there.
We're not talking about the real world!
We're talking about men's fantasies!
But still, you can't go that far.
R-Really?
You need to be more considerate of the heroine.
Even if it's just once in a while, treat her nicely, okay?
So how should I fix this?
Isn't that something you should come up with?
You're being awfully strict.
Event Number: Meguri 14
Absolutely terrible.
How?
I mean, isn't this event right before the one
that starts the heroine's route?
Yeah, it is...
In other words, isn't this the event where Meguri begins to fall for the protagonist?
Meguri and the protagonist make up
Why is such an ordinary event the one that raises her flag?
I mean, it's as if you've been in her route the whole time.
What does that—
Anyway, that's why it's terrible.
You should... um... change it a little.
No. There's no way I'm changing this one.
Of all the scenes I've written, this one is my favorite.
I love this scene.
Then why are you asking for my input?
You can just write it yourself, can't you?
Hey, Katou...
Cheer up, would you?
It's not like I'm mad at you or anything.
Okay, then can we take a look at Meguri 15 now?
Just the plot.
I really want to know how you feel about it.
You can just write it however you want to.
I told you before, didn't I?
This has to be the best scene in the game.
Event Number: Meguri 15
I really need you for this.
You're so self-absorbed and pushy, Aki-kun.
Sorry.
Yeah... I think I'd change at least a part of this.
Which part?
Here, when something sad happens, and the protagonist is crying.
He thought he had lost everything, but then she returned back to him.
The protagonist begins to cry.
So, having the protagonist cry was not a good idea after all?
Having something like that raise a flag isn't right, is it?
No, not that.
The problem here is with the heroine.
"Would it be okay for me to cry?"
Meguri embraces the protagonist.
She shouldn't hug him here.
Really?
That's right.
Doesn't it mean that Meguri's flag wasn't raised?
It doesn't. Not in the slightest.
Her flag was raised long before this part.
So here, she should let the protagonist cry his heart out.
Do you think the players would understand that?
If they don't understand that much,
they'll never be able to enter the Meguri route.
I see.
Yeah, okay.
If that's how you think, I'll touch it up a bit.
Keep up the good work, Tomoya-kun.
Katou, did you just...
Well, you know...
After this scene, they start calling
each other by their first names, right?
After that, Meguri and the protagonist start calling each other by their first names.
Y-Yeah, in the game, sure.
So it's fine, right?
I see. I guess it is.
Isn't it?
Okay...
Well, I'll get a little more work done before going to sleep.
Bye, Megumi.
Sure.
Bye, Tomoya-kun.
Uh...
Hey... Megumi?
What is it, Tomoya-kun?
You can end the call now.
I'm not going to sleep anyway.
Anything wrong with me watching?
Not really...
So don't worry about it. Just pretend I'm not here.
How am I supposed to do that?
Good night.
G-Good morning, Megumi.
Good morning, Tomoya-kun.
What a relief...
What'd you mean?
I thought this might end up like that
time I called out to you back in April,
and you just started laughing all of a sudden.
I absolutely 100% don't remember doing that.
You did! You definitely did!
You saw my new glasses, and were all "ugh."
If you keep this up,
I'm going back to calling you "Aki-kun."
My apologies!
Please forgive me, Megumi-san!
All right.
So what time did you end up getting to sleep?
Truth is, I basically didn't—
Tomoya-senpai—
Can you still write without getting any sleep?
Huh? Are those two...
Megumi, Tomoya. Morning!
Oh, good morning.
Good morning, Eriri.
I wonder if you just have to be that dense to be a genius.
I finally finished it, Meguri 15.
You couldn't write anything for the entire month,
but once you got started, it only took one night, huh?
Anyway, this is the best thing I've written.
It's my masterpiece, with both of our hearts in it.
Go ahead, have a look.
Sorry for the wait!
Here's your iced coffee. Please enjoy!
This might take a while.
You don't have to sit here and watch.
Don't worry about it. Just try not to get
distracted and concentrate on reading.
How was it?
It was so embarrassing I wanted to stop reading.
All right!
That wasn't a compliment.
If a girl feels embarrassed reading it,
I'm sure the guys will get all excited by it!
Thanks, Katou.
Like I said, I wasn't complimenting it.
And you shouldn't be calling me "Katou."
Right. Sorry, Megumi.
So? What comes next?
Well...
The protagonist and Meguri have finally gotten together...
Is Meguri going to lose her memory?
Or maybe the protagonist will die?
Did you forget the entire idea behind this game?
I didn't forget it.
I wish I could, though.
Our first priority is showing off how amazing the heroine is.
So naturally, after this...
They're going to flirt like crazy, right?
Yeah, I figured...
So t-tonight...
Are we going to do it?
W-Well... If you're tired, we don't have to.
I'm fine.
Well...
It's for the game, after all.
Yeah.
Event Number: Meguri 16
So, is this what you wrote up based on our meeting last night?
Yeah.
The first all-out flirting event between the
protagonist and Meguri after they start dating.
Does that mean you're writing a second, or even a third?
Well, I'll think about that after this is finished.
Right, I wanted you to take a look at this part here.
"Meguri trembled slightly. But after a short while,
I found her small hand tightly grasping my own."
"Lots of people were waiting at the train station alongside us."
"Hidden amongst that crowd was a newly-formed couple."
"Enjoying the innocent thrill of performing this small act of affection in public."
Okay. After reading that
incredibly embarrassing excerpt out loud,
what is it that you want from me?
W-What do you think?
The heroine's reaction here...
I think it's incredibly moe, but...
And what would I know about that?
I thought that maybe you could help me express the heroine's feelings here.
There are plenty of ways she could react to this, after all.
And you want me to decide?
I figured that reading it out at an actual train
station would help set the mood a bit better.
How would I know how she'd feel?
It's fine if it's not perfect, could you still—
How could I know if I've never experienced it?
This is such an old-school event.
It's the perfect event for otaku guys.
Well, if you want to know whether this
is embarrassing or not, it absolutely is.
I know, right!
But couldn't this be made into an
even more of a special moment?
How is that?
Um, I think... maybe...
With a more intimate grip?
And what exactly would that be?
I mean...
Oh, yeah...
She's the main heroine after all,
you have to go at least this far.
Still, isn't this a bit too intimate?
You've had more intimate contact
with a certain other person, haven't you?
Did you have to bring that up right now?
You've even kissed, haven't you?
Come on, how am I supposed to use this in the script?
Event Number: Meguri 20
You're not sure where to go next?
Right.
For Meguri 20, I have two ideas on how to handle it.
The first?
To write a climax for the scenario.
Like some sort of large event?
Right.
For example, Meguri could lose her memory.
Or maybe the protagonist could die.
Uh...
I mean, we've showed off the heroine's appeal a lot by now, right?
So I thought maybe we should change things up a bit.
I haven't decided exactly what to do yet, though.
Alright. What's your other idea?
Well, without really changing anything,
we could just keep up the lovey-dovey events.
Until the end?
All the way.
I'm not sure if players would like it
if we go with that kind of half-hearted ending.
The story would be a bit lacking in variety...
I don't think it would be lacking at all.
Getting into a relationship with the
person you love takes a lot of courage.
I don't really think calling that half-hearted is fair.
So you don't think we need any sort of big climax?
I don't.
Okay.
Yup.
Alright, then let's go with that.
No last-minute serious developments.
I'll add even more lovey-dovey dates,
kissing, and that kind of stuff instead.
Yeah, I get it.
Keep it up.
That takes care of our next scouting trip location.
Saturday, September 23rd, at one o'clock.
At Ikebukuro.
Let's take a walk around town and try to come up with material.
I'll send the details over to you later. See ya.
Wait a minute.
About going around town next Saturday...
Do you have other plans?
No, it's not that.
I don't have anything else planned...
But you know what day that is, don't you?
Your birthday.
We're just going out to gather material, right?
Maybe.
Are we not?
Which would you rather it be?
That's not fair.
A-Alright then...
If I said it wasn't just for
gathering material, would you still come?
Absolutely.
I'll go no matter what the reason is.
I'll look forward to it.
Y-Yeah?
Thanks.
I don't know how it'll go Tomoya-kun...
Don't blame me for whatever happens.
What do you—
I'm sorry, Megumi.
I can't make it.
It's kind of hard to explain right now,
but someone's life is in danger.
I'll call you later and tell you all about it.
I'll definitely call and explain everything.
Tomoya!
Eriri, Utaha-senpai...
Patient's Name                      Akane Kousaka
Your business card?
We exchanged cards when we
ran into each other the other day.
Apparently she collapsed in front of a convenience store,
and didn't have any ID on her.
Just my business card in her pocket.
She never carried any cards or a license or anything.
The only thing in her bag was always cash.
What did the doctor say?
She had a stroke.
When the ambulance arrived, she couldn't even talk.
Apparently that's been getting better, but...
But?
She... can't move her right hand.
Wait a minute.
She's an artist! A manga artist!
Isn't that like losing everything?
No, they say that she'll be able to
draw again when she gets better.
And what if she doesn't?
If you take away an artist's ability to draw,
how are they supposed to stay in the fray?
Eriri...
She's the greatest...
No, she's a monster capable of competing at my level!
If you take all that away, she might just lose herself.
It's still too early to make assumptions.
We can't help but worry about the worst-case situation.
What we should do for now is hope that she recovers.
No mater how long it takes.
What's going to happen with Fields Chronicle?
Can you afford this kind of setback?
Don't worry about it. Our work is nearly done.
We'll be finished after making a few more tweaks.
That's good. If that's the case...
What are you saying, Kasumigaoka Utaha?
We have no idea how the game is progressing as a whole.
Um, Sawamura-san!
We don't even know what revisions we have left!
Kousaka Akane handled everything between us and Maruzu.
Is that true?
Maruzu doesn't directly communicate with us.
In order to preserve the integrity of our
work, she acted as an in-between for us.
As much as I really, truly, didn't like it.
But now we'll actually have to face them, won't we?
I'll take care of the arrangements
for Akane's hospitalization and check in on her later.
Are you really going to have to do that?
She may have connections from work, but she doesn't
have friends or the best relationship with her parents.
Well, that's understandable.
I feel like Kousaka Akane wouldn't want to hear that from you.
Anyway, the rest of you should head home.
You still have work to do, right?
We do, but without her direction, we're not sure how to proceed.
Don't worry about it.
I'll talk to Maruzu about how Fields Chronicle is progressing.
Well, Hashima-kun and I will.
Hashima?
He has known Akane for a long time,
and she's trusted him with plenty in the past.
Go ahead and update Hashima-kun with where you're at.
Glad to be working with you, Kashiwagi Eri-sensei.
You're the last person I wanted to work with.
Who knows what you'll get me into.
Relax, I wouldn't dare mess with
one of Akane-san's team members.
Besides, I'm a member of Blessing Software.
Once this is over, I'm heading back to my circle.
How about you head back right now?
I don't need you for anything.
Yeah.
Sounds like her life isn't in danger, for now at least.
Anyway, there's nothing left for me to do here.
I can head over there right now...
Oh, makes sense.
It's too late now, isn't it?
Alright, then I'll see you at the circle meeting tomorrow.
Sorry, Megumi.
For not celebrating your birthday with you.
I'm really sorry.
Happy birthday.
Happy birthday, Katou-chan!
We're a day late, but happy birthday, Megumi-san!
Yeah, happy birthday,
and uh...
Um, thank you, everyone.
Okay!
Let's grab some cake and get this meeting started.
We're still one member short, though.
Oh, Onii-chan is...
Something came up, so Iori won't be able
to join our circle activities for a little while.
It doesn't really matter if he's here or not anyway.
Megumi-san?
What? Come on!
I wanted to ask him about our performance next month!
Oh, I can handle Icy Tail for—
I'll take care of it.
Eh?
Are you really okay with that, Katou-chan?
Well, I might not be able to negotiate as well as him,
but I should be able to handle working with the venue or some small changes.
More importantly, our circle leader here needs to
focus on finishing up the game's scenario, right?
Y-Yeah, thanks. I'll leave it to you.
Alright!
Then I'll be counting on you, Katou-chan!
Whew, that's such a relief!
I'm sorry for getting in the way of your circle again.
Nah, it's fine.
I don't even know what that guy was doing here.
He's useless when it comes to actual game development, that's for sure.
You make it sound like he's useful for anything at all.
Wait, do you actually hate Hashima even more than I do?
Anyway, how's the work on your game coming along?
Great!
Or at least, I wish it was.
Oh...
Yeah.
You're my best friend, so I won't hide anything from you.
Honestly, losing Kousaka Akane hurt us a lot.
Megumi
Your deadline was coming up, right?
Shouldn't everything nearly be done?
Yeah, but we're lagging behind on reviews.
Especially about keeping things in line with earlier entries.
I'm no art director, just an artist, after all.
But if you think it's okay, shouldn't that be enough?
This game...
No...
This is the one game that, for myself
and for a bunch of people, needs to be perfect.
As Sawamura Eriri...
No, as Kashiwagi Eri, I can't let the slightest mistake through.
I have to draw as fast as possible.
With this game, I have to make everyone
acknowledge me as the greatest illustrator.
If I don't, I'll have left the circle for nothing.
I would have left you and Tomoya behind for nothing.
Eriri...
Well, don't worry about it.
It's just my own selfish goal, after all.
That's not true. It's probably not just your goal.
That's true. Maybe Kasumigaoka Utaha feels the same way.
Anyway, I still have work to finish up.
Yeah, talk to you later.
Oh, right!
It's a bit late, but happy birthday, Megumi.
Let's go out and celebrate together once we're finished!
Thank you.
You're wrong, Eriri.
There's still one more person...
Someone who's been watching you for the last 10 years.
Well, that meeting with Maruzu was beyond hellish.
Don't just start the conversation
with that kind of depressing news!
I guess I've learned one thing.
A pure creative-type like Akane-san
should never be left in charge of a project timeline.
Don't just laugh it off, explain.
I don't wanna hear it, but tell me what's going on.
The deadline Maruzu set has long since passed.
Wait a minute.
How did that happen?
Kashiwagi Eri and Kasumi Utako...
The more they were pressured, the more they grew.
Asked for retake after retake, continued getting better.
And Akane-san became obsessed with that growth.
How long did Kousaka-san say it
would take to finish everything?
Another month.
That long?
But Maruzu is done waiting.
They're just going to scrap any
events with unfinished art or scripts.
From there, they say
they'll rearrange everything to fit together.
Apparently, they think they can make
something good enough with the material they have.
What's going to happen now?
Well... Akane-san's opinion will be ignored,
and Maruzu will continue according to
their own schedule with what they have.
Kashiwagi Eri and Kasumi Utako won't be able to do anything.
Their part in Fields Chronicle 13 ends here.
And you let that happen?
Don't Eriri and Utaha-senpai want to keep going?
Do you really think they'll just accept this?
Maybe if Akane-san had handled the negotiations,
she might have been able to do something about it with her pride and passion.
But it's impossible for me and Machida-san.
At the end of the day, we're too sympathetic to the views of Maruzu's director.
What should we do?
Isn't there anything that we can do?
We've done all we can.
That's...
Listen up, Tomoya-kun.
Blessing Software is your home.
You've managed to come this far with
the help of your fellow circle members.
That desire of yours to do something?
You should be using that to work with Izumi, Hyoudou-san, and Katou-san.
Say what?
I'm just telling you what Machida-san told me.
No way!
I still have over ten pieces left unfinished!
Nearly half of them need to be redrawn.
And I've only really finished the main story.
There are plenty of side stories left to be written.
This is why I didn't want to leave things to Hashima.
Well, he probably saw this as a win.
Now that our work here is done,
we'll be paid as outlined in our contracts,
and won't be penalized for missing the deadline.
In some ways, this is indeed a win.
Do you really think of this as a win?
What can we do about it?
Maruzu decided that they don't need us anymore.
Maybe they would listen to Kousaka Akane, but
listening to the complaints of a couple newbies
would just get in the way of finishing their biggest game, Fields Chronicle.
What should we do?
How can we get Maruzu to listen to us?
How can we make them let us
work on this until we're satisfied?
Sawamura-san...
Of course!
If we just head to Osaka ourselves to negotiate—
That won't work.
If we went over there, with our high
pride and terrible communication skills,
we'd just end up in a huge argument.
Then, isn't there someone who could negotiate for us?
I wonder.
Maybe someone who truly believes in our skills.
Someone who believes if we were allowed to see this to completion,
that we would create a masterpiece.
Someone willing to kneel, cry or do anything to fight for us.
That's it.
There is one.
The only one.
Hey.
Nah, I was still awake.
Yeah.
I understand.
Leave it to me.
So, you're not coming to school?
Yeah.
You're going to Osaka?
You're going to make a game with Eriri and Kasumigaoka-senpai.
If I don't go, Fields Chronicle 13 will just be a good game.
Isn't that good enough?
It should be a masterpiece.
The legendary game that those two are capable of making.
If you do this, will the game end up being legendary?
I don't know for sure.
Even so, Eriri and Utaha-senpai said that they needed my help.
So, is this what you want to do?
Even if you have to throw away our game?
You said it yourself, didn't you?
That you'd work hard to make a legendary game.
Yeah.
You said we'd make it together, didn't you?
But Fields Chronicle 13 is Eriri and Utaha-senpai's biggest chance in the spotlight yet.
But our game is our chance, right?
For the last year, we've put in everything,
and finally reached the spotlight, haven't we?
Tell me, Tomoya-kun, how should I react to this?
Like a 3D girl, causing you trouble, getting angry, and crying?
Or the 2D main heroine, sending you off, smiling and waving?
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
No, this is all my fault.
That's true, but...
Megumi...
Sorry, Tomoya-kun.
It looks like...
I couldn't be your main heroine after all.
Listen up, Taki-kun.
You can't just run in hoping to convince a company like Maruzu with passion alone.
Akane could use her status as a shield, but
you'll have to approach the problem head-on.
You'll need to think of the best solution for both parties,
be able to explain the benefits of your proposal,
and be prepared to make compromises.
And if that doesn't work?
Then it all comes down to passion.
Whether it's making hollow threats, shouting, or begging them in tears,
you'll have to do everything in
your power to change their minds.
I thought you said passion wouldn't work?
You won't be able to convince them with passion alone.
But without passion, people won't feel motivated to act.
Motivated...?
That's why maybe you could convince them in my place.
With your crazy dedication for Shii-chan and Kashiwagi Eri-sensei,
if anyone can do this, it's you.
I'm back!
Welcome back, Rinri-kun.
Eriri, Utaha-senpai...
I...
I did it!
I got the deadline extended by another two weeks!
Why just two weeks?
You were supposed to get us a month!
Are you trying to kill us, Rinri-kun?
Is this what I get for putting all that effort into negotiating?!
Uranus
That is why I will show it to you.
The true form of Venus and the truth of this world.
Yes! Yes! Yes!
This is what I'm talking about!
The party's facing their greatest threat yet.
At the brink of despair, their former arch-rival Guiel appears, saying
"I'm the only one allowed to defeat you!"
What a classic situation!
And Guiel's art here! Gosh!
At first glance it looks plain, but it's anything but!
What the heck?
I've never seen such a mind-blowing expression!
Everything has been great so far.
But now we're going to make it legendary.
Remove characters?
Yeah. We're going to have to remove Lute and Sarashi.
This was the best compromise I could reach.
What? We have to cut out two characters?
They originally wanted us to cut five.
I managed to get them to agree to two.
Five?
There's no way the story would work after that.
Exactly.
These two are the least relevant to the main story.
So I used them as bargaining chips.
But I've already created the characters, and I like the designs...
Their stories have been written, too...
I'm sure we'll be able to use those down the line.
Let's keep them around in preparation for a remake.
People will get new content and we'll double-dip on the earnings.
That sounds so scummy.
Hashima's definitely rubbed off on you.
In exchange for cutting those two,
Maruzu agreed not to make any cuts to the main story.
If anything, we'll be adding more to it.
This here is another scene Kousaka-san was planning.
Before I came by yesterday,
I talked to her and compiled all the details.
You talked to Kousaka Akane?
She's hard to deal with already.
I can't imagine what she's like, stuck in a hospital bed.
It was fine!
I had Machida-san there with me.
Wrong!
Are you even listening?!
Once you've finished up the content Maruzu asked for,
you're free to work on whatever you want.
You'll be able to work towards
the Fields Chronicle 13 that you and Akane-san imagined.
Let's get started.
We'll show them.
Sorry, I'm gonna be
skipping school for a while.
Also,
I'm sorry about earlier.
There's a lot we need to talk about.
Lemme know if you're up for a call.
Megumi
Tomoya      4 Unread Messages
'Sup?
What's is it, Hyoudou-san?
Well, I just finished writing a new song
and really wanted you to listen to it.
I just finished drawing some great art, too!
I already told you, didn't I?
The circle is on break for a while.
But you know, there's not a lot of time left for Winter Comiket.
Exactly! We're in the home stretch now, aren't we?
Not my problem. Tell that to our leader.
I heard from Tomo. He said he'd be unable
to participate for the next two weeks or so.
Oh.
Either way, just because Tomoya-senpai isn't here,
doesn't mean we need to stop working!
That's true. You two can go ahead and keep working.
Sure, but...
We should be working as a team to focus our efforts!
That's not happening.
Without our leader around, we can't make any decisions.
That's not true!
We still have a leader to rely on, don't you think?
Huh?
That's right.
We have Hashima-chan's brother here, the greatest producer around.
Why would you joke about that now of all times?
You know, I thought things would get too awkward if we stayed all serious.
Okay, but did you have to make the worst joke possible?
We meant you, Megumi-san!
Hashima
That was great! All of your songs are so legendary!
Keep the compliments coming!
But really, I'm just motivated by your art.
Yeah, that sounded good.
Onii-chan
Play that when the protagonist and Meguri start going out.
That scene needs to be plenty emotional.
Alright! I got the director's approval!
The game's climax is really coming together!
Now we just need the script.
You promised you wouldn't bring that up, Onii-chan.
Anyway, why aren't you down here, Hashima?
You're upstairs, right?
Oh, don't worry about it.
I can get my work done without seeing you all face-to-face.
Isn't it a pain being off on your own?
It'd just be awkward for all of you
to have a guy around, wouldn't it?
Tomo doesn't mind that at all, though.
We don't really mind either, do we?
Onii-chan
Either way, letting the creative types concentrate
and do their own thing is more my style.
Hashima... You're actually a pretty decent guy, aren't you?
How many times do I have to tell you not to think of me as a nice guy?
Yeah, I don't really get it. That weird concern of yours.
We've lived together for 15 years, and I still don't get it.
This is pretty disgusting, even for me.
Wait...
Could I...
Megumi
Meguri
That's one painful script to read.
So, what is this?
A threat from a stalker? Or some narcissistic rambling?
Either way, it is so embarrassing
I'd been better off not reading it.
H-Hey!
Were you writing that for your own game?
Eh?
O-Oh, yeah.
It's part of the main heroine Meguri's route.
W-Well, Eriri is sleeping and all,
so I've got some free time, and...
It's not really a problem.
After all, this is your true responsibility.
Is it really that disgusting?
It sure is.
Kousaka-san complimented it, though.
She said this was my strength.
Something you'd never be able to write.
Really...
It's like I'm reading some filthy otaku's diary.
Oh come on.
You mean a filthy otaku's delusions, right?
Right.
...Sorry, Megumi.
You're so persistent.
Megumi-san?
We're netting again today, right?
Of course we are.
Our schedule's been pushed to its limits.
At this rate, we might not make it in time for Winter Comiket.
So you're going to help us out, Megumi-san?
I'm not going to help.
I'm just going to do my job.
I don't want to be considered a failure just because of our leader.
I'll show that guy we can continue without him.
That's the spirit, Megumi-san!
If you want to complain about Tomoya-senpai, I'm all ears!
I'm not just complaining, this is justified anger.
What's up?
Nothing. Just taking a break.
It's already this late, huh?
So, have you made any progress?
Take a look.
You...
You did this in just two days?
What do you mean?
You've seen me finish seven pieces in a day before, haven't you?
Sure, you collapsed right after.
But really, this is amazing.
I wonder what got into me.
What do you mean?
You're just improving, obviously.
That's not what I meant.
Okay, then what did you mean?
Why was I able to draw at all?
Eriri?
Even though you're right here...
Even though you're watching...
Why am I still able to draw?
What are you saying?
It'd be a problem if you couldn't.
That's exactly why I'm here.
Well, yeah.
Hey, Tomoya... Once we've finished this game...
It'd be nice if we could make something together again.
Yeah.
Let's do this again sometime.
Right.
No matter how long it takes,
I'll keep putting in the effort,
and one day, I'll make you an offer.
Okay!
I'll be waiting. As long as it takes.
I'll definitely become an artist at your company!
I told you, it's not like that.
The reason I'm angry is because he's acting
so irresponsible despite being our leader.
No way.
The way I see it, you're angry
because Tomo threw you to the side,
and is now hanging out with Sawamura-chan and Senpai.
That's just because you've got some weird misunderstanding of things.
More importantly, weren't we supposed to be
discussing how Meguri feels about the protagonist?
How did that turn into a discussion about me and our circle leader?
Because you're hiding things, of course!
I'm not...
I heard from Senpai.
You two are secretly going out behind our backs, aren't you?
What? Really?!
I knew it.
Kasumigaoka-senpai spread some dumb rumor.
She says you two sneak off and call each other
and send each other romantic messages.
We don't. I've been ignoring everything from him recently.
That's because you two got into an argument.
Are the two of you really aren't dating?
We're not.
Tomoya-kun and I are—
Tomoya-kun?
See? I knew it!
Since when do you call Tomo by his first name?
Whoa. It's a whole new side of Megumi-san!
What's wrong with that?
The two of you have called him by his first
name or a nickname forever, haven't you?
Jealous much?
Come on!
You just keep assuming we're like that.
Cut it out already.
You're doing good, Izumi.
Make sure you catch Katou-san's expressions here.
If we keep this up, we'll be able to create the best...
Rather, the most annoying main heroine!
You got it.
I get why you're so anxious, though.
There's nothing to get anxious about, not for a guy like that.
Sawamura-chan and Senpai, could feel
the pull of fate from the moment they met Tomo.
And even I've been with him since we were born.
Compared to any of us,
you and Tomo haven't had much drama.
Um... Am I not important enough?
Did Kasumigaoka-senpai tell you that, too?
If she did?
Can you just leave me alone?
However I feel about Tomoya-kun
is none of Kasumigaoka-senpai's business.
Are the two of us really not important enough?
Don't lump me in with you, Hashima-chan!
But, I mean...!
Maybe to all of you, Tomoya-kun is a really special person.
But to me, he's nothing special at all.
He's totally normal...
That's why I...
This is the last one.
How is it?
Great.
It's perfect. Maruzu won't have
a single reason to complain about.
More like, I wouldn't let them.
Send
We're done!
Indeed.
Two weeks late, though.
More like, two weeks early!
All thanks to a certain newbie replacement director.
But...
This is the ultimate Fields Chronicle!
Can't deny that.
We had to work twice as hard at the end, though.
So, what do we do now?
Wanna grab dinner and celebrate?
Let's take a break. I don't even feel like moving.
I'm gonna head home.
At least come and celebrate with us.
I was just outside help.
The two weeks I put in can't compare to
the months Kousaka-san worked on this.
This isn't my work.
But Blessing Software's new game is without a doubt mine.
The two weeks I've been away can't
compare to the months I worked on it.
I'm sure of it.
Even if you feel that way, Megumi and the others might disagree.
Maybe they've gone and removed you from the credits.
I've got to get back to make sure that doesn't happen.
I really enjoyed this.
I'll never forget these last two weeks.
In a few hours, your own game's hell
will have you forgetting all about this.
You can save these comments for the next time
you keep us working like this for a whole year.
Yeah, sounds good.
Later.
And he's gone.
Back to the circle. To Katou-san's side.
He just went back to where came from.
He never really belonged here.
That lazy otaku, who for so long put in no effort,
and had nothing but big dreams,
got involved with Fields Chronicle...
It's unbelievable, isn't it?
Well then, as we agreed,
now it's our turn to do something for him.
I know.
We'll have to give it our all to make sure that
the main heroine's route doesn't end early.
There is one.
The only one.
Someone who believes in our skills...
Someone who would be willing to kneel, cry, or do anything—
That's enough, Sawamura-san.
Relying on Rinri-kun would be against the rules.
Why?
We betrayed him. We betrayed the circle.
But he forgave us. Tomoya said he'd be rooting for us!
But right now, he is...
His circle is... making their own new work.
And they're putting in no less effort than we are.
If we made Rinri-kun do this for us,
we might end up crushing his dream.
But... if we give up, the promise we made to him...
Our vows to become extraordinary creators will be broken!
If you want to rely on him no matter what,
then there are things we need to do.
Like what?
The first isn't so hard.
Once our game is finished, we have to help Rinri-kun...
Help Blessing Software to finish their game.
If that's all...
But we did leave them before.
Would they be willing to accept our help?
That probably won't be too difficult.
At least compared to the next thing that we'll need to do.
Would we need to help with something else?
It's not something we'd have to do any actual work for.
We just need to prepare ourselves for it.
Once our game is finished,
we'll have to support Rinri-kun's love.
What are you saying?
You get it, don't you, Sawamura-san?
If you bring Rinri-kun into this, he won't
be returning to the childhood friend route.
Or the senpai route.
After all, that choice will put him on the main heroine's route.
He'll form an even stronger bond with Katou-san and enter the climax event.
No way.
Megumi... She wouldn't...
You'll just have to ask her yourself then.
Do you still believe that an ordinary girl like her would
never fall in love with an eccentric guy like Rinri-kun?
Shut up!
Even if we push him down that route, we'll still be friends with each other.
But we won't be able to pursue his dream
alongside him, or fill the role of his sole companion.
Sorry, Kasumigaoka Utaha.
I put you in a difficult position.
It seems like I only ever lose. I wonder why.
You might seem like a gloomy girl with a terrible
personality who schemes behind the scenes,
but you're actually pretty reliable,
and really a kind person, aren't you?
Alright, we'll get started tomorrow.
Helping Rinri-kun and Katou-san make up.
Maybe we won't even need to do anything.
Megumi is more resilient than she looks.
You're the only one who never noticed it.
That deep down, she's a dark, greedy,
troublesome, and an unpleasant girl.
Coming from you, it sounds pretty convincing.
She would never give up on Rinri-kun.
No, she'd rather bottle up her feelings and let them smolder.
She's the overly-sensitive type who will only be satisfied when he confesses.
So mean!
Megumi? What are you doing here?
You sent me some weird stuff.
An hour ago.
Weird stuff?
So, is it finished?
Yeah, I finished both.
Fields Chronicle and the Kanou Meguri scenario.
This is really disgusting, you know?
I wrote how I feel about you as plainly as possible.
Do you think there's a single girl who would be
happy to receive such a disgusting love letter?
I don't know. I don't really understand these things.
But, well, I guess not...
But at the very least, I'm confident that this is
the story that got my heart pounding the most.
I'm going home.
Wa-Wait a minute!
Do you have any idea how behind schedule we are because of you?
Well...
Look, I finished the scenario at least!
Did you think I'd let you off with just that?
But you came over here to see me!
That's just because I wouldn't be satisfied without complaining to you in person!
You cried for me!
Back at the train station, I know you were crying!
That's just because I was angry about
you following your selfish whims!
You haven't gone back to calling me "Aki-kun."
After getting this angry at someone,
I can't just act like I don't know them!
I don't care anymore.
I don't care, Tomoya-kun.
I don't care about any of this.
I don't want to forgive you, but just I don't care anymore!
Because... I...
I...
I love you, Megumi.
I love Kanou Meguri,
I love the 2D main heroine,
but I love you, the real Katou Megumi, the most.
Why me?
Why not any of them?
Because you're the only girl,
with who I can be honest about my feelings.
I don't need to pretend or act stubborn.
It's not because I admire you, or because of some obsession.
You're the main heroine anyone would envy,
but you weren't really that far out of my league.
So I thought maybe this could work out.
Do you think any girl would be convinced after hearing that?
Well, I guess not...
Normally, you'd be right.
I see.
But...
You managed to convince me.
Maybe to all of you, Tomoya-kun is a really special person.
But to me, he's nothing special at all.
He's just an ordinary guy.
That's why I...
I thought he could be the one.
You might not be able to accept that.
You might dislike me for it.
But...
I don't care!
Tomoya-kun... is mine.
Me-Megu...
Megumi...
I really am easy, aren't I?
U-Uh... Y-Yeah...
But if you love me, why did you go to back to Eriri?
Sorry.
Why did you go back to Kasumigaoka-senpai?
I'm sorry.
Well, I can't imagine you not being obsessed with them.
What should I do?
I wonder.
S-Sorry! I'm sorry!
Huh?
I-I got the wrong idea...
I...
I figured since you closed your eyes, you were okay with it...
Tomoya-kun...
Yeah.
I shouldn't have done something like that out of nowhere.
I really can't read the—
You weren't wrong, Tomoya-kun.
Your timing was off, is all.
Aside from that, you've got it all right.
It's exactly what I wanted.
Okay, then on the count of three.
Yeah.
One, two, three...
They're letting you out next week, huh?
Yeah, I can move my right hand a decent amount now.
And it looks like your left hand has evolved.
When my right hand's fully recovered,
I'll be able to get twice as much work done!
If you try that, something even worse
might happen, so please don't.
I tried out the beta.
What did you think?
What do you think?
I'm not satisfied.
Only 70% of what I wanted, made it in.
That's the best result we could hope for without you there.
Yeah, without me, that's as much as
anyone could hope to get done.
Good job.
So how's your circle doing?
Will you make it in time for Winter Comiket?
It's hell right now.
Well, I guess that's partially my fault.
Oh, I know! Next week, I'll help you—
Just rest for a while!
I mean, you'd totally upset
the circle's power balance, so please don't!
Well then, I'm gonna head back to hell.
See you soon, young man.
Yeah. If we meet again...
We will meet again.
You want to come over to this side, right?
You're going to fight, aren't you?
Chasing after Kashiwagi Eri and Kasumi Utako.
Do you really think I could do that?
With how stubborn you are,
you'll be able to stay in the industry, at least.
Like Iori.
I don't know if I'd want that.
If you ever feel like trying, bring your proposals to me.
If it's your work, even if it's right before a deadline, I'll take a look.
Kousaka-san...
And then,
I'll call it garbage until your heart breaks.
If I ever see you on the street, I am not saying hello!
Hey, Tomoya-kun
Hm?
Meguri's line here
Is this really okay?
Is it a typo?
More like, it doesn't go well with the previous line.
Are we missing some dialogue?
What?
Nothing.
Nothing at all.
Oh man, this awkward atmosphere!
This is why I said to avoid in-circle relationsh—
Guys, if you let yourselves get distracted so easily,
we'll never finish the game in time.
Okay! We're in the home stretch.
Just the final scene and epilogue left, seven images total.
Wait a minute! Isn't that more
than what we had planned yesterday?
It can't be helped. Meguri is just too cute!
Not to mention, the scene that you fixed up earlier was so good!
You know, where after screwing up their first kiss,
they repeat it, and Meguri kisses the protagonist!
After reading that, how could I not add more art for it?
Even if we may risk missing the deadline, I can't help it!
No, we really can't miss the deadline.
Izumi-chan's work is where we're cutting it closest after all, huh?
We heard everything.
Looks like it's time for our comeback.
Hold up. You guys have been coming here every day.
Is Fields Chronicle going to be okay?
It's fine! We're professionals. We finished our work ages ago.
At the cost of our schedule, sure.
Let's see... So this is the latest line art, eh?
I'll color it.
Wait! Wait! There's no room! Jeez!
Can't you just work from your own house?
It's just a short walk away!
What are you saying?
We can only reach peak synergy
if we're discussing things face-to-face!
These are the lyrics for the ending theme, right?
I'll be correcting these today, then.
It's fine! All you do is complain every day!
That's just how your lyrics are.
The ideas are great, but the grammar is abhorrent.
Don't worry about me, just help them debug or something!
There you are.
Just getting some fresh air.
It's winter already, you know.
Hashima Izumi was getting too heated up.
Izumi-chan is amazing, isn't she?
She's learning from me, of course she'd be amazing.
The same way you grew by learning from Kousaka Akane?
I'll have you know, I had my breakthrough on my own.
At Nasu Kougen, fighting right up until the end...
Sorry.
What are you apologizing for?
It was over an year ago.
For what happened back then, and after that...
And for whatever happens in the future.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I couldn't be your rival ten years ago.
I'm sorry for giving up on trying to compete
after seeing you get so much better.
Tomoya!
I'm sorry for blaming you for how we
got separated, and for avoiding you.
Stop it!
Why are you saying all this now?
Back then, I wasn't considerate about others felt.
I was a terrible otaku who ended up hurting his friends.
It's not like you're much different right now.
Maybe.
Despite that, for making up with that terrible otaku friend,
thank you.
I'm just as much of a terrible otaku too.
Well, maybe...
I'm getting cold, time to head back in.
Ah, wait, hold on a second...
There's something I need to tell you...
You abused your position as leader of the circle,
and approached the main heroine, from what I hear.
You're dating Megumi, right?
E-Eriri...
I actually...
I, uh...
It's fine.
I get it.
I'm heading back in now.
Hey, Tomoya.
Were you in love with me?
Ten years ago, did you love me?
Who cares.
Who cares!
Okay!
Uh...
I was about to take a bath...
Hey, Megumi.
Wanna get in together?
Sorry, Eriri.
F-For what?
I realized that I did something inconsiderate.
You and Tomoya-kun...
I knew about the feelings the two of you
harbored for each other for ten years.
And sure, some of those might be painful or unpleasant,
but you two shared even more precious memories together,
and I knew that, too.
Yeah, we really let things get complicated.
So if you want to hate me, I'll take it.
Even if you're angry with me for the next ten years...
W-Wait, Eri—
Come on, just how much do you love Tomoya?
I... Uh...
You forgave that traitor so quickly, and now you're going out?
There was no room for me to even help you.
Eriri...
It might sound strange coming from the
one who asked him to betray you, though.
About that... I'm not sure what to feel.
You and Tomoya, huh?
I thought he was the type a normal girl would never fall for.
It's true that Tomoya-kun is far from normal.
But he's not nearly as special as you or Kasumigaoka-senpai.
You're talking about our talent, right? And not personalities.
You see, it's exactly because neither of us could catch up to the two of you, that we were perfect together.
What the heck...
Tomoya-kun said it himself,
that maybe someone on my level would be within his reach.
I'm pretty sure that would normally be a reason
to get angry and break up with him.
Maybe I'm just not the type of an ordinary girl
who can fall for an ordinary guy.
Really, what the heck...
Seriously... what the heck?
Alright then.
We've paid off our debt to the circle.
Now it's time to start our next real project.
We don't have time to waste worrying about him.
Did that proposal went through?
It's a new series tied in with Fields Chronicle.
There's no way Fantastic Bunko could turn it down.
I see.
So it's time for you to face forward.
Keep running.
And don't stop until he can't catch up anymore.
It'll be alright.
He will still follow, no matter what.
After all, without a doubt, he loved us.
Not Kashiwagi Eri or Kasumi Utako,
but us, for who we truly are.
That's why he'll always be chasing after us.
As a fan, chasing after his beloved artist.
And as a rival, trying to catch up to them.
Tomoya...
Tomoya!
Let's...
Let's wait for him, shall we?
Yeah.
Let's wait for him while advancing as fast as we can.
Winter Comiket, Day 3
We're so late!
I told you we didn't need so many pamphlets.
If the printer was working, we'd be fine.
Isn't it your job to deal with unexpected issues like these, as the circle leader?
I'll accept that criticism, just hurry up!
We finished the game on schedule,
but still ended up in a rush, huh?
I'll listen to your criticism, but please save it for later!
Hm... I don't know how I feel about that.
We don't have time for that!
It's finally here. Our second Winter Comiket.
Yup!
This one is the real battle.
I hope a lot of people come by.
Do you think 2000 copies was too many?
I hope the main heroine becomes popular.
Of course she'll be popular!
After all, she's the girl I found.
The one who makes my heart beat faster than ever!
Hey, Tomoya-kun.
What do you think?
Was I able to become the main heroine you hoped for?
Not for all the players,
but just for one person.
Was I able to become your main heroine?
Should we just break up?
Eh?
Wh-Why?
What's up?
Why would you say that?
After all, we never see each other lately.
I've told you before, haven't I?
I've been busy with work,
even on weekends. I don't have the time.
Working a sales job that's out of your comfort zone.
After throwing away your dream of becoming a creator.
I mean...
I don't have the talent...
Besides, I kept you waiting for years...
So I figured I was done chasing my dreams.
Are you saying it's my fault?
Did I ask you to do that?
Am I holding you back?
No, that's not what I meant...
You know that's not it.
Tomoya-kun. That's just how you feel about yourself, right?
W-What do you mean?
You still can't forget that person, right?
I'm going home.
Megumi!
We can't chase our dreams together anymore, can we?
'Sup, Tomoya-kun.
Iori?
Running away again?
Is it the debt collectors?
Or are you being chased by a girl?
Actually, I thought up this amazing proposal that would turn things around for me.
The client liked it too,
and we were about to sign a contract, but...
Suddenly, your past misdeeds were revealed?
Exactly.
So hey, think you can sell this to someone?
With this project, we'll reunite our two man
dream team, and make the ultimate game.
How long are you going to keep chasing those stupid dreams?
Rinri-kun?
Rinri-kun...
No, Tomoya-kun...
Utaha-senpai...
How to Raise a Boring Girlfriend
The Final Chapter
On that night—
The heck are you singing?
No, no...
What the hell is this?!
G-G-G-G-Gimme a break!
Sorry. I'm sorry!
Please excuse us.
What's this supposed to be? What's going on here?
What did you think?
This is Kasumi Utako's masterpiece,
and Blessing Software's latest project.
The plot for How to Raise a Boring Girlfriend: The Final Chapter.
How could you do this in the movie? That too in the epilogue! This dumb fantasy should be illegal or something!
You really had me sweating there, in more ways than one.
Hm. My character was pretty trashy. I liked it.
I still don't understand your tastes at all.
So there you go.
The plot is finished, so we just need to get
the art and development schedule going—
There's no way we're making this. What a load of bullshit.
We're supposed to be making a sequel to our game.
You tossed the last game's happy ending right out the window!
This is as bad as killing off the last game's protagonist in a car accident.
I got so excited, I stayed up all night writing this, too...
It definitely reads like it was written overnight!
Most importantly, why is the main heroine
this time some older, gloomy, yandere?
What happened to the wonderful, blonde childhood friend?
Well naturally, if I were contracted to, I'd write that route too.
Let's see...
Maybe for another two million yen.
I-I'll take care of that.
Don't bribe her!
Come on, Utaha...
This may be an offer from some no-name company,
but you should still take it seriously.
That's not fair, Eriri.
I've researched this company's past works.
Based on that, I came up with a plot
I thought their fans would enjoy most.
Yeah, right. If you say so.
It seems like we'll want to discuss the direction
with our employers here before starting on anything.
Well, that was the plan from the start.
After all, they are a popular and well-established company.
Stop it with that weird reaction of yours.
Aren't you the employer here?
Yeah, but I mean...
It's just, we're finally doing this.
It took a little longer than I hoped, though.
It feels like we were working together just yesterday.
Time passed by in a flash for us.
Yeah...
What do you think you're doing?
Here you are, Rinri-kun.
Damn you!
How did it go?
Your meeting with Eriri and—
Tomoya-kun?
Megumi... Megumi!
You're not gonna go anywhere, right?
You won't leave me, will you?
Did someone show you some terrible plot writing?
You know, like Kasumigaoka-senpai?
Don't just get it right!
It's finally going to come true, isn't it?
Our dream.
Oh man, being able hear that from you is such a relief!
Sounds like she really did traumatize you.
Well, once this project kicks off, things are going to get busy!
I've been busy ever since you decided to make the game.
I'm counting on you, Director.
Everything depends on you, Scenario Writer-san.
Make sure to make good use of those two, Vice President.
Don't let them run over you, President.
Let's make this happen.
If we don't make it happen, who will?
Wait until we're back home.
Huh? It's open?
Wha—
Oh hey, welcome home.
Welcome home, Tomoya-san, Megumi-san.
Wh-What are you two doing here?
This great phrase popped into my head,
and I just couldn't sit still.
Same for me!
I thought of a really good character design, so I couldn't just sit around!
The office is next door!
And you two aren't even working!
Yeah, but we used to work
in your room all the time, you know?
We're not just a circle anymore, we're a company!
Don't mix work with your personal lives!
Don't mix work with our personal lives?
Are you seriously telling us that?
Well, I mean...
Yeah, yeah!
Who do you think you are?
That's rich coming from you.
Did I really just hear you say that?
These dishes and the furniture,
Tomoya definitely didn't pick out any of this.
Eriri...
Well, I suppose you pass, barely.
Is this what you do when you go to
someone else's place for the first time?
Don't act so distant, Katou-chan!
That's right!
Those two are going to be working with us now, aren't they?
What a handful...
Wait, those two?
Welcome back.
I decided to go ahead and take a shower first, Katou-san.
Kasumigaoka-senpai...
How long has it been since we had the whole team together?
We're going all out tonight! Let's call your brother over too!
Alright!
I've got the food taken care of!
Please forgive me!
Wait a minute, I didn't even do anything.
You're so loud, Tomoya-kun.
Oh, come on, Megumi...
It's fine.
Why don't you go entertain the guests?
I can't do that...
At the very least,
bring this out.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
Since the six of us were together.
Y-Yeah.
Shall we begin?
Our first overnight meeting in years.
Sure.
I'm a bit annoyed that they're intruding in on us,
so I'll manage with this for now.
They're here!
We've been waiting!
You really kept us waiting, you know?
Were those last ten seconds really necessary?
Oh, come on. I'm not falling for your bait.
Don't be rude!
Okay! Okay!
Let's get this started!
To the reunion of Blessing Software's original members!
the end
for real
Cheers!
Good job!
Good work everyone!