I'm always searching for it.
Always seeking it out.
That's a miss. It's Kelp filling again.
Today's is all kelp.
Why, Akane?
I've said it a million times, I want mayonnaise and tuna!
I like kelp.
You heard her.
You lost to Aoi.
You said it a million times and still lost.
Shut up.
Come on, let's practice.
But I'm not done eating!
Hurry up and finish!
My Akane Special is gonna roar.
That's a terrible name.
Me too.
I wanna play too.
Want me to teach you the guitar?
Then what do you want to play?
What, for real?
Do you secretly admire me or something, Aoi?
No!
Really?
Come to think of it, it'd be cool if a girl played the bass.
All right, Ao! When you get bigger,
you'll be our bass.
Hey! what'll I do then?
That's great, isn't it, Aoi?
You can be the chorus, Abo.
Or how about a dancer?
Listen here, Banba.
Come on, we were gonna practice, right?
What should we begin with?
Akane?
The usual!
All right!
Again?
Here we go, Michinko!
Yeah, yeah.
Wait a second.
Oh, come on!
Banba, plug in the mic!
Huh?
All right, here we go!
If you go there
It's said that all your dreams will come true
Everyone wants to go there but it's a far away world
That land's name is Gandhara
It's a utopia somewhere out there
How could I even get there?
But
Someone please tell me
I'm sure that place
is just too far away.
They met with an accident.
For both of them to go.
I heard the other person wasn't watching the road.
It's such a shame, leaving two daughters behind.
Akane is still just a third year student, right?
How will they make it through this?
Aoi.
Be a good girl and listen to your sister.
From now on, the two of you will have to give it your all.
I can't come with you.
Why? What do you mean?
We promised to go to a vocational school in Tokyo together!
Akane!
Stop bullying Akane, you dolt!
Aoi.
Don't take Akane away from me, you dummy!
Fatso!
Fat? My body fat is seven percent!
Shut up, you pig!
Hey, Aoi.
Monkey! Gorilla! Don't take Akane away!
Akane and I will always be together!
I'm still looking for it.
Akane.................
1 Unread Message
Akane
lllllllllll
I want pork meat for dinner.
But we had that just yesterday.
I want it today too.
. I can eat it everyday.
Let's go home.
New
Akane
lllllllllll
lllllllllllllllllllllllllllll
October 28th
OOOOOOOOOO
Manager
1 Unread Message
Illllllllllllllllllllllllllllll
October 28th
OOOOOOOOOO
Manager
1 Unread Message
I'm searching for it.
The place where all dreams come true.
Her
Blue
Sky
October 25th
Friday
I'm going to Tokyo.
I understand the place you want to go to
but it's not for college, is it?
How about employment?
I'll work part-time while rising to fame in a band.
Who else is in the band?
Just me.
I'll just check off employment then.
Alright, next.
Ohtaki, get in.
Okay.
Is she in a mood?
Hurry it up, Oht—
Oh, I'm gonna be a bride!
I don't know who the person is, but—
Employment it is.
Alright, next.
Hey, let's talk a bit more about my future!
City Hall gets busy this time of the year.
I probably won't be picking you up from next month.
It's an hour long walk to school from our house!
Well, it's a nice season.
You get to admire the autumn leaves
while hiking up the mountain.
I hate mountains.
Living in a basin is like being surrounded by walls.
It's as if we're being held captive in a gigantic prison.
There it is! Your puberty lyrics.
Yeah, whatever.
Anyway, I'm gonna get outta this place.
Huh?
Hello!
Oh!
Welcome back, Akane and Aoi.
What are you up to?
It's for tonight's meeting.
Masamichi invited too many people so I was borrowing some cushions and tables from Mrs. Yamaguchi.
Ah, we'll lend you a hand. Come on, Aoi!
This should be plenty.
Yeah, it should.
Sorry for troubling you on your way home.
Not at all.
I'll be at the meeting too, after all.
Hey Akane, would you like to have a pear?
Sure, I'd love to!
What a wonderful sister you have.
Be grateful, Aoi.
Whenever they tell me to be grateful,
it only makes me wanna rebel more.
City of Music Festival - First Informational Meeting
Look, I'm tellin' ya,
the miso potato cart needs more variety of flavors.
Like miso mixed with yuzu or the seven spices.
City of Music Festival - First Informational Meeting
Would people actually come for something like this, though?
Why're you being so pessimistic gramps?
This city's been stealing all tourists in the area for sightseeing.
From here on out we need to plant our own flag!
Yeah! We have to catch a big wave or it'll be our loss.
Tourism Bureau's very own Masamichi is funding it, after all.
Exactly!
Even at City Hall, it's rumored that
he's moving around quite a lot of this.
Quit spreading false rumors, Akane!
What, so it's not true?
I bet there's plenty of funds.
Look, you have to understand.
In addition to bringing in a band from outside, we should—
Why don't you participate, Ao?
If it's used for some town renewal project, it's not music anymore.
That's not enjoying the sound.
Instead of music to your ears,
it's music that bores you to tears.
You might think what you said just
now was very clever, but it wasn't.
Ow! Ow! Ow!
Anyway, this town will be reborn through music!
Aoi! Tsugu!
Dad.
Uh, are you gonna practice at the temple room again today?
Yep.
Just wrap it up by nine.
The low tone of your bass reverbs and sounds kinda creepy.
I have a s-soundproof room at my house.
Don't you want an elder brother?
Huh?
C'mon Dad, slow your roll.
I won't let her marry someone who's been divorced.
I'm the victim here! My wife cheated on me!
I'm a divorcee with a halo!
Doesn't matter.
Hey, Aoi!
Do you remember Shinno?
Oh, vaguely.
Why?
Oh never mind, it's okay if you don't.
My hit points that keep dropping rapidly
It must somehow be my own fault
Anyway, this is a difficult place to live
About what my dad said earlier,
I don't agree with it either.
It stinks like blue cheese
But still, even he—
Don't talk about stuff like that in here.
So we can talk about it somewhere else?
I'd rather not but
it'd be better than here.
Wrong.
Here, you have to hold it down tight.
Oh, hey Ao, I just noticed
you have a mole in the white of your eye.
Just like me!
A mole in the eyeball is a sign we're gonna become big shots.
We're both Eyeball stars.
Eyeball stars!
What's with that name?
No one would get it.
What? It's cool.
It's cool!
Dankichi Nitobe is the one who performed
in the New Year's TV song contest, right?
Yeah, I kind of remember.
He was riding a weirdly flashy portable shrine.
Oh, I've seen that one too.
For this event, we're gonna have him write a song about the area.
He'll use the phrase fireworks go boom-boom in the lyrics
and when he sings it, real fireworks will go boom-boom-boom!
Fireworks? Wow.
So you really did move a lot of this, didn't you?
This will be... my opus.
The opus I'm s-staking my life on.
So I'm counting on your help with this event, Akane.
I already cleared it with the Civic Life Bureau.
So I've heard. Good luck, Miss Aioi.
Eh, Wai—
Nakamura, the meeting's about to being!
Alright then, I'll give you the details later!
Wait a second, Michinko!
Well, we're not very busy
these days anyway, so give it your best!
You do realize that Michinko likes you, right?
Well...
You shouldn't do anything to lead him on.
He's an old friend and a co-worker.
Even if I know he has feelings for me, there are things that mustn't be said.
That's what it means to be an adult.
Akane and Aoi
Aioi
Being an adult is so boring.
That aside,
why don't you give it another thought?
College.
You can study and still be in a band.
We've had this conversation already.
You promised you'd stop bugging me about it.
Don't go back on your word.
Alright, I'm going to go practice.
Stop it!
Where the hell did that come from?!
And your rhythm and timing are messed up!
Who're you?
Hey.
We're both Eyeball stars.
Shinno?
You know me?
Hey, that's my school's uniform.
Maybe you're one of my fans?
Wanna shake hands?
Huh? Wha—
So you really are Shinno.
Of course I am! And who're you?
Akane!
H-Hey, wait!
I said, hold—
What the hell?
What the hell is this?!
Hey, let me outta here!
A-Akane!
Huh?
Done with practice already?
I'm making your favorite minced meat tonig—
Sh-Shinno is—
Sorry!
So what about Shinno?
Uh, right!
I was practicing and thought of him all of a sudden.
Like how's he doing...
That's all, I guess.
I haven't heard from him in ages.
I don't even know if he's dead or alive.
I see. That's one possibility.
Actually, that's like, the only possibility!
After all, he hasn't changed one bit.
Aoi?
Hey, you left the front door open.
That's careless.
Michinko?
Wait, what're you two doing?
What are we doing?
Making din—
There's no time for that!
I need help with the event!
Yeah, I know but—
Huh? Didn't I tell you about today?
Today?
Never mind! We need to get moving!
When he gets here, hold this up high, with all the gusto you can muster!
So this is what you were working on last night?
Hey, don't spill any miso on it!
Sheesh. I shouldn't even be here—
But why is he coming today?
The event is a week from now, right?
The thing is...
Mr. Nitobe is the authority on local songs, you know?
He said something about being unable to sing about the land's soul
unless he samples the local food and mingles with the people.
And City Hall is paying for that, isn't it?
Isn't that what you'd call sponging someone off?
Tsugu?
What the—
Ladies and gentlemen, sorry to keep you waiting.
One lone man, Dankichi Nitobe
has crossed lands from afar and traversed
mountains to bring you the gift of a smile.
A f-feint?
Isn't that Dan?!
What's he doing here?
Akane?
Here I am, this handsome man
Get your smartphones out and say cheese!
If only I could meet you
I-Isn't that...
Shinno
Come on, Tsugu! Hold it up high!
My happiness points woud've have doubled, boom!
A little tiresome
But still!
Wel
come
home
Mast
er!
Welcome
home
Shinnouske!
A little painful
But still!
But after all that's said and done, I'm still hungry for
Another helping of your smile and nothing more
Okay everyone, together now, say cheese!
Hey, Ao!
Jeez.
Mom, Dad, and all of my ancestors, lend me your strength!
Man.
Ao, the taxi driver gave me this invoice—
Hey.
So that Shinno guy was really in there?
Yeah.
I thought he was a ghost but If the Shinno I saw at the station was real, then who did I see here?
A lookalike?
I don't know, but he was definitely Shinno too.
I don't get it but something really weird's going on!
Fire Extinguisher
Well?
Nobody's here.
That can't be...
Why'd you run away?
Ao?
L-Let go of her!
Whoa.
Huh? Who's this kid? He looks just like Michinko.
Who are you?
I told you already, I'm Shinno!
Who the hell are you?
Ao, let's run away for now.
Ao?
Aoi Aioi.
Eyeball star number two.
That day,
when Akane refused to go to Tokyo with me.
I didn't feel like going home.
So I stayed here, thinking about a lot of things.
And the next thing I knew,
it was morning already?
Why is that a question?
I don't get it either.
But I felt sluggish, so I was zoning out
over there when this awful cacophony woke me up.
Cacophony?
I swear it feels like I just got up.
And you're telling me that thirteen years have passed.
I have no idea what's going on anymore.
I see. You're like Rip Van Winkle.
How's that even—
Oh well,
If time's passed there's nothing I can do about it.
You're quick to adapt to weird situations.
Nah, I'm accepting it thanks to you.
You're obviously a miniature Michinko.
How carefree.
At least we know he's not a ghost. He has a physical form.
I see. But then...
Maybe a living spirit?
Living spirit?
You've heard of it, right?
When you have strong feelings for someone,
a spirit spawned from those feelings
leaves your body without you realizing it.
Yeah, I've heard! The spirit puts a deadly curse on that person!
Shinno, is it because Akane shot you down?
Maybe you were born from those unresolved feelings.
What are you talking about?
Unresolved feelings or whatever, I haven't given up.
After thinking about it, I've made up my mind.
First I'll go to Tokyo and become a big musician!
Then I'll come back for Akane with all this fanfare!
What's with the excessive positivity.
Why'd this have to happen?
Akane must be thirty-one by now, right?
Wait, so thirty-one—
Uhh.
Then, thirty...
Hey, Akane isn't married, is she?
Nope.
All right!
Wait, I probably shouldn't be happy about that.
I have to hurry up and get—
Do you want to see her?
Are you an idiot? I can't just see her like this!
Idiot?
Jerk.
Were you even listening to me?
I've gotta become a big musician fir—
I not sure if he's big or not but he did become a musician, right?
Come to think of it,
your thirty-one year old self did become a musician, in a way.
That's awesome!
I'll be right back!
Wai—
See ya!
This must be fate, huh?
I was surprised, too.
I thought you'd be our best bet for creating a local song,
so I was gathering footage in preparation to ask you.
And I was surprised to see my old buddy in the backup band!
Right, Shinno?
That hurt.
This'll be a triumphant homecoming performance for Shinnosuke.
I'll have to give him a guitar solo so he can shine.
That's so cool, I wanna do a solo too!
You guys, that's still mostly raw.
You sax doesn't have enough soul in it.
Excuse me, another plate of this firm kind of meat.
No no, it does.
So you told Aoi that Shinno was coming back?
Did you say something, Akane?
What's this?
Are the two of you together?
Well, I'll leave that to your imagination.
Hey, Michinko.
Bleh, the booze tastes crap now!
Bring the expensive stuff!
And more meat!
So he can't leave here?
Living spirit? He's more like a bound spirit.
He knew that and yet he flung himself.
So my wish does come true.
At that time, I thought to myself.
Hurry up and graduate. Go to Tokyo. Race to the future.
And then come back for Akane as soon as possible.
I thought that day couldn't come any sooner.
So even if I am a living spirit,
it's definitely not due to some grudge.
Anyway, I don't really get it but one thing's for sure,
If the future me and Akane get together, everything will fall into place, right?
Then this living spirit me will go whoosh!
Right back into the real me's body.
I'm counting on you, Eyeball star.
Has he always been like that?
Probably.
He seemed a bit more mature back then, though.
What're you gonna do?
Are you going to do what he said,
and help the two of them get together?
That might not be a bad idea.
Is that so?
It's better than having Akane
be bound to me here forever.
C'mon, let's go to the next place! An after-party!
S-Sure, just a second.
Hey, Shinnosuke. If you're gonna puke, do it in the can.
That was some tasty meat.
Let's go somewhere with fish.
Nah, he's no good.
I guess it can't be helped.
I haven't been drinking so I'll drive him back.
Masamichi, I'd like to go to a place which has girls,
wherever the local beauties hang out.
Uh, sure!
Gandhara
Gandhara?
You're awake?
If you go there
My dream did come true, in a way, right?
It's said that all your dreams will come true
It sure did.
You're mocking me.
I'm surprised you turned out to be a morose drunk, Shinno.
Everyone wants to go there but it's a far away world
You're single, so...
have you been waiting for me?
Have I been waiting?
Well,
I don't think so.
Here we are.
Walk properly. I'll get you some water—
Have a drink with me, Miss Aioi.
Don't act silly.
C'mon.
The hell?
Don't put on airs at your age.
Are you being serious?
Why not?
You've got nothing to lose.
Is that the kind of thing you say
to someone you met after thirteen years?
Don't disappoint me.
It's not like I wanted to come back.
Not as I am right now.
I'm back!
Aoi?
Welcome back.
You're home early.
I can only take so much wining and dining.
I'm just going to skip bath and go to bed.
lllllllllllllllll
Web Encyclopedia
llllllllllllllllllllllllllll
Living Spirits
Hey, wanna sleep together?
What?
It'll be fun! We haven't done that in a long time.
Hey.
Yeah?
Tell me about Shinnosuke Kanamuro.
He's just a drunk.
Not how he is now, how he used to be.
It's been so long that I've forgotten.
I do have a bad memory.
But in all these years, you've never had a boyfriend.
I did, from time to time.
No way! You never let it show!
Why didn't you ever say anything?!
What's that? You really are in love with me, huh?
Excuse me?
Whatever!
Yummy!
But are you sure it's okay for me to eat your lunch?
I'll go to the convenience store later.
Yeah?
Well then.
So you get hungry too, huh?
I wouldn't say hungry, but I can eat, I guess.
Killing time is the toughest thing here.
You've got a guitar if you're bored.
The strings are rusty.
Want me to buy you new ones? Nickel, righ—
Nah.
That's okay.
Instead, would you get me a copy of Jump?
It doesn't feel right, not reading KochiKame.
That series is over.
What?!
There's no way KochiKame can be over!
If Ryo goes, then what does eternal mean?
Beats me.
For real?
Who did Ryo end up with? No wait, that'd spoil—
He really doesn't have a care in the world, does he?
Huh? This isn't Tsugu, but Michinko?
This is what he used to look like?
No wonder Shinno called Tsugu a miniature.
Akane.
They were in the same class.
Woah.
CONQUER THE WORLD!
)
It's as if an elementary schooler wrote this.
Akane
wrote something that I would've written.
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
Akane Aioi
It does know the blueness of the sky, huh.
Aioi!
Hey, would you reconsider?
If you joined our band—
Joining a band that sucks more
than me would be a waste of time.
What was that, you bitch?
That girl's got a really nasty tongue.
What a waste.
A lone girl in a boy band sounds just way too good.
But I guess you can afford to pass up on that opportunity.
After all, you're going to Tokyo
because there's an older guy there, right?
Ugh.
It's rumored that you're always
picked up and dropped off by a guy in a car.
C'mon, introduce me to your boyfriend's friends!
l wouldn't blame you if it doesn't work out.
Alright, wanna go now?
Next, about the budget for the stage—
City of Music Festival
Before that, what's this
budget for Mr. Nitobe to love the locale?
Oh, that is, well...
It's for
Members are enjoying
themselves too!............
things like this.
Ah, shaved ice is a local specialty.
Receipt
Excuse me, Is this the
contact address that's
listed on the receipt?..
Receipt
Excuse me, Is this the
contact address that's
listed on the receipt?..
Wait, 18,000 yen for shaved ice?
Receipt
Excuse me, Is this the
contact address that's
listed on the receipt?..
Receipt
Excuse me, Is this the
contact address that's
listed on the receipt?..
He said that unless he tries all of the flavors,
he can't understand the shop owner's spirit.
City of Music Festival
I hope he gets diarrhea.
Hey now, Nagatoro.
City of Music Festival
River boating too, huh?
Marinated pork and soba with walnut dip for lunch.
City of Music Festival
Just how much does this guy eat?
Akane!
What is it?
I'm guessing you're mad, aren't you?
Wouldn't it be strange if I weren't?
Like I said last night, it really was just a coincidence that
I found him as I was about to make an offer to Mr. Nitobe.
But if things aren't brought to a head,
you'll always been tied down by Shinnosuke.
That's enough.
Do you doubt my autonomy that much?
I'm just a human being, after all.
I've always lived my life on my own terms, with my own decisions.
I'm not someone who gets influenced by others.
Does your boyfriend have a job, Aioi?
Or friends from university?
I mean, I like the idea of a working adult,
I can't get through to her but her hopeless positivity...
but I really want to go to a university cafeteria!
kinda reminds me of Michinko.
Is he here?
Huh?
Is that your friend? Hello!
Oh, h-hello.
See? Not a guy.
What?
Downed by a deer?
A deer?
Yeah.
Mr. Ito, the bassist and Mr. Kodama, the drummer got food poisoning.
It was super delicious.
I have no regrets.
You should!
You were told to cook it thoroughly, weren't you?
If I'd waited, this guy would've eaten it!
That'd be you!
Wow, they're like real rock musicians!
Anyway, you'll both have to fast for a week,
until the inflammation subsides.
It doesn't seem like they'll be able to perform.
But you'll get plenty of nutrients through an IV drip.
Worst-case scenario, it won't be a live performance.
I'm afraid not, my friend. I'm afraid not.
Mr. Nitobe?
Sound is a living thing.
It's a form of life.
If it isn't live, I cannot sing the heart of enka.
The one thing Dankichi Nitobe
never does is sing to recorded music!
B-But...
Finding substitutes at this point on such short notice...
You need a drummer and a bassist, right?
Yeah, that's right.
We've got them!
A drummer
and a bassist.
Rehearsal Hall
The heck is this.
The stands-ins are a high school girl and a City Hall employee?
It sounds like fun.
It won't work.
But Mr. Nitobe loves the idea.
He's at City Hall right now, explaining it.
Mr. Nitobe went there himself?
Why is this happening?
I don't want to be part of a brat's playtime.
I'm a professional.
It was you who told me I was an Eyeball star.
Why don't you watch me
and then decide whether it's playtime?
Hey, Aoi.
Good idea!
By all means, show us what you've got.
Michinko.
If you go there
It's said that all your dreams will come true
Everyone wants to go there but it's a far away world
Oh, they're pretty good.
Yeah, I'm impressed, but why Gandhara?
That land's name is Gandhara
It's a utopia somewhere out there
Woha, so cool!
How could I even get there?
Someone please tell me
Gandhara, Gandhara, they say it was in India
Wonderful! I feel love in their performance.
This will be the highlight of the festival.
Gandhara, Gandhara, the country of love, Gandhara
Awesome!
How cool is that, Ao!
Performing in a professional backup band at your age.
Well, it just kinda worked out.
Isn't that what you want?
If you're near the real one,
it'll give Akane more chances to talk to him.
Yeah, there would definitely be
a chance to get them together!
But,
can I really do this?
Performing with professionals.
Of course you can.
You're just like me, an Eyeball star.
All right, let's practice. You brought the score, right?
Oh, yeah!
Hey!
Aoi, are you in there?
What's wrong?
N-Nothing.
What about you, Akane?
Um...
I'm sorry, about getting you mixed up in this.
I couldn't help it when I imagined you standing on a big stage.
Oh, that's alright.
I'm kinda looking forward to it actually.
I see.
Oh, I brought some sweets.
You should have them too, Tsugu.
Well then, don't stay up too late.
I don't think she suspected anything.
Yeah.
You had me scared!
She's grown into an old lady.
Well,
An incredibly cute old lady.
An old lady more cute and beautiful than any idol or model.
Um, are you okay?
What do you mean?
Akane must've been through a lot in all these years.
It's like yesterday for me but
Akane has been alone this whole time.
I want her to find happiness as soon as possible.
Shinno.
Still, I bet now that I'm an old man,
I've gotten really good with the guitar.
Well, yeah.
For real?
Want me to record it for you? You playing.
With this.
You can do that?
Man, smartphones these days!
That game was amazing too.
Let me borrow it for the night.
Forget it.
Then how about mine?
It's okay?
I don't mind if it's just one night.
Besides, Akane and Tsugu are the only ones who call me.
Um, the password is—
Hey! That's personal information!
Thank you, Ao!
Your sister really raised you well!
Hey! Don't touch my head like that!
Hey.
Are you really gonna record it?
Why not?
He might be disappointed to see his present self.
I don't know.
I do!
Shinno may be a dummy,
but he's somewhat kind and
would never make fun of someone!
And also—
What?
Nothing.
So, what are you doing here?
You're going to record Shinnosuke, right?
You can leave that to me! I'm good at it!
I can also do odd some jobs, like a manager?
She was already here by the time I arrived.
Well, it's good to have more resources, right?
You really get it huh, little man.
There you are.
Rehearsal is about to begin so get ready please.
Okay.
Rehearsal Hall
All right, great job!
Shinnosuke is so cool!
I'll do an equipment check, so please stand by!
What's this?
Is this your idea of a joke, Aoi?
You're playing bass, right?
So why're you trying to stand out?
S-Sorry.
Gimme a break.
Women aren't fit to play bass in the first place.
All right, Ao! When you get bigger,
you'll play bass in our band.
Your hands and body are small and you can't maintain the rhythm.
You're the one who told me that!
Okay, okay! But we're still amateurs.
We're new to this so there's gotta be—
Amateurs trying to stand with
professionals is the real issue here.
And you, Michinko.
You're following the bass and that messes the rest of us up.
If the drummer can't keep the rhythm, he's got no business—
Hey there! Shin!
There you are!
This place is so big!
Hey, Eiko!
Hi!
We're here, Shin!
Why?
It seems they've come to pick you up.
Mr. Nitobe is already on his way.
Professionals really are something, eh?
Uh, well—
Come on, Shin.
Let's go!
You're a real grouch when you're drunk, Shinnosuke.
Come on, Dan is waiting.
Woha, he's the wild type.
I guess that's all for today.
What're you up to?
I sent the recording to Aioi's phone.
October 30th
Y-You... rotten old man!
He saw it already.
What the hell is wrong with this seedy old man?
And he's going to a hostess bar?
I can't let him have Akane like this.
I'll have to rehabilitate him before getting them together.
But still...
I really did become a professional, huh?
Damn, that bastard.
Acting cool and all when he's even got an outie.
An outie?
Yeah.
Here, wanna see?
No thanks.
Well, since it's come to this, it's your turn, Ao.
Show him a performance so brilliant
that it'll crush his pride to smithereens.
Will...
Will I be able to do that?
Of course you can do it! No doubt about that.
Right, Eyeball star?
All right then, let's get practicing.
Do you have a metronome?
I have an app for it on the phone.
Smartphone again? This really is impressive.
Huh.
If Shinno returned to that Shinnosuke,
what would happen to this Shinno?
When you play the bass, no matter how sloppy things get,
you gotta beat out the rhythm right and support everyone.
While listening to everyone else's sounds,
you need to keep up your own pace.
What?
Shinnosuke isn't here?
Why? The performance is right around the corner!
Well, we didn't have a rehearsal scheduled for today anyway.
Besides,
he said practicing with amateurs will just dull his own skills.
That jerk!
I'm sick of him looking down on us!
He's totally different from Shinno.
How'd he turn out like this?
Shinno?
Yeah, that's what we used to call Shinnosuke back in the day.
Wrong! Shinno isn't Shinnosuke at all!
Huh?
Mr. Nakamura!
I opened it up for you.
Thanks!
Come on, Aoi. Time to practice.
There's not point if our rhythm group
doesn't have the rhythm locked down.
I know that!
Shinno and Shinnosuke, huh?
Doesn't matter which but if he's not here, I'm going home.
That guitar solo was great.
I know, right?
Can you do it?
Nah, too tough for me.
Found you!
All right.
One more time.
Hey, you okay?
You've been playing for a while now.
And you were practicing with Michinko before that, right?
I'm fine.
It's almost nine, right?
At a time like this, even Michinko will allow it.
Don't you have to study?
Don't worry about it.
It's not like I'm going to college anyway.
Huh, so what're you gonna do?
Go to Tokyo and join a band.
Woah!
Someone who'll follow in my footsteps, right in front of me!
Don't praise me so squarely like that.
I'm not doing it for a logical reason.
You're not?
I want to leave this town
so Akane can live the way she wants to.
I'm sure she's been holding back on doing
the things she wants to because of me.
If I stay here, Akane will forever be chained to this place.
Besides, there isn't anything I especially want to do.
So I don't want her to waste money on me.
I don't want to be a burden on her any more.
You're blaming yourself too much.
Nobody thinks it's your faul—
Everyone thinks exactly that.
The neighborhood housewives and our relatives too.
Ao.
It's the truth.
That's why, I'm leaving.
You're incredible.
You know,
I've been thinking about why I'm here.
A living spirit?
I don't think it's because of any lingering attachments.
But the truth is
that some part of me might be afraid to leave this town.
In that respect, you're incredible.
You're full of doubts,
but you thought it through and made up your mind to leave.
Huh?
I got back at you for last time.
Got back? You're—
Bassist's gotta have everyone's back, right!
That's right!
Now that's my band's future bassist!
Wait, what? This is the future.
Then—
You remembered?
Remembered? I promised you, didn't I?
Isn't that why you're playing the bass?
Do it to me too.
What? Ruffle your hair?
My forehead. Flick it. Please.
Well, if that's what you want.
As hard as you can!
Okay!
Ouch!
Alright then, see you tomorrow!
Hey!
Ao?!
What the heck am I doing?
I've got to get Akane and Shinnosuke together.
I owe it to Akane,
and Shinno too.
Morning!
Good morning!
Friday the   st
Friday the  st
Here Comes Handsome
Get this, I heard Chika was with a man yesterday!
What, for real?
Yeah! An older guy and he looked pretty cool.
More like, an old geezer?
But I heard he was pretty hot.
Maybe he's rich?
Morning, Aio—
Huh?
Huh?!
That hurts! Let go of me!
The guy you were with yesterday...
It was Shinnosuke.
You're disgusting.
Wait, so you do have a crush on Shinnosuke?
Of course I don't!
But Shinno—
Jeez.
Look, I wouldn't make a move on my friend's man.
Shinno is different from Shinnosuke, right?
That's right.
And you like that Shinno guy.
Yeah, I do!
Th-That's so out of character.
I do like him! Is that bad?
No, nobody said it was bad.
What're you doing? Hey—
It's bad.
It's totally wrong.
A-Aioi?
Oh no.
Did I forget to lock the door this morning?
Um,
A-Aoi?
You startled me.
Sheesh, if you're going to return early, just give me a call.
I kept trying to reach you but it wouldn't go through.
Why?
Shinno.
Why didn't you go with Shinnosuke?
What's this, all of a sudden?
If you'd gone with him,
I'm sure he wouldn't have turned out like that jerk!
He may have stayed the same old Shinno!
Uh, what are you talking about?
I don't want to end up like you, Akane!
Denying myself what I want to do and regretting it.
No!
And having everything end here like this.
I absolutely refuse to do it!
This isn't what l want to be saying!
Akane, you're
I really am
such an idiot!
An idiot, huh?
Hey, Aoi?
Oh, it's open.
Aoi! Are you in here?
She doesn't want to end up like me, huh?
Kelp again.
I think I'm just a good-for-nothing type of person.
Yeah.
You text an elementary schooler demanding to pick up your bass, and barge into his room and lounge around as if it's your place.
That totally counts as good-for-nothing in my book.
But that Shinnosuke is a thousand times worse than me!
Ao, watch the panties.
m 0 0 l -22 18 l 126 105 l 150 84 l 3 -3
Here Comes Handsome
Ao, calm down.
Michinko!
I'm going to help you get together with my sister.
Dad, it late night.
A-Aoi,
you said you were dead set
against anyone who's been divorced!
I'll retract that statement.
I'd rather she be with you
than be taken away by that Shinnosuke.
I appreciate the sentiment but I don't need your help.
The entire reason I asked Mr. Nitobe to do this was for Shinno.
m 0 0 l -22 18 l 126 105 l 150 84 l 3 -3
Here Comes Handsome
I figured you can't move forward
without clearing the deck first.
That's the age we're at, both me and Akane.
That's cold!
Hey, what was that for, Aoi?
It's foul.
Adults and your woolly belly! It's all foul!
Ao.
Hey Tsugu, get me a towel please, would you?
Tsugu!
1st
CITY OF
MUSIC
FESTIVAL
Entrance
Hey, Akane?
Where should I put this?
Oh, I'll take it.
Sorry for making you do all this on a weekend.
Not at all! I'm not in a club so I have plenty of free time.
I'll help all I can till the show begins, day after tomorrow.
Aioi!
Hey!
Ignored again.
Hello.
The lighting director was looking for you to confirm positions.
Oh, got it.
I guess he was also looking for Shin— I mean Mr. Kanamuro.
Ah.
Alright then, I'll make sure Shinnosuke stands out.
What? But...
This is his hometown, right?
I suppose it's complicated for him.
Complicated?
I've always been in the background,
but he actually made a solo debut a while back.
But it was with just one song and that was it.
Yama.
Motoyama.
What's up?
Aren't you gonna help prepare for the festival today?
I will, but
I thought I'd tell you first.
I like Ao.
A first love thing.
What are you blushing for?
I-I'm not blushing.
B-But you're just a precocious runt.
Well, for now I am.
But by the time I get a full-time job,
our less-than-ten year age gap won't mean much.
W-Well, yeah.
Since Ao's not great with academics,
I'll have to pick up the slack there.
I intend to become a man of value.
I see.
You've got balls.
The only thing is, now I've got a rival.
Eh? For real?
Yep.
So, how do you feel about Ao?
H-Hey! Wait a second!
Tsugu, think calmly now.
That's what I should be telling you.
Well, I...
Look, in my experience, Akane just shot me down.
Until then, Aoi was just a little kid.
Anyway!
I'm just the spirit of Shinnosuke, so in this form
even if she were to fall in love with me, it'd never work out.
Yeah. I agree.
That's why,
Hey, come on.
How long are you gonna ignore me?
Stay away from me, Jezebel.
Woha, that's quite an extreme label.
Didn't I tell you already that nothing happened?
You can't expect me to believe that!
A scoundrel plus a Jezebel equals illicit sexual rela—
Look, I was surprised myself too.
He was totally serious the whole time.
What a wuss.
Where's the prince who'll take me away from all this?
Ohtaki, where's the sign-in sheet I asked you to take care of?
Sorry! I left it on top of the cart by the entrance!
If you go there
It's said that all your dreams
Will come true
Why'd you stop?
Keep playing.
I had a feeling that when I moved to Tokyo,
all my dreams would come true.
But they didn't.
But your dream did come true. You play guitar for a living.
It's not like I planned on joining
a backup band for an enka singer.
Still—
I'm not complaining.
I'm grateful to Mr. Nitobe.
I'm satisfied to at least be involved with music.
But I'm not sure if it was worth leaving,
considering all the things I had to give up.
Then, can I request a different song?
Her Blue Sky.
How'd you—
I listened to it, your solo debut song.
That's my dark past.
I like it about as much as I like Gandhara.
I used to not like it at all
The horror movies or your caramel flavored kiss
I just couldn't get into it at all
And yet here I am, screaming and searching for your face beside me
Dankichi Nitobe style!
The pit in my empty, vacant heart is so dark that I can't see a single thing
What's up with that? Sing normally!
Next, math teacher Saito style!
The pit in my empty, vacant—
Akane
and
the one who can make her laugh like that,
can only be
Shinno, after all.
Alright, thank you very much.
Ugh, my stomach hurts.
Sheesh, you were supposed to sing normally.
You know, it's still nice hanging out with you like this.
It's like I can relax.
I'm thinking about coming back.
It's not like there's a future ahead of me with my current job.
You can't!
How do I put it?
It's like everyone else got a solid job and is settling down.
Maybe I'm at a point where I should be doing the same.
Don't!
If you do that, then Shinno will disappear!
What're you on about?
In this day and age, thirty or so is still a youngster, right?
It's too early to settle down.
For me, there's something here that only I can do.
I haven't given up on anything yet.
Yep. It's from here on and out.
I see.
That's right.
Here on and out, huh.
Are you going back?
Yeah, I'd better get going.
See ya.
So even Akane can cry like that.
I never knew.
The last time she cried...
How long has it been since I last saw her cry?
Akane, can you get me the—
Jeez.
Strategy Notes
for
Aoi
©
Akane Aio
Strategy Notes
Strategy Notes
Strategy Notes
Strategy?
Strategy Notes
for
Aoi
©
Akane Aio
Strategy Notes
for
Aoi
©
Akane Aio
Strategy Notes
for
Aoi
©
Akane Aio
for
Aoi
©
Hey, Aoi! Are you oka—
Yum!
Come on, Aoi, if you've got nothing to do, help me out a bit.
No way!
You're good at making deep-fried food so the ingredients
shout with joy when a talented person uses them for cooking.
Well, I suppose.
What's this burden l was on about?
I always had the feeling that Akane could do anything.
But
she only acted like she's perfect.
All for me.
Huge success in making Aoi happy!
It's all because she's been working so hard.
And yet, I—
What the hell am I doing?
Oh. It's just you, Ao.
What happened to using our password?
Jeez, you scared me.
I like you, Shinno.
Listen, I'm flattered but
think about it properly for once.
I'm just a living spir—
Shut up!
I mean, your voice is so kind.
Someone with a voice like that generally says comforting and compassionate things!
Even if you don't mean to comfort me,
your voice is wonderful and warm
but it kinda makes me sad so I don't wanna hear it.
For now, just let me get all my feelings out.
I like you, Shinno.
Not Shinnosuke, but you, the Shinno who's here in front of me.
I want to be with you forever.
Rather than having you return
to Shinnosuke, I want you to stay here!
Ao.
But
I love Akane even more!
And Akane still loves Shinnosuke.
If I think about Akane's happiness,
then you would...
I have no idea what I should do anymore.
Tell me, what should I do?
Don't touch me!
If you touch me, it'll only make me like you more!
Th-Then, what'd you want me to do?
You've got no idea either, do you?
How could I?
Then!
Never mind!
Hey, wait! I said wait!
Please!
Please,
wait.
I can't chase after you.
I can't even if I wanted to.
All I can do is see you off from here.
I don't have any idea either,
of what'd happen to me if I returned to my original self.
But watching you run off crying like a brat
and being unable to do anything about it...
I'm not crying.
I'm not crying!
It's the rain!
Hey, why am I even here?
Why?
Concert Hall
CDs from the City of Music
Morning.
Um..
I'm sorry about yesterday.
Th-There's no need to apologize!
I was totally pushing it.
But—
Well, uh—
It's not here!
Performers Waiting Room
Are you missing something, Mr. Nitobe?
My pendant! The one I'm always wearing is missing!
Pendant? Oh! That gaudy looking one.
It's the source of my energy.
All the feelings I've received from people
all across this land are stored inside of it.
Without it, I won't be able to sing the local heart.
I won't be able to sing the heart of enka!
That phrase sounds awfully familiar to me.
Mr. Nitobe, it wasn't in the car either.
Mr. Nitobe.
Well, when was the last time you saw it?
The last time?
In that case, we could—
Photos
Oh, the Wado Ruins.
Oh, there it is!
Isn't that Mitsumine Shrine?
Seems like you had a blast.
I mean, you've got women in your arms in every photo.
That's the rapport I have with the locals.
So these pictures are from yesterday.
Ah, check this.
The pendant's missing from this photo on.
Oh, right.
Which means...
The last place he had it on it was...
There!
Ah, that tunnel!
Charming, isn't it?
There was a fence but I just went through it like this.
That's it!
Yeah, it did have this sort of survival instinct feeling to it.
Then I'll go look for it.
Huh? Are you sure?
In the meantime, please prepare for rehearsal, Mr. Nitobe.
B-Be careful out there, Akane!
Akane!
Aoi?
Is something wrong?
No.
Be careful.
I will. And you do your best at the rehearsal.
All right.
Having faith that my pendant will return to me,
let's do what we've set out to do.
Let's make the most out of everyone's support.
There's no time to relax!
The fact that it's coming from you amazes me.
By the way, where's Shinnosuke?
Ah, he said he had to stop by somewhere,
so he'll meet up with us later.
Sheesh, why'd he have to come this far out?
Tremors?
I'm sure I felt a tremor before.
Yes, this is Nakamura.
Really?
Yes.
There's nothing on the news yet.
Huh?!
Yes, understood. Okay.
What's wrong?
There's been a landslide near Hino.
I gotta go back and issue a warning from the Tourism Bureau.
A landslide?
What?!
Apparently it happened in the mountains,
so we don't have any confirmed damage at the moment.
Oh, I see.
That must've been the earthquake I felt!
It's been raining a lot lately.
That's a small mercy.
Hino? That's near the tunnel where Akane went!
Is Akane—
Ao!
Calm down. Use your phone.
Aioi.
No good. It's not going through!
Hey, you're over thinking it.
Negativity doesn't do any good.
Be positive! Act positive!
You've got no right to say that.
Anyway, I'm going to City Hall.
I'll let you know if something comes up, so wait here!
Akane
Sorry, Mr. Nitobe, but you should wait here too.
Certainly. Please be careful!
Akane
Tsugu, take care of everyone else!
Right.
Ao.
Hey, Aioi?
Yeah, so can you send a car—
Huh?
H-Hey! Ao!
Where're you going?
Why is my high school self here?
I see. It's as I thought.
Have you come to pick up the Akane Special?
How did you...
The treasured guitar that Akane went with you
to buy after saving up from your part-time job.
Looks like it's been abandoned for years, though.
Pathetic.
Just because your dream didn't come true,
that's no reason to sulk.
What would a kid like you know?
I don't even wanna know about some grimy old man.
You...
Shin—
Shinnosuke?
Why?
Is something wrong, Ao?
That's right, Shinno! Akane is—
What?!
A landslide?
And Akane got—
I don't know yet, but
Michinko is looking into it right now.
She should be fine, but
I can't reach her and I have a bad feeling about this.
Come on, don't spook me.
Well, for now, let's wait for Michinko.
How can you be so calm about it?
Why're you just standing there?!
Why?
Hurry up and go look for Akane!
Why aren't you doing anything?
I mean, even if I go now—
If you don't—
H-Hey.
If you don't go, who will?
Don't disappoint me.
Shinno.
Weren't you supposed to become a big musician
and come back to take Akane with you?
Instead you're a member of some backup band.
And to an enka singer?
That's outrageous!
Shut up.
Pathetic!
I feel like I've been dunked in a swamp of puke!
To think I'll become someone like you—
Shut the fuck up!
Stop it!
Even if that's true,
I'm out there doing something each day!
Yeah, you've become hopelessly better at the guitar.
With all your playing, I bet you could make a living anywhere!
This world's all about luck and connections!
Just because you're good, doesn't mean you'll make it.
You don't know anything, you brat.
Yeah, that's right, I don't know anything!
Because I never left this place.
What?
Shinno.
That day, when Akane told me she wasn't going to Tokyo,
I was extremely shocked.
Going to Tokyo, forming a band, performing at concerts, making a major debut and enjoying every single day.
That was my dream.
But it was all under the assumption that Akane would be with me.
I know I said I'd become a big musician and come back for her, but nobody really knows what could happen.
At that point, some part of me decided that
I didn't want to go anywhere and stay here forever.
That's what I thought.
But
you left!
You moved forward!
Come on, make me believe it.
I'm you, right?
Then make me believe it!
I'm sure a lot of things won't work out.
But still, in the future,
that I might end up like you,
make me believe that!
I...
Forget it!
Shin—
What... are you doing?
I'm going!
I said I'm going!
You can stay here and whine
forever like the old geezer you are!
Why?
I might've been frozen in time,
but my feelings for Akane will never change!
No one can beat me on that, not even you!
A-Ao?
Me too!
When it comes to feelings for Akane, I won't lose either!
Didn't you tell me not to touch you, Ao?
Shut the hell up!
Oww.
There.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
What the hell was that?
Well then, we're gonna go.
What're you gonna do, old man?
Wh-What am I supposed to do?
I...
Let's go, Ao!
Huh? Wha—
Hey! You guys—
Don't think you can get away saying whatever you want!
Wait! Shinno!
I used to not like at all
You're going too fast!
The horror movies or your caramel flavored kiss
Hey! Wai—
No way!
I just couldn't get into them at all
And yet here I am, screaming and searching for your face beside me
Here I come, Akane!
He's flying? What the hell!
Where'd that come from?
The pit in my empty, vacant heart is so dark that I can't see a single thing
This is awesome! How am I doing this?
My body starts to run despite having no ground to
That's what I wanna know!
Aren't there any taxis around here? Damn countryside!
A shower begins to pour from the red stained sky
It hits me and the smallest shadow I've ever had begins to flow
I can't keep my blurred, blue memories hidden anymore
You know, when I saw that photo, it all just clicked.
Like what?
At the time, he had to lock away
his feelings in order to move forward.
Because I still want to experience those same days one more time
But now, he has decided to confront them again.
You, you, you, you, you
Always, always, always, always
Are the first one to leave
Tell me, tell me, tell me, tell me, tell me
Why, why, why, why
Why'd you disappear into the sky without saying goodbye
So he doesn't come to regret these feelings that I have.
Look, we can't let cars go any further until the area is confirmed to be safe.
You can go back to the nearest station—
It's fine!
Here, keep the change.
Hey!
Only cars can't get through, right?
In that case—
Hey, aren't you Shinno?
It's me! Abo.
A shower begins to pour from the red stained sky
Woah.
Long time no see! When'd you—
I'm sorry!
I'm in a hurry! Can't talk right now!
Hey, wait! Where're you off to in such a hurry?
It hits me and the smallest shadow I've ever had begins to flow
To Gandhara!
That's why I was here.
I held my hands up high in the air and really felt like I could reach it
Regrets, huh.
I know of one.
People with demon faces start to spin around and swoop down on me
When you can't support the feelings of the ones you love, you'll regret it for the longest time.
I'm gonna take the nightmares you've been having of not getting to see the one you miss
I know that because I couldn't support Akane.
Turn them into clouds and eat them up, because they make you sad
Ao?
That's why I'm gonna help you and Shinnosuke.
A shower begins to pour from the red stained sky
It hits me and the smallest shadow I've ever had begins to flow
Wha—
I can't keep my blurred, blue memories hidden anymore
Because I still want to experience those same days one more time
What was that for?!
Well,
They say babies stop crying if you blow a puff of air.
You know, I want to know how blue the sky is
The heck?
So I'm chasing after it, chasing after it
Shut up.
The sky is so blue.
Let me reach it
I've always been so focused on leaving
that I never realized it was this beautiful.
Yeah.
It sure is.
Found it.
Good grief. All that trouble over this.
Look at you, even in the middle of this emergency.
I swear, you've got nerves of steel.
Shinno?
There you are!
Where's the other me?
Where's Akane?
I see.
Preposterous, isn't it?
It's definitely you, Shinno.
You believe me?
You're here right in front of me, after all.
It's scary how nothing fazes you.
But I'm glad.
It's dark in here.
If it were bright, you'd see how old I've gotten.
You'd probably be disappointed.
Ah, sorry, but I've already seen how you look now.
What? When? Where?
In that temple room.
When you went to check on Ao
and when you brought rice balls.
Really?
They were kelp again.
The rice balls. I kept telling you
I wanted mayonnaise and tuna,
but you always used Ao's favorite kelp.
Sorry about that.
But you know,
I get it now.
The frog at the bottom of a well
doesn't know the vastness of the sea
but it does know the blueness of the sky.
You liked that expression.
Shinno?
Mayo and tuna can't beat kelp, huh?
Not after you know how blue the sky is.
She's gotten cute, hasn't she?
I don't know about that.
She's grown, sure.
But she's short-tempered, tactless, and not very bright.
She's straight as an arrow.
Straightforward and dumb.
That's why she reminds me of you.
I'm glad.
Your sister, Ao is the most
precious thing in the world to you.
I'm glad I fell in love with you.
You can't!
It could collapse at any moment, so unless you can fly—
Let go of me! Akane is still—
What're you two doing?
Akane! Thank god—
Aoi!
Whoa! Akane, you're heavy.
Heh, mean.
More importantly, are you all right?
It was nothing! You're such a worrywart.
What are you talking about?
We were all worried about you!
I'm sorry, Aoi.
Sorry to make you worry!
Jeez! You should be!
Huh? You're going home by yourself?
Yeah.
What? Why? We can all fit in here.
N-Nah, four people is a tight squeeze in your car, Akane.
I'll catch a taxi on my way back.
In that case, I'll—
Nah.
The three of you should go.
Aoi?
Later then, Shinno.
Sure.
Thanks for everything, Eyeball star.
Huh?
Is he asleep?
It's fine, isn't it? He worked hard.
You know,
He said I had moved forward.
But I haven't made it across yet.
He reminded me that I'm only halfway through.
That's why, I don't want to give up just yet.
And I'm not giving up on you either.
The three of us, huh?
I see. Aoi is about the same age as I was back then.
Maybe I'll try making rice balls with mayo and tuna next time.
What'd you mean—
Huh?
I'm not crying!
I'm not
crying.
Stupid Shinno.
The sky
is too fucking blue.
———
I'm sure the future we dream of
Is round like the stone I found back when I was young
I used to think there's no such thing as these scars
Just this quite and peaceful feeling
The extraordinarily ordinary man left in the pursuit his dreams
I wrote my dream on my chest and threw myself out into the ocean
The air feels weirdly muddy because I'm crying for some reason
See you later, I'll say it again throwing those stones at the sky
I'm gonna be crushed by this overwhelming power, by this loneliness, this toxicity
Evoke a unique world where there are miracles
Goodbye, the shadow of that boy from the future
Let us meet again at a place where we can call home
The blueness of the sky is like the palette of the eye
Let me dive in and let me wrap it up, even tears on your side
I'm sure the future we dream of
Is like a story out of a picture book with glass shoes and flying witches
I believe that for no strange reason
Hey baby! I grew up somewhere between all the sweat and laughter
I'm gonna be crushed without seeing happiness and the flowers that bud out in the field
I hope they all bloom in the end and light everything up
Goodbye, the dream of that boy from the past
Will we meet again at a place where we can call home?
The blueness of the sky is like the oasis of the heart
Let me swim and let me dive in, let me return here again
Goodbye, the shadow of that boy from today
I'm sure we'll meet again at a place where we can call home
The blueness of the sky is like the palette of the eye
Let me dive in and let me wrap it up, even tears on your side