At first, I just wanted to become
an adventurer so I could help people.
At least... that's what I thought.
I want to be an adventurer!
Special Episode: The Priestess's Log
You're a priestess, aren't you?
Yes.
I'm an adult now, so I wanted
to help other adventurers.
This will act as your ID in the guild.
Your identification tag shows that your rank
is porcelain, the lowest rank for adventurers.
So I'm a beginner.
Yes.
It will also help identify you if something were to happen to you, so make sure not to lose it.
Yes, ma'am.
And that ends your registration.
You can find quests on the board there.
Please go ahead and find one suitable for your rank.
Or you could join a veteran adventurer's party and—
Hey, wanna go adventuring with us?
Huh?
You're a priestess, right?
My party's missing a priest and we've got an urgent quest. So we were looking for at least one more person.
Would you come with us?
An urgent quest?
We're gonna go slay some goblins.
Goblins?
Yeah, they attacked a village, stole supplies
and livestock, and even kidnapped some girls.
We need to hurry up and save them.
Um... You're all porcelain-ranked, right?
I'm sure if you wait a little while,
other adventurers will show up...
With the four of us, we shouldn't have
any trouble dealing with goblins.
Right?
Come with us.
Make up your mind already.
Okay. If you think that I can help you.
On my first official quest,
I wasn't able to save a single person.
I'm so sorry...
I'm so sorry.
That's one...
And that makes two.
Um... Who are you?
Goblin Slayer.
Within that dark cave, I met Goblin Slayer.
He was not the kind of valiant hero
or savior that most would imagine.
All he cared about was killing,
slaying, and annihilating all the goblins.
Children?
They multiply fast.
If we had waited any longer,
there'd be about fifty of them,
and they would've attacked.
You were lucky.
Are you going to kill them?
Of course I am.
They hold on to grudges for life.
And the survivors of the nest learn
from their mistakes and adapt.
There isn't a single reason to let them live.
Even if there was a good goblin?
A good goblin? I guess there might
be one if you looked really hard.
But in the end, the only good goblins are
the ones who never come out of their holes.
That makes twenty-two.
I had heard rumors that he had an unfortunate past.
I'm not aware of the details of what happened,
but if that event hadn't occurred,
he probably would've never taken the
mantle of Goblin Slayer upon himself.
In order to find something I could do,
I decided to help Goblin Slayer slay goblins.
Eventually, we joined a group of adventurers who
wanted assistance in slaying hordes of the Demon Lord.
O merciful Earth Mother,
please protect us, the weak, with the powers of the earth.
Iacta!
You fool.
What... What did you do?
This is a gate scroll, linked to the bottom of the sea.
Now, then... What were you called again?
I guess it doesn't matter now.
Goblins?!
You would use this to kill mere goblins?
Goblins...
are far more troublesome than you.
Right when we all got used to being in a party together,
we ended up facing the biggest threat of our lives.
Footsteps...
I can't tell how many but there's
something strange among them.
Here they come!
A hob... No...
A goblin champion.
We'll cut our way through.
Indeed. Let my blade assist you.
U-Um...
Six.
You can go all-out.
Understood.
Damn it, there's a lot of them!
No use complaining about it!
You holdin' up over there?
Some... what...
Seventeen.
Goblin Slayer!
Orcbolg! Did they get him?
No!
The Protection...
How could this be?
Calm down and concentrate!
Long-ears!
You stupid goblins! Unhand her!
N-No...
Let go of me!
Why, you...
Bullshit.
I heard that assassins like using string
made of human hair as a killing tool.
Apparently it doesn't break easily or come undone.
Go! Hurry up and heal her!
Thank you for the assistance.
Orcbolg!
Beard-cutter!
Sir Goblin Slayer!
Kill it!
Hey, take a good look, goblin!
Who's next?
You?
Or you?
Bless the stars. We somehow made it.
How is she?
She will survive.
Had the wound been any deeper,
there would've been nothing I could do.
I see.
I'm... sorry...
Don't worry about it.
Gob... lin... Slay... er...
These things happen...
U-Um, uh...
D-D-Did you see?!
Yeah.
Don't worry.
You don't have any scars.
I couldn't protect Goblin Slayer.
I was reminded of just how inexperienced I still was.
When I was young...
Huh?
I thought if I took a step, the ground
beneath me would open up and I would die.
There was a time when I hesitated
to even walk because of that.
It's not impossible, but no one worries about that.
That was really strange to me.
She and my sister laughed at me for it,
but it took me a while to realize that I still have to walk, no matter how scared I am.
So that how it is.
It is.
Even now, I'm scared to death.
I'm thankful that you're helping me,
but you don't have to.
I told you I was going to do what I wanted to do.
Did you?
I did.
You really are hopeless, you know that?
Sorry.
I don't want to hear that.
And then, I realized that he was still
haunted and tormented by the trauma of his past.
When one of the most important
people in his life was in danger.
He went...
to slay some goblins.
O merciful Earth Mother,
please protect us, the weak, with the powers of the earth.
Protection!
I-I'm sorry...
I'll... never do anything like this again...
I-I'll go back to the forest...
and live peacefully...
Like hell that's going to work...
Lord? Lord, my ass.
You're just a goblin.
Just a filthy little goblin.
And I'm...
Goblin Slayer.
That's one goblin head...
Goblin Slayer!
O merciful Earth Mother,
please place your gentle hand upon this being's wounds.
Heal!
I'm sorry.
I ended up only using two Protections.
Yeah, thanks.
Please don't push yourself so much.
I can't win if I don't.
Goblin Slayer!
You said you wouldn't push yourself anymore!
Goblin Slayer...
Please try to think things through a little more!
I'm sorry.
It's because... I trusted you.
You truly are such a hopeless person.
Goblin Slayer is truly hard to work with.
He barely speaks, and he doesn't care how he kills goblins.
He had fought alone for so long.
I want to help Goblin Slayer.
To our fallen comrades, our victory,
the farm, the town, adventurers and of course,
that weirdo over there who never
talks about anything but goblins!
Cheers!
Hey, Goblin Slayer...
Do you mind if I ask for a reward, too?
What do you want?
Please take off your helmet.
Why?
I kept my eyes closed that other time
because I was so embarrassed...
I think you look a lot cooler this way!
Ah, now this is the face of a warrior!
I am no longer the newbie adventurer with silly dreams.
Hey... Let me see...
You have excellent features indeed, Beard-cutter.
I hope that I can now provide a ray of hope
Hey! Get outta the way!
to those cowering in despair, deep within a dark cave, crying and calling for help.
Right now, my hope is that I can be
like the person that I admire so much.
If you ever need help, we'll always be there for you.
So, it has nothing to do with luck...
at all.
I see.
That would be nice.
I'm still going on many adventures with him.
The other day, we received a letter asking Goblin Slayer if he would save some adventurers who were in trouble.
And then...