At first, I just wanted to become
an adventurer so I could help people.
At least... that's what I thought.
I want to be an adventurer!
Special Episode: The Priestess's Log
You're a priestess, aren't you?
Yes.
I'm an adult now, so I wanted
to help other adventurers.
This will act as your ID in the guild.
Your identification tag shows that your rank
is porcelain, the lowest rank for adventurers.
So I'm a beginner.
Yes.
It will also help identify you if something were to happen to you, so make sure not to lose it.
Yes, ma'am.
And that ends your registration.
You can find quests on the board there.
Please go ahead and find one suitable for your rank.
Or you could join a veteran adventurer's party and—
Hey, wanna go adventuring with us?
Huh?
You're a priestess, right?
My party's missing a priest and we've got an urgent quest. So we were looking for at least one more person.
Would you come with us?
An urgent quest?
We're gonna go slay some goblins.
Goblins?
Yeah, they attacked a village, stole supplies
and livestock, and even kidnapped some girls.
We need to hurry up and save them.
Um... You're all porcelain-ranked, right?
I'm sure if you wait a little while,
other adventurers will show up...
With the four of us, we shouldn't have
any trouble dealing with goblins.
Right?
Come with us.
Make up your mind already.
Okay. If you think that I can help you.
On my first official quest,
I wasn't able to save a single person.
I'm so sorry...
I'm so sorry.
That's one...
And that makes two.
Um... Who are you?
Goblin Slayer.
Within that dark cave, I met Goblin Slayer.
He was not the kind of valiant hero
or savior that most would imagine.
All he cared about was killing,
slaying, and annihilating all the goblins.
Children?
They multiply fast.
If we had waited any longer,
there'd be about fifty of them,
and they would've attacked.
You were lucky.
Are you going to kill them?
Of course I am.
They hold on to grudges for life.
And the survivors of the nest learn
from their mistakes and adapt.
There isn't a single reason to let them live.
Even if there was a good goblin?
A good goblin? I guess there might
be one if you looked really hard.
But in the end, the only good goblins are
the ones who never come out of their holes.
That makes twenty-two.
I had heard rumors that he had an unfortunate past.
I'm not aware of the details of what happened,
but if that event hadn't occurred,
he probably would've never taken the
mantle of Goblin Slayer upon himself.
In order to find something I could do,
I decided to help Goblin Slayer slay goblins.
Eventually, we joined a group of adventurers who
wanted assistance in slaying hordes of the Demon Lord.
O merciful Earth Mother,
please protect us, the weak, with the powers of the earth.
Iacta!
You fool.
What... What did you do?
This is a gate scroll, linked to the bottom of the sea.
Now, then... What were you called again?
I guess it doesn't matter now.
Goblins?!
You would use this to kill mere goblins?
Goblins...
are far more troublesome than you.
Right when we all got used to being in a party together,
we ended up facing the biggest threat of our lives.
Footsteps...
I can't tell how many but there's
something strange among them.
Here they come!
A hob... No...
A goblin champion.
We'll cut our way through.
Indeed. Let my blade assist you.
U-Um...
Six.
You can go all-out.
Understood.
Damn it, there's a lot of them!
No use complaining about it!
You holdin' up over there?
Some... what...
Seventeen.
Goblin Slayer!
Orcbolg! Did they get him?
No!
The Protection...
How could this be?
Calm down and concentrate!
Long-ears!
You stupid goblins! Unhand her!
N-No...
Let go of me!
Why, you...
Bullshit.
I heard that assassins like using string
made of human hair as a killing tool.
Apparently it doesn't break easily or come undone.
Go! Hurry up and heal her!
Thank you for the assistance.
Orcbolg!
Beard-cutter!
Sir Goblin Slayer!
Kill it!
Hey, take a good look, goblin!
Who's next?
You?
Or you?
Bless the stars. We somehow made it.
How is she?
She will survive.
Had the wound been any deeper,
there would've been nothing I could do.
I see.
I'm... sorry...
Don't worry about it.
Gob... lin... Slay... er...
These things happen...
U-Um, uh...
D-D-Did you see?!
Yeah.
Don't worry.
You don't have any scars.
I couldn't protect Goblin Slayer.
I was reminded of just how inexperienced I still was.
When I was young...
Huh?
I thought if I took a step, the ground
beneath me would open up and I would die.
There was a time when I hesitated
to even walk because of that.
It's not impossible, but no one worries about that.
That was really strange to me.
She and my sister laughed at me for it,
but it took me a while to realize that I still have to walk, no matter how scared I am.
So that how it is.
It is.
Even now, I'm scared to death.
I'm thankful that you're helping me,
but you don't have to.
I told you I was going to do what I wanted to do.
Did you?
I did.
You really are hopeless, you know that?
Sorry.
I don't want to hear that.
And then, I realized that he was still
haunted and tormented by the trauma of his past.
When one of the most important
people in his life was in danger.
He went...
to slay some goblins.
O merciful Earth Mother,
please protect us, the weak, with the powers of the earth.
Protection!
I-I'm sorry...
I'll... never do anything like this again...
I-I'll go back to the forest...
and live peacefully...
Like hell that's going to work...
Lord? Lord, my ass.
You're just a goblin.
Just a filthy little goblin.
And I'm...
Goblin Slayer.
That's one goblin head...
Goblin Slayer!
O merciful Earth Mother,
please place your gentle hand upon this being's wounds.
Heal!
I'm sorry.
I ended up only using two Protections.
Yeah, thanks.
Please don't push yourself so much.
I can't win if I don't.
Goblin Slayer!
You said you wouldn't push yourself anymore!
Goblin Slayer...
Please try to think things through a little more!
I'm sorry.
It's because... I trusted you.
You truly are such a hopeless person.
Goblin Slayer is truly hard to work with.
He barely speaks, and he doesn't care how he kills goblins.
He had fought alone for so long.
I want to help Goblin Slayer.
To our fallen comrades, our victory,
the farm, the town, adventurers and of course,
that weirdo over there who never
talks about anything but goblins!
Cheers!
Hey, Goblin Slayer...
Do you mind if I ask for a reward, too?
What do you want?
Please take off your helmet.
Why?
I kept my eyes closed that other time
because I was so embarrassed...
I think you look a lot cooler this way!
Ah, now this is the face of a warrior!
I am no longer the newbie adventurer with silly dreams.
Hey... Let me see...
You have excellent features indeed, Beard-cutter.
I hope that I can now provide a ray of hope
Hey! Get outta the way!
to those cowering in despair, deep within a dark cave, crying and calling for help.
Right now, my hope is that I can be
like the person that I admire so much.
If you ever need help, we'll always be there for you.
So, it has nothing to do with luck...
at all.
I see.
That would be nice.
I'm still going on many adventures with him.
The other day, we received a letter asking Goblin Slayer if he would save some adventurers who were in trouble.
And then...
They went your way!
Leave it to me!
Great job, ladies!
Oh, whoopsie.
Come, now, pay attention.
Hey, Wizard!
I know.
May I ask for this dance, milady?
But of course.
Sagitta
Tonitrus
quelta
oriens
raedius!
iacta!
I guess that about does it.
You probably shouldn't let your guard down.
I'm not.
Even though we may face goblins... Nay.
It's because we get to face goblins
that adventures are worth going on.
Fear not.
I have a brilliant plan!
Dear Goblin Slayer,
I have a request for you.
It's about a noble's daughter
who left home to become an adventurer.
She departed after accepting a quest and hasn't been heard from since.
Her parents requested that the guild find her.
This isn't a rare occurrence.
The problem is that the quest the noble girl has undertaken involves slaying goblins.
O merciful Earth Mother,
please bless us, the wanderers in the darkness, with holy light!
The guild came to me for help, but you were the only one I could make this request of.
Please consider lending a helping hand to that poor girl.
I pray from the bottom of my heart that you return safely.
Best regards.
Great job with the Holy Light back there.
Huh?
U-Um, I... Thank you very much.
First there were two, then seven, and this makes nine.
Altogether, that's twelve.
I don't like how they gathered all hostages in one spot.
I also don't like how the bodies
of the dead villagers are intact.
Do you think there's another ogre?
I'm not sure.
Ow...
Damn it...
What's going on?
Talk about slow.
You used Stupor to put even the hostages to sleep?
Their stench is wretched.
How many bodies?
I counted four.
Sir Mage had three, so our total is seven.
So altogether, we have nineteen.
I thought I counted twenty at first.
Are you the mayor?
Y-Yes.
We're adventurers.
What?
Adventurers?
A silver rank? Could you be... The Goblin Slayer?
Thank you for coming!
Do you have an herbalist in your village?
A priest would also do, so long as they can perform a miracle.
The only priests around here are
the traveling priests that pass through.
We do have an herbalist, but...
All right. We'll help tend to the wounded.
We don't have many potions ourselves,
so you'll have to settle with miracles and first aid.
Orcbolg!
So there were twenty.
You little... You're not getting away!
Use this.
What's with that arrow?
The tip was all loose.
I modified it to be like that.
What?
I'll explain later.
We'd like to stay at your inn for the night.
Also, we'd like information on any
adventurers who came here before us.
And if you have one, we'd like a map of the mountains.
That's fine, but as for payment...
The goblins are more important.
Once we get some rest, we're going after them.
This is so nice and warm.
Looks like you're still growing.
Stare...
Not fair.
Eek! What are you talking about?
What do you...
E-Everyone else should've joined us.
Well, we've got "The best medicine is alcohol!"
And "Dirt suits me much better."
And as for Orcbolg...
He's keeping watch.
If you don't make a move, he's going
to be that way right up until the end.
Though we did get to come this far north
because of that, so I guess I don't mind.
Um... Did you leave your forest because you got bored?
You're half right and half wrong.
I mean, I had a duty and felt fulfilled doing it.
But one day, I saw a leaf being carried downstream.
I wonder how far it'd go, and then I just never looked back.
I chased after the leaf, ran through the trees,
and before I knew it, I was outside the forest.
I jumped across the rocks in the dry riverbed...
What did you find?
A dike. One that the humans had made.
I'd never seen one before,
but I thought it was pretty interesting.
That's where the leaf had stopped.
Say, humans die after living for about a hundred years, right?
Well...
I wonder why you guys can't live longer.
Maybe I'd understand if I was human too.
And if you were born human,
you'd wish you were as beautiful as the elves.
I'm sure if you were born an elf,
you'd wish you were born human.
I guess you never truly get
what you want in this world.
Apparently, the adventurers on the rescue mission before you hoarded all the food.
And they refused to slay any goblins if the villagers didn't give them food.
That's basically a threat.
Then again, it's possible they needed the food.
What do you mean, "needed" it?
Pursuits can last a while sometimes.
Well, we don't have that much time on our hands.
We don't know what the nest is like
or how many goblins are in there.
There's a chance that the adventurers are still alive.
It is possible.
Apparently, the last time they were
seen, they looked quite weakened.
If goblins were going to have a nest, it'd be here.
I wonder why they didn't go
back underground immediately.
So, wood and food. Which means...
Yeah.
They're trying to starve them out.
Orcbolg, why did you give me an arrow like that?
When you shot that arrow,
the tip came off, leaving only the shaft.
So?
The steel was poisoned.
Unless they dig it out of their body,
their flesh will rot, spreading sickness their nest.
It won't take care of all of them
at once, but it'll be a huge blow.
I still can't fathom what goes
through that head of yours.
I-It's so cold!
It's going to be dark soon.
Once we've warmed up, we're going in.
I never knew a place this cold even existed.
Come on, drink! It'll warm you up!
Come to think of it, isn't it your goal to become a dragon?
Indeed.
Oh, I know!
Once you become an immortal dragon,
I'll come over and hang out with you.
It'll probably take about a thousand years, yeah?
You can't imagine how boring that is.
You won't be able to bear it without any friends.
I see...
A dragon that talks about his adventures slaying goblins.
A dragon that's visited by an elf.
And a dragon that loves cheese, right?
Not bad at all.
Right?
In any case, let us first concentrate on the matter before us.
Careful. There are spears in there.
Wow, talk about malicious.
Goblins are capable of laying such traps?
Who knows?
I don't see any totems.
Perhaps they don't have a shaman.
I'm not sure, but I don't like it.
They were capable enough to attack that village
and dispose of the adventurers that came before us.
There must be someone intelligent among them.
We'll strike from the right!
O merciful Earth Mother,
please bless us, the wanderers in the darkness, with holy light!
Holy Light!
Seventeen.
No hob, no spellcaster, but they have arrows.
Let's go.
Here we go!
First one's mine!
Time to work, you gnomes!
Roll grains of sand together, and it shall become rock!
This is going well, Beard-cutter and Scaly!
Indeed.
Got it.
Ten!
Eleven!
Thirteen!
The enemies will pick themselves back up soon.
Right!
O merciful Earth Mother,
please bless us, the wanderers in the darkness, with holy light!
Seventeen.
You okay there, long-ears?
Ow... Sorry. I messed up.
I'll heal you right away. Is it poisoned?
Here. Let us remove the arrow first.
Stay still, okay?
What's the matter?
The shaft...
Where's the tip?
Still inside.
They actually learned?
Does it hurt?
I-I'm totally fine.
Do you think there was poison?
I don't think so... but...
I'll do it. Get me some fire.
Huh?
You got it.
Huh?!
Dance, dance, salamanders.
Let us borrow some flames from your fiery tails.
Bite down on this.
I'm going to gouge out the tip.
N-No way!
That leg is gonna rot off otherwise.
And once that happens, we won't be able to heal it.
Could you at least try to make it hurt as little as possible?
I'll do my best.
Seriously, don't make it hurt, okay?!
I can't guarantee that, but I'll do my best.
It's still throbbing.
A-Are you all right?
I think so.
Can you shoot arrows?
Of course I can.
Then let us all proceed.
She's still breathing.
Looks like the mission is complete, right?
This is a shrine, isn't it?
I wonder if a priest from the evil sect was here.
Um, this...
That's awful.
It doesn't appear to be a goblin totem.
I believe it's the green moon.
It's the sign of a god.
The deity of external knowledge, the God of Wisdom.
The green moon?
You mean where the goblins come from?
Would they heal the goblins with
miracles and teach them to use them?
The God of Wisdom is a rather eccentric god, but...
Perhaps it was a dark elf
or a high-ranking priest of the evil sect.
What? I doubt that.
If you control a bunch of goblins,
but you only use them for looting,
doesn't that make you as dumb as the goblins?
So it thinks like the goblins, leads the goblins,
heals them, attacks people, and is a follower of evil.
A priest? It couldn't be...
A goblin paladin.
The reason goblins attack villages
is because they're low on food.
If we just wait here a few days, I'm sure
they'll get impatient and come jumping out.
Way to go, Sis.
Well, if that's all it takes, that'll be great.
We'll be in trouble if we get hit by a blizzard, though.
What do you think, spellcaster?
I'll do whatever she wants. She's our leader, after all.
As I said, it's just a matter of time.
It doesn't look like they're coming out today.
Maybe they've got their guard up now.
I'm sure they'll come out at any moment.
They're goblins, after all.
Sorry, Sis. I'll be right back.
That's what you get for eating snow.
We don't have much firewood
left to continue melting the snow.
We need to think of something.
Let's keep watch a little longer.
I'm sure the goblins are suffering right about now.
We'll follow your orders. You're our leader.
You can't possibly be suggesting that
we flee without even fighting the goblins!
As tired as we are right now,
they might just overpower us.
We don't have much food or firewood left.
You're content with people laughing at us for being the adventurers who ran away from some goblins?
That's all I could get today.
How about this?
One of us could go down to the
village to get supplies and food.
But who would go?
You should go.
I'm the only one doing any work around here lately.
I'm done with this crap.
Agreed.
To be honest, I was against it from the start.
Very well.
I agree that's the most logical option.
Ah, lady adventurer, you're back.
How are things going?
Well, um... We're still working on it.
Really?
I was wondering if you could spare us some food.
How did things end up like this?
Why are goblins giving us so much trouble?
Those stupid goblins...
G-Goblins?
It won't come out...
My sword won't come out!
No... S-Stop!
Stop...
No!
Where are the others?
Dead.
I see.
I want to ask you something.
Just answer as well as you can.
Do you mind?
What were you doing?
Starving them out.
I thought it would work.
I see.
We would all work together and raise our ranks.
I thought it would all work out.
I see.
I guess things like that happen.
Hey, wait.
What?
Are you Goblin Slayer?
That's what they call me.
Ow...
Goblin Slayer...
How's your wound?
I'm fine.
It still hurts a little, but it's been treated.
I see.
So you were talking about a
God of Wisdom back in that cave, right?
What's his deal?
The God of Wisdom is the deity of external knowledge.
So he's a god of knowledge?
The God of Knowledge that we believe in has dominion over intelligence, reason, and the truths of this world.
He guides those who wish to know the unknown.
He believes that the suffering and frustration experienced on the path to gaining knowledge are important.
But he provides knowledge indiscriminately to one and all.
As a result, ways to destroy this world are created.
And he's not interested in the
innocent lives that are lost because of it.
Now my head is starting to hurt in addition to my leg.
Whatever the reason, the problem is goblins.
Their lair must be elsewhere.
It seems there are some ruins higher up here.
What sort of ruins?
A dwarf fortress.
Ah, the dwarves' fortress from the Age of the Gods.
It's not gonna be easy to get in from the front.
You got any ideas?
I just thought of one.
I'll go, too.
You can't.
We came here on a request from your parents to save you.
You should head home and talk to them first.
I have to get it back.
Get what back, if I may ask?
Everything.
Everything that I've lost.
A true dragon is one who has his honor.
A dragon without honor is no dragon.
H-Hey, what if she dies?!
Well, you might die, too.
All of us might die.
All living creatures eventually die.
You elves know that better than anyone.
Well, yeah, but...
We should take her with us. Otherwise...
I'm neither your parent nor your friend.
If you have a request, you know what you need to do.
I know that.
I'll get the reward money and pay you up front.
And I'll go with you.
What can you do?
I know the way of the sword, and I can cast lightning spells.
Very well.
Is that good enough?
As long as you're okay with it, Orcbolg.
Then let's go slay some goblins.
I don't agree with this!
Why are we being treated like spoils of war?
Because it would not make sense
if it was me or the other men.
Do you hear those fools yapping, Sir Bishop?
Soon enough, they'll become offerings
to the God of External Knowledge.
Let them do as they please for now.
Um... Are you cold?
I'm fine.
Well, I'm cold, so I'm going to get a bit closer.
Do as you please.
Hey, I guess you aren't completely dense.
Thank you very much.
I planned to give these rings to you at the fortress.
They have breathing spells sealed within them.
Rings that allow us to breathe underwater?
That should help with the cold a little.
You should've given these to us earlier!
These are amazing.
Right?
Here. You should use it, too.
I don't need it. I'm not cold.
Yes, of course.
Now you can't run away.
I am the Bishop of the Green Moon,
a humble servant of the God of External Knowledge!
Open these doors!
Don't worry. We're all here with you.
Here they come.
Is that the goblin paladin?
No.
I request an audience with the
honored paladin who rules this fortress.
Yes, I bring offerings.
Let us throw them in the dungeon and cut off
their hands and feet so they can't run away.
Are they actually communicating?
Apparently, it's the miracle of telepathic communication.
Ah, so we shall begin with this girl.
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
Why, you...
Calm down!
Well, I did expect this.
Hey, give it a rest already!
Goblins need to die!
Oh, for crying out loud!
This was to be expected.
It's better we keep an eye on her if she's going to be reckless.
Yeah, but...
P-Please, calm down.
You should be the angriest right now.
Calm down.
Take care of your wound first, then heal her.
Her hand will rot and it'll leave a scar.
Right.
There were survivors among the hostages.
Go check on them.
Right.
I'm not sure if I'm up for the task alone.
Come along, Scaly.
Well, spellcasters are known to be physically weak.
Let's go.
I understand how you feel, but it might be better to hold off until later.
Why did you bring that girl?
Because we need her.
We need her?
Now that we've attempted this,
there's only winning or losing.
That's not what I'm talking about here.
I know.
At least, I believe I do.
Get ready.
Sorry.
I lost my temper.
It happens.
To you, to her, and to me.
Even you?
Yes.
I can't picture it.
Is that so?
Yes.
I see.
Will the hostages be all right?
Probably safer than taking them with us.
What's that sword made of?
Aluminum.
The blade was forged from
a red gem and tempered with lightning.
Mind letting me have a closer look?
So, where are we headed?
We should head to their armory first.
But before that, how many spells
and miracles do we have left?
Um... I have three remaining,
and the other two have four and three.
So we have a total of ten.
We forgot to include the girlie over there.
Two.
So we have twelve remaining altogether.
No, we should save our two lightning spells if we can.
Will that let me kill goblins?
If all goes well, yes.
Well, we're counting on you.
All right.
Why did you give her the torch?
She was hurting from being left out.
I wanted to give her a part to play.
Didn't you notice? She seemed a bit
bashful when I gave her the torch.
This seems a bit different for an armory.
Well, this is a dwarf fortress,
so we might find some ore deposits.
But would the goblins actually reinforce their blades?
Regardless, leave this to me.
Hey, girlie. Help me out.
We're going to carry some of this out of here.
Beard-cutter isn't exactly kind to his weapons.
I believe I do make good use of them.
You're not going to get very far with just a short sword.
Guess we should see what kinds of swords they have.
I don't need any other sword.
So you don't want an actual sword.
Very well. Now we're getting to know each other.
How are we going to get along
if you don't speak your mind?
Well, are we ready?
Go for it.
O great ancestors who sleep within the great whiting.
Take these with you through the burden of time.
Is that a prayer for decay?
Indeed.
Now we have the prisoners from their
dungeon as well as their weapons.
All according to plan.
Yeah.
We messed up.
This is a goblin coronation ceremony.
And a coronation ceremony needs a priest.
A cleric to conduct the ceremony.
Well, he's sort of dead in the dungeon.
Wh-What's wrong?
O merciful Earth Mother,
please lay your revered hand upon this child's wounds!
Get down!
Are you all right?
Y-Yes.
At least they tried.
How are you doing over there?
We're surviving.
Let's split up.
I'll act as the decoy.
My physical strength would be
optimal to carry the prisoners out.
I will take up that task.
All right, let's go.
All right.
Don't.
I know... I know... I know.
But this isn't...
Why do they get to... laugh and do whatever.
It's all my fault again.
This all happened because of me... Because of...
I need my sword back! I need it...
Give it back... Give it back!
I want to go home!
Father, Mother... I've had enough...
I see.
All right.
Huh?
I'll retrieve your sword.
I'll kill the paladin.
I'll kill the goblins.
I don't mean just one or two.
I don't mean just a single nest,
or just the ones in this fortress.
I'm going to slaughter all the goblins.
So stop crying.
O merciful Earth Mother,
please bless us, the wanderers in the darkness,
with holy light!
Let's go. Keep your head down.
O-Okay. Should I cast Protection?
I'll leave that to you.
Okay.
I'm leaving the rear to you.
All right.
It'll be okay.
That's one.
And two.
Three.
They're coming from behind!
How many?
I'm not sure, but a lot!
All right.
I can't keep up...
Ugh! Why are there always so many of them?
Take that!
Thirteen.
Well done.
I wonder if they're doing okay up there.
What? You worried about Beard-cutter?
I'm not really worried about Orcbolg.
I'm worried about my two friends up there.
You got a problem with that?
Well, you're an elf.
I guess you're partial to this friendship business.
Throughout the ages, flooding it has been standard to conquer a castle.
But starving the enemy out is also a worthy option.
All right.
Pull!
Twenty-nine.
We're making good time.
Let's fall back. Get ready.
Goblin Slayer!
Took you long enough.
Do it. I'll buy us some time.
All right.
Okay...
Tortrus...
O merciful Earth Mother,
oriens...
please provide us protection...
Iacta!
Take that!
We're ready!
Never forget your adventurer tools
when heading out for adventure, I guess.
Where are the others?
I'm so sick of those goblins and their stupid holes.
You're telling me...
Right on time.
We're safe.
Thank goodness.
Everything good on your end?
Yes, we're fine.
We did it.
Yes.
Beard-cutter, what happened to your sword?
I threw it.
Some things never change.
Thanks.
Nothing beats the feeling of being able
to shoot as many arrows as I want!
Could you not say such scary things?
My apologies.
I'll take care of the rear.
Back me up.
You got it!
Gnomes! Undines!
Make me the finest cushion I'll ever see!
Who do you goblins think you are?
Move!
Ugh!
There are fewer now. I'll take over. Go.
Eight, nine.
We can't just descend to the village like this.
There was a valley, wasn't there?
It's not far from here.
Then we'll go there.
Here, Beard-cutter!
Thanks.
Thirteen.
Right, what's next?
Give me a shovel!
You got it!
My apologies...
Nineteen.
Twenty.
Go on ahead. I'll crush them here.
Can you handle it?
Of course I can.
That was the last of the weapons.
Then I shall lend you mine.
Leave the backup to me.
My spells are about to run dry.
Goblin Slayer...
Save your miracles.
I will. I know you're counting on me.
I have a plan.
Right.
Fire when I give the signal.
All right.
He learned.
You rude little bastards!
In that case...
You fell for it.
Goblins are not bright creatures,
but they aren't complete fools either.
However, you are an idiot.
Fire!
Tonitrus
Oriens
Iacta!
I have a bad feeling about this.
Oh, damn it!
O merciful Earth Mother,
please protect us, the weak, with the powers of the earth.
Protection!
Goblin Slayer!
Where is he?
Where's Goblin Slayer?
Probably toward the bottom,
if he was carried away by the snow.
Probably.
It's better if we don't talk too loudly just yet.
We should walk over to find him.
Aren't you worried about him?
Of course we are. He is our comrade, after all.
But, you know...
He is Goblin Slayer, after all.
I messed up.
I should've prepared for the
impact rather than the lack of air.
G-Goblin... Slayer?
Are you all right?
We should be asking you that.
I thought it was weird.
There's no way Orcbolg would give us these rings to breathe underwater for no reason.
Were you planning this from the start?
To an extent.
It would've been nice of you to explain that.
Don't be foolish.
What if the enemy heard our
strategy and tried to thwart us?
Yes, but you just make us worry when
you don't tell us what's going on.
I've got plenty to say to you, but this is
definitely how an adventure should be.
Adventure...
I see.
So this was an adventure.
Hey.
I found it.
I managed to get the sword,
but the scabbard was washed away.
I guess the avalanche was a failure, after all.
You sure cry a lot.
We somehow survived another year.
Let us praise the Gods of Fate and
Chance, and of Order and Chaos!
Cheers!
Happy New Year!
I worked real hard last year.
Yeah, I guess.
I swung my spear around and killed some monsters.
So that goblin-killing guy is no match for me.
Yeah, yeah.
You worked hard. You sure did.
So what're you gonna do now?
I'm planning to go see my parents
and have a long chat with them.
I'd like to make graves for my fallen comrades, as well.
I'll decide my path after that.
Yeah, that sounds like a plan.
You always need to take care of your friends and family.
Sweet nectar of the gods!
Sir Goblin Slayer should've joined us.
No kidding.
I never get a chance to drink with ol' Beard-cutter.
Not all encounters end up favorable,
but one should still cherish fate.
I, um... I'll make sure to write.
Of course.
Please feel free to write us about anything at any time.
I'll make sure to send you plenty of replies.
I'll make sure to write lots and lots.
Oh, me too!
I've always wanted to write a letter to a friend.
Maybe I'll write some letters, too.
I rarely get to meet girls my age since I work at a farm.
Working at a guild isn't much better.
By the way, where's Goblin Slayer?
Don't you want to share your
childhood friend with the rest of us?
I'd be lying if I said I wanted to share him...
But I guess I'm feeling kind of generous this year.
Indeed.
You should always play fair.
You can come over.
Do you keep watch like this every year?
Don't ask stupid questions.
R-Right...
They always try to attack on New Year's.
Here. They wanted me to bring this to you.
I see.
You even set up camp out here.
I spent ten years of my life slaying goblins.
But it can't be said that goblins don't evolve.
Do you know what the goblin paladin was plotting?
No...
Metal refining.
That can't be...
The dwarf fortress, mining tools,
and that girl's aluminum sword.
Ore that was forged with lightning.
There's only one possible conclusion.
I need to do whatever I can against them.
I can't let my guard down.
Honestly...
All you ever talk about is goblins,
every time you open your mouth.
I bet slaying goblins is more important
to you than hanging out with your friends.
No.
See? I knew it...
I don't like big and noisy crowds,
but I don't mind when everyone's having fun.
It's always better to have someone watching your back.
It's cold out here.
I'm aware.
I see.
Now that that's settled, let's have some dinner and do our best until morning.
I see. Oh, I forgot to mention...
What is it?
I'm looking forward to your help this year as well.